Then this is the most ideal you ever had.
Let's go.
Is it a camera's ready?
Ah!
I love it!
It'll take a few hours.
That's awesome!
You made it!
You finally made it.
Finally, finally.
Yeah, isn't it good?
Yeah.
Oh, why?
Hey everyone!
I'll say it in half a cup.
Yeah, if you know this is Timmy, he's actually part of the cast.
I think it's part of the couch, wasn't it?
Yeah, couch.
Yeah.
How's it feeling?
It's not feeling good.
You excited?
Yeah, glad to finally be here.
Oh!
I'm so excited to be here too.
Do you want to do a season of savorov?
Yeah, let's go.
This looks like the most old-looking date of it.
Yeah!
It looks like a normal date.
Who might be more?
Just how do you be?
Sizzes, paper, rock.
Oh!
Okay, I think you should go first.
Oh, sure.
Oh, okay.
Oh!
What do you call a blonde during a handstand?
What?
A brunette with bad breath.
This is currently so bad.
I don't get it either.
It's because of the dryness and the oils.
Oh, like, grove.
Oh, I got that either.
Are you loving?
Oh, shit.
I just want to say, if I don't win this, I'm embarrassing.
Oh, you shaking?
Yeah.
Oh, he's shaking.
Well, it's fucking weird.
Cheers.
That's not too big.
Yeah.
They all can't be bangers, mate.
No.
But please, make one of the best.
What disease do you get from having sex in a gym?
Don't know.
Ferbys.
Yeah.
Hmm.
I thought you were going to love for that one.
No.
Okay.
All right.
Why is parking a car like finding a girlfriend?
Why?
All the good ones are taken.
So you just stick it in the disabled one and hope no one finds out.
Ah!
Oh, shit.
I think it's so true.
Oh, that's a good idea.
That's a good idea.
Oh, he's in the game.
Oh, my God.
He's like, he's like, coffee disabled sports today.
All right.
You love it?
Cheers, Timmy.
I'm laughing.
What?
Oh, my God.
That's a fucking shit, guys.
Yeah, I know that happens to me the first time.
You have to, like, not laugh.
Yeah.
Yeah, like, that's the point, right?
It's like tweet or D and tweet or dumb.
Fucking shit.
What a pre-sale to get rid of flies in church.
Let us spray.
It's gonna be.
Hmm.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Yes, that's how it works.
What do you call a guy with no arms?
And no legs and sits at your front door?
What?
Matt.
Do you get it, Peyton?
No.
Cause he was drunk.
Right?
Like a dormant.
Always a dormant.
Oh, sorry.
You're not mining, get that thing.
Oh.
It's really surprising that you're like jokes.
You have to really think.
What?
Matt.
You're not.
Thanks a lot, Roy.
Come on, man.
I'll pack a brother.
These are riddles, TV.
He's delivering away now.
Hmm.
How do you get Pikachu on a bus?
You poke him on.
He's...
Fine.
I'm a smiling.
Right?
What's your business?
You're verbally smiling.
That's a lot.
I'm a smiling.
Wow.
Okay.
Where do girls have the most curly hair?
Where?
Africa.
Who would you find these?
Oh, give me that one.
That's...
I don't need.
You're gonna find these.
Thank you.
I don't need.
Don't...
Hey, Timmy.
What's there?
No.
Wait.
It's all yours.
You have to find these.
Africa.
Oh, give me that one.
I don't need to.
Thank you.
It's all yours.
I'm glad we're all done.
Hey, Timmy, what's bare and boring?
What?
Your walls, but not anymore. Thanks to display.
Do you quickly get bored with how your room looks?
With display, you can transform it in no time.
Hang new metal posters in seconds
and switch them out whenever you want.
No tape, no nails, and no tools like Timmy, required.
Forget the hassle of paper posters.
Displays are all metal. They're durable.
And the colors be packed.
Plus, with over 2 million artworks,
you'll find the perfect piece to pin up your blank space.
Timmy, you have a line here.
Plus, display offers fast delivery.
Not too fast, I hope.
Thinking of a last minute gift for someone?
Display has got you covered.
Find metal posters for anyone,
whether you're seven or 77.
Display comes gift-ready.
Display is celebrating Black Friday, starting November 22nd.
Now they're offering the biggest discounts of the whole year
with up to 44% off your order.
Also, for the first time ever,
our texturiddesignant will be discounted too.
To get your exclusive discount on your new displays,
use the link in the bio or shop using the code, yeah, man.
Your walls won't ever be barriguing!
Head to displayed.com today.
So?
Yes.
An old man and young girl go across the road.
Yeah?
Who do you hit first?
I don't know.
Neither. You hit the brakes.
They are all fucking riddles actually.
I'm making me laugh.
These are dead facts.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
I'll look service on the outside.
Teeth.
I'll look at the killer.
Yeah.
Thanks.
How do you say I'm constipated in German?
Tell me.
I'm far from pooping.
You're gonna laugh.
I think it's a laugh that is making me laugh.
Got him.
That's a cool one.
Thank you.
I know I thought of you, but I'm sorry.
I like that.
That's what's constipated.
How do you get Hessian herpes?
I don't know.
From rooting old bags.
She was fun fact of the day.
I love her delivery.
Do you know what Hessian is?
Yeah, it's a bag like a Hessian sandwich.
Yes, I know.
I just wanted to give it a shot.
It just wasn't that funny.
I understood it.
Thank you.
Oh, Timmy asked me if I understood something.
That's cool.
Got some real battle on the mind.
Shit.
This is the final stage of the event.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Have a have a have a have a have a have a have a have a have a have a have a have a have a have seafood.
What do you call a bra in Dutch?
A stop and from flopping.
Flopping.
Flopping of.
All right, stop it from flopping.
You're just stopping in flopping.
Flopping.
You'reocrine.
You're gonna get it.
Get em out.
No, I do.
I feel like that's only reserved for cat that one.
I got my own cat.
How did that go up?
Did you see me on your own face?
It did.
I did it.
I did it right.
What the hell is that?
I don't know.
I'm not going to be on my own face.
What the hell is that?
It's all a boy.
It's all a girl.
What do you get when you cross Timmy and a disco ball?
A shimmy.
Oh my god.
That was it.
Thanks for that one.
I thought you like it.
Shimmy.
That's what I'm going to be like.
You good?
Yeah.
Not really.
Yep.
How can you tell if a cabbage is boiled?
You boil it.
The wheelchair floats at the top.
You are just like...
Every disabled joke you can think of.
Don't let a chromosome get you down.
Oh my god.
That was so quick.
That's on to me.
Quickness.
It doesn't look like any quick.
Me talk faster time.
Timmy's allowed to say these as well.
What do German pedophiles and chocolate holics have in common?
They both love Kinder.
Yes.
Thanks for the yes, Matt.
Love that.
It matches.
Yes.
More German.
That's just zergort.
Overjogging.
Please go down.
What's the difference between yourself and a bus?
What?
When riding a bus, everyone gets off.
I have no respect.
You got it.
Just in case.
Wow.
Timmy, I feel like that just really crossed the line.
Why did Stephen Hawking not make it to heaven?
It wasn't an elevator.
Only stairs.
Nice.
I can't go getting to heaven.
What do you call a nuns wheelchair?
What?
A virgin mobile.
Timmy, what the fuck?
Because I was like, was it mobile or maybe ill?
Bummy Spell and was not good day.
It's a hot one again.
It's hot and sour.
Ready?
No, really ready.
What is...
What did you say?
I thought it was my go.
I'll listen to you.
It's gone.
Give me a good one.
Make me laugh.
The artichewer on you today.
I don't know.
What if I tried to say something?
I tried to say it.
Oh, right.
You're getting sassy.
Che.
You had a chee.
Ben, can we just...
This guy.
What is her son Mavin Laden's favorite drink?
A double Manhattan.
Oh, that's right.
I can kitty.
Yeah.
How do you know that the toilet is in lunch at your house?
The what?
The toilet.
Yeah, the toilet.
How do you know that the toilet has in lunch at your house?
Because he took stuff from the fridge?
Your dog's going.
Who knows, it's gonna be nice, no?
Yeah.
Let's keep the toilet work, sorry.
Change, change, change, tie it to Asia.
Yeah, I know you.
What is her?
No, Germany's got talent.
Why?
Because no one will ever be greater than Hitler.
What?
That's like that was budget.
You're lovely, Jimmy.
Oh my god, Jimmy.
Where the cat was?
Oh, I wish I could come back.
That's all I have to say.
Oh, Jimmy.
What do you call a person that can't pay for gender reassignment surgery?
Transaction declined.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Sorry, Jimmy.
They're funny, very nice, they're really very clean.
They're gone.
And tequila really hurts.
You want it?
Tequila really hurts.
Which is tequila?
So because I had to do a pill please.
Oh!
Oh, I can't come on, please.
You got to go on.
What do you call a disabled kid with a gun?
Special forces.
Jimmy.
What a good accent.
I'm not going to talk to you.
I just...you?
Oh my god. Can you do the punchline again?
I want to see the front of your face do it.
I want the gun.
Major Buffy.
Okay, well I laughed at the start.
Good work, little pig.
Okay, what board is on stupidity?
Mexico and Canada.
Hey, hey.
I'm another one.
Can I say another one?
What's a narcissist favorite thing to say?
Hey, I'm Rory Lowe and I'm a comedian.
Oh my god.
It's an early roast.
You just need all my mind, Rory Lowe.
Sway.
Tired of money.
It's a real need to show off to her.
How I'd do this roast now.
I learned something new the other day.
Oh yeah?
That the parapussy will throw you further than Dona-Mont.
Motivational speaking.
That was a fun tune.
That's one.
It was a fun tune.
That was a fun tune.
Mar-a, the pussy can pose here.
You are not being disabled to an everybody but oh my god.
Bells and tv.