Things happen to you.
Like, is it your house in near Dover?
Oh, yes.
Yes.
I'm glad you brought that up because I do rent my house.
I'm glad you're here.
If you're interested. Two other people.
I mean, two other people.
And it's the nearest house to France,
which is very important in this story.
And it's 425 pounds a week.
And it sleeps.
It sleeps.
It sleeps people for four, seven nights.
It's clean. It's very cleaner.
Yes, yes.
Anyway, one day I got a call from the police
and they said, are you the owner of the gun in placement?
And I said, yes.
And they said, are you aware that it's been used
as a drop for criminals to get rid of their drugs?
Or, you know, it's a drug drop.
I believe that's the phrase.
And I said, well, of course I didn't know what do you mean.
And they said, well, people have rented it.
They were a gang, a gang from Liverpool, I think.
And they took my house and they dropped the drugs in the bay.
Or they, and there was a helicopter that came on the roof.
It's a flat roof, yes.
And they had cocaine.
They had 30, something like 13 million pounds worth of money.
What? No, no, it wasn't like a little thing.
This was a massive thing.
What?
30 million.
Jesus Christ.
I'm so fucking insane.
Of cocaine.
That is actually...
That was freaking hard.
No, I don't...
Oh, not super-no. That was like wholesale.
Oh, wholesale?
Listen, I'm...
It's wholesale.
Oh.
Well, of course I was horrified because I didn't know.
I mean, I don't have anything to do with the people
that rent it.
I just take the money, you know?
Yeah.
I need to go more.
And I was... Well, I could get more for it
because it's really lovely actually.
That's all that...
But what's upsetting, Mummy, was when it was reported, of course,
in the Daily Mail,
all the people online said,
oh, she must be in it.
You know, she's part of the gang.
Oh, no.
They were calling me Miriam Escobar.
I'm back for a Western.
I mean, we see Tom Hanks gun-token, which we rarely see.
Well, I don't have...
I don't wear one.
I am given one later on.
So it's not like, you know, I'm not doing the root and toot
and kind of...
But I ride a horse and I drive a wagon and I've discovered...
So I'm not a rider per se, but I did learn.
I had a fabulous...
Got to know a fabulous whore named Wimpy,
who was my horse.
And I don't know if anybody here has written a lot
or made a Western Emily has a couple of Westerns
under her belt, as I recall.
Emily, my darling, how are you?
How for you?
Wonderful to see you.
It's good to see you.
Emily Glunt.
Do you know what I'm about to do a Western?
Like, next year, I'm doing a six-part Western
and we were just discussing how allergic I am to horses
and I do every scene with a horse, you know.
I'm going to be anti-histamine up to my eyeball.
Do you have to kiss the horses and make those noises?
Doesn't that...
Isn't that what happens in Westerns to make out with your horse?
You develop an affection for those beasts.
You and Wimpy.
You and Wimpy...
You're kind of with...
Every morning you throw your arms around Wimpy,
say, how are you, my darling, little chestnut?
So do you nuts about you?
Which you sort of have to do because I have a feeling
that horses, honestly, they would much rather live in a world
without human beings climbing on top, though.
And they know the moment you climb on their back
that you're terrible at riding.
I mean, I've been learning right now,
I'm in London now rehearsing for it,
and I go riding three times a week
and every time they give me a different horse
to see how you fare with one that's more slightly
or one that's less of a Ferrari.
And I got on one of the other day called Rusty.
Oh, my God!
It almost took off with me. It was terrifying.
I couldn't walk the next day. Rusty did me in.
Rusty did me in. Rusty did me in.
Oh, wow. Is that the name of the film?
That's what it is.
Oh, my God.
There is...no, of course, this isn't the spotter.
But so there are, you know, there are set-tos,
you have some touchy moments and words,
and I'm seeing them, can I?
But can we talk about the sex scene?
It's one of the best sex scenes I've seen.
I've seen it.
I think talk about the sex scene.
It's one of the best sex scenes I've seen in forever.
That sex scene.
Who put that to go?
Yo, seriously.
Oh.
No, it's not.
It's not like they're kind of like prancing around naked.
It's just, it's a really clever...
Who put...do you guys put that together?
Did we just go up, put it together?
No, we had nothing to do with that.
Excuse me, I'm just starting over my universe over here.
And of course, it's not just you in it.
Other screen legends, Jeremy Iron.
He didn't the sex scene?
No, I'm seeing it.
Jeremy.
Jeremy was in a...
Jeremy was particularly.
He was great.
He was buying the camera.
Why are you having sex?
I'm trying to tell.
This is a breakthrough role for you, Jack,
because an American accent?
Yes.
Is doing an American accent?
What, in that clip?
Yes.
Lydia!
He was.
Was.
I feel the Oscar bars pissing away.
Oh, no.
He's so serious.
No, it was good.
It was good.
I heard it.
You see, not a lot of actors do when they're doing American accent.
They tend to just go for one region of America
and they commit to a single American accent.
I decided with this role that I would take on a tour around all 50 states.
Sometimes in the same scene.
I thought, why just do one when you can show off them all?
So I would start the scene talking like I was from New York
and then over with Sudden, I'm suddenly speaking like I'm a calligirl
and by the end of the scene they're stopping me
because it sounds like I'm from the Duke's a hazard.
I went all over the place.
But I thought, you know, just show off your skills.
You were a bartender.
I just love that you would be such a good bartender, Marker Fluff.
Thank you.
A generous...
You know, he'd do a generous pour.
He would always do a generous pour, Marker Fluff.
I would do a generous...
It's hard.
Mostly because people would be like, come on, man.
Really?
But nobody didn't eat you. How do you own cocktail?
I had the Marker Rita.
LAUGHTER
And where's the gum and gruffalo, but no.
Marker Rita.
But I ended up having, you know, I'd start early
and I'd had my Thursday night crowd, partially,
because... And I'm sorry, Sean McPherson, wherever you are.
I gave away a lot of free drinks.
It wasn't a great quality in a bartender.
But you were good dealing with drunk customers, which is...
I had the deal with a lot of drunk customers.
Which is...
I had the deal with a lot of drunk people, yes.
And sometimes they were not very nice.
Oh, no.
There would be nights where I'd be up to my eyeballs and a-holes.
I'm saying nothing.
LAUGHTER
Do you like your wine?
I don't know what it's called.
What did I say?
Nothing.
Is that a spoiler?
No!
It's nothing!
Marble, you're boring!
Oh, you went...
Oh!
So, no, wasn't there a guy who wanted a...
Wasn't there a drunk guy?
Oh, I get it!
Yeah!
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
Wasn't there a drunk guy?
Wasn't that kind of bar?
Wasn't there a drunk guy who wanted a...
A book?
Yes, there was.
Okay, tell us about him.
So, occasionally, you would get someone who was so obnoxious
and it was the end of the night and this guy came in.
And he's like, I don't know.
And he was wasted and he was such an a-hole.
And he's like, I want a Zambooker.
I'm like, come on, man.
You're doing okay.
You're like, give me a Zambooker.
And...
Did he hit his knee like that?
Oh, I thought...
Give me a Zambooker.
I'm like, okay, so I pour him a Zambooker.
Late it!
I'm not gonna let you drink, man.
I don't like drinks.
Okay, you want to let you drink?
You let you drink yourself.
Late it!
Okay.
I like the drink.
He takes it.
And it goes all over his face,
dripping down his face,
and he's like, you've been through flames everywhere.
And I'm trying not to laugh.
And he...
He beats the hell out of himself to get it out.
Give me another!
Oh, sure thing.
You want me to light it for you?
Yes!
Same thing all over me.
It was one of the greatest nights.
I sort of like him for having another one.
I love him.
He walked out with like a flaming red goat.
That brings back a really painful memory.
It was you?
No.
Well...
That was amazing.
I was like 12, 13.
I was a late bloomer,
but I had a premature mustache.
Like I had hair there and nowhere else, right?
I mean, my head, of course.
And I was begging my dad,
because kids were making fun of me.
Like, oh, you're stash, swimmer, you're moustache.
And so I was begging my dad, hey, can I please shave?
And my dad was like, you're too young to shave, I'm sorry.
But I was...
I took matters into my own hand.
And I borrowed some of my sister's nair.
Oh, no.
And for those of you who don't know, it's like a chemical hair removal.
It's a...
We got an imac.
Okay, so I put it on my lip,
but I left it on too long.
So I had a burn mark.
Just like that.
I had to then go to school,
and everyone knew I had tried,
and then I'd take my hair off,
and they're like, what the...
So all these other names,
so I'm sorry to bring up.
We'll give that a trauma, but I want to share that.
Very good.
Don't you talk to someers
and tell you how your height difference
makes those stunts more complicated?
I can't keep going.
I didn't say it. It's a day of sitting.
That is a good story.
It's a good story.
Well, you see, there's a particular stunt.
I don't know if it's in this, but there's a...
He, Spider-Man, swings us on top of a bridge,
and he places me there.
That's the bridge.
Yeah, that's the bridge.
We eventually jump off of that screaming.
That's right.
So he's supposed to gently, you know,
rest MJ on the bridge and walk away from her.
Because of our height difference, I obviously...
If we're on the same...
Yes, we were attached.
We were attached. I would land before him.
Because my feet obviously hit the ground before he does.
So...
What would happen?
Well, it's called a bottom mark, isn't it?
And the bottom mark is to basically...
It's a thing that they do in stunts
that is basically designed to stop you shattering your kneecaps.
Oh, yeah.
So, Zendaya would land, and I'm the superhero.
I'm supposed to look cool.
And she would land, and then I would sort of land like this,
and my feet would swing from underneath me,
and then she would catch me.
And then you'd like to...
Oh, I'm not doing that.
You're actually very, very lovely about it.
And you were like, oh, my gosh, thank you.
It's something nice to be caught for a change.
We're full of us.