What's the difference between a baby and a feminist?
At some point the baby will grow up and stop crying.
How'd it do?
OK.
What was it?
So, don't know.
So it was...
Hey!
I'm Sat.
Matt. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
First time?
Oh, yeah.
One, two.
Don't know what to expect.
Neither do I.
This is a baby rock.
Yeah.
Seezas, baby rock.
Oh!
Are you ready to go first?
Let's have a little geese in here.
Which animal has the largest chest?
What?
A zebra.
That's super close.
You're going to come out of that, Matty.
Let's give me some four-plate, baby.
Oh!
Ah!
Do me that.
Did you hear Mary Poppins stop wearing lipstick while giving head?
Apparently the super-color fragile lipstick makes the dicks atrocious.
I'm fucking impressed.
You didn't fuck that hard.
I was in that mirror a lot.
Super fragile dicks.
Fucking dicks.
We're off.
All right. Nice.
You're a lot.
You're on this one, I love this one.
No.
Thank you.
Too little.
A banana.
And a vibrator.
A sitting on a table.
The pedan attends to the vibrator and says,
what are you trembling about?
I'm the one about to be eaten.
Yeah, not bad.
I'm just getting rid of the fillers and the stuff.
Oh, we didn't do the baths.
Where's the chocolate?
Oh, next, next one.
I can't really.
I'll lose it.
Are you tightest staring into the blank space in your wall like this one?
Check out display.
With over 2 million artworks, you can find the perfect piece to pimp up that blank space.
It even comes with a magnetic mounting system, which is so easy to use, even Timmy can use it.
TEMMAR!
Forget paper posters.
Display is all metal.
It's durable and the colors pop.
Plus, with fast delivery, you'll get your art faster than you can say, I'm back, baby.
And at Display, we've got something for everyone.
We've got...
Movies.
Music.
Celebrities.
More movies.
Anime.
And art, gaming, fantasy, sports space.
And so, so much more.
So if you want exclusive content and discounts, use the link in the description and shop with code Yamad.
Say goodbye to that plain boring room of yours.
Visit Display today.
Let's see how durable these gloves...
...isn't that a bad thing?
Oh, that's a bad thing.
F***ing f***ing f***ing.
My mom died when she...
I'm sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
My mom died.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Is that a path's trick?
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
Yeah.
My mom died when we couldn't remember her blood type.
As she died, she kept telling us to be positive.
It's hard without her.
Oh my god.
That's not bad.
That was pretty good.
My mom died.
That was the...
...leaf just for that.
I was front loaded that during.
Hmm.
Oh.
I...
I let out gas while lying on my back.
But my balls got in the way.
It was a scrotal eclipse of the fire.
I'm back in the fire.
F***ing f***ing f***ing.
F***ing f***ing.
F***ing chaff, bro.
A scrotal eclipse of the fire.
F***ing f***ing.
Alright, we'll pick this up.
We'll pick this up.
Alright, let's go.
Ah.
Duped off.
Hitless favorite planet.
F***ing f***ing f***ing.
Favorite at least favorite.
What's a big gas giant, so...
Oh, my god.
There we go.
Second to make the end of it.
You fun it now.
Well, that's funny.
Shit.
You didn't give it the start, I didn't know you were.
I was waiting, I'm like, just f***ing say it.
Don't leave me up.
I've been aggressively having sex with two twins.
And uh-huh.
I want my friends to ask me, how do you tell them apart?
And I'm like, it's very easy.
Uh-uh.
Janice has a piercing on her nose.
And Henry has two big pairs of hairy balls.
Aggressively.
Uh-huh.
Harry balls are a grudge liquor.
It was the two pairs for me.
It's a different.
He has four balls.
That is aggressive.
Oh, okay.
Oh, I don't want to do this.
Now, did you hear Princess Diana was on the radio the other day?
Oh, nice.
And the dashboard and the windscreen.
Too soon?
That was good.
Oh.
A redneck walked into a protest and immediately got called a racist.
And he was like, I'm not racist.
My wife has a black eye.
No, okay.
That was good.
That was a little...
That was the way that one offs up.
Tell me, I'm going to keep this one.
Okay.
Fuck.
What does a 13-year-old pregnant girl and her unborn baby have in common?
Their mom's going to kill him.
That's three heavy ones, man.
Sorry.
I'll do a clean one.
A pedophile.
I'm Australian guy goes to New Zealand and he sees a guy fucking a sheep on the side of the road.
And he goes, in Australia, we shear our sheep.
And then the New Zealand guy goes, fuck off.
And then the baby is like, you're hearing her with anyone.
You're hearing her with anyone.
That's red, I'm just hearing her.
This is not good.
Did I'm whooping out fucking horrible?
I was doing a clean one.
Okay, here you go.
I'll give Rory Pat an Ian arguing over what makes her better pet.
Pat said he loves dogs.
Rory said, nah man, cats are better.
Dogs always be telling the cops where the drugs are.
Ian said, food is food.
What's the joke?
Food is food is food.
Don't do this to me, Ian!
That's just facts.
They're eating the pets.
That's not a game man.
You're dick.
Is it edible?
But you're absolutely.
What's your favorite breed of doggy?
We've seen with Chilly first.
I need to be a little too slow.
I never go.
Oh god.
I had sex with a disabled girl.
I handy-clapped those cheeks.
Oh my god.
Did you just...
Did you squirt?
Fuck off.
Did you just fuck off to yourself?
That was a good one.
I ran that one.
He's back baby.
Today, I found out bananas are gay.
What?
That was a joke.
That's it.
Look at the reaction on Pat right now.
Don't cut the catch cam.
It's going off there.
It's going off at home.
I'll text you.
My phone's turned off.
My uncle's a really bad antriloquist.
I'm gonna make two fingers in me and tell me not to speak.
True story.
What's worse than ants in your pants?
Your uncle.
Your uncle is a mess.
It's making my uncle...
No, whatever you keep touching on the back of my neck.
We're trying to work over each.
My uncle took my weed, so...
My uncle took my weed, so I took his wheelchair.
If I'm not rolling, no one is.
I couldn't concentrate.
You have a big sweat.
It was like all the lights.
Oh, no.
This is bad.
This is the best episode ever.
What's the difference between a baby and a feminist?
At some point, the baby will grow up
and stop crying.
What did the...
That was your fault.
That was absolutely the anti-fend.
What did the mentally challenged kid get on his maths test?
What did you get in your test, Timmy?
What test?
I'm not a tackle.
What did the mentally challenged kid get on his maths test?
Drove.
That's a fucking thing.
That's a good one.
That's a drill.
Yeah, it's a ruck.
Oh, this is not good.
This is fucking great, dude.
I tried picking up this Asian girl the other night.
I was descending into math.
I hope this is worth it.
I tried picking up this Asian girl the other night.
Sex, sex, sex.
Free sex tonight.
I was like, wow.
And a friend said, hey, that's actually her number.
66636 tonight.
29.
Okay, okay.
I'll bring it back and bring it back.
No, no, no.
Look me in the fucking eyes with this next joke.
Call him daddy.
I'm gonna call him my poem just like my search history.
Disabled.
Oh, no.
Where's Bummin?
Dude, you're Bummin, man.
I mean, I'll be there shit together for fucking months, man.
Oh, no.
Let me back that up with this one.
I just got my doctor's test results and I'm really upset about it.
Why?
Turns out I'm not gonna be a doctor.
Got you, bitch.
What do you call a Mexican baptism?
Before you say it, shall I?
Yes, what do you call a Mexican baptism?
A baptism.
Bean dip.
Oh, no.
That one!
Wow.
This is setting up the truth.
Matt was too drunk to get any of my jokes.
Oh, my God.
I said my word.
Oh, no.
No, no.
We're all bitch.
Woo!
Please go!
So when's that hate child guy?
I have to go.
Oh, my God.
We did it!