My lesbian friends bought me a gold timepiece for my birthday.
I think they got confused when I said I want to watch.
Hey guys.
Oh!
He was there!
Okay.
How are you?
I'm good, how are you?
You look drunk.
I'm fine, I don't know what you're talking about.
Yeah.
I'm a slut.
Alright, alright, alright.
Let's get this over and die with.
What does everyone seem to want to rush through these segments of me?
Okay, anyway.
Is it a weed or a weed?
Don't buy you a lip at me.
That's it.
Let's go and see what this is.
See if this paper rock.
Let me fast you.
Okay, so I haven't seen any of these jokes.
I got to punch my friends to write them down.
So let's see how this goes.
Okay.
A little envelope.
It feels like we're about to find out a prize.
This could go anyway.
Yeah, I don't know, I don't know what these...
I'm very scared.
You look nervous just from the first line.
What's the difference between a Catholic priest and a pimple?
What?
At least the pimple waits until you're a teenager before it comes on your face.
That's the first one.
That's all off, my god.
Ugh.
That's bad.
So, funnily enough, I am going to be using all replies to my story from the fans.
From the fans.
They're going to shit.
Wait, I didn't answer.
Some of these are actually very good.
Ugh.
What's the difference between a rusty bus stop and a crab with a boob job?
I can't see the bus stop.
A crab with a boob job is so funny.
I'm just not interested in this.
Are you ready?
It was a little crab with a boob job.
So, I really want to know, are you thinking of Sebastian?
Tell me the fucking joke.
I would love to, but I can't actually see the punch line.
So...
Oh my god.
I think once a cross...
No, wait, once a crusty...
Wait, once a...
I know it.
Once a crusty bus station and once a busty crustacean.
That's good.
When you were thinking about the crab with a boob job,
were you thinking of Sebastian from the little mermaid?
No, I was thinking of a little crab with big yellow titties,
like scurrying across the beach.
It's like jiggling around.
You look like two shops in here, my god.
It's so funny.
Let's put it in there.
Come on.
Ma...
We all know you like to cheat, but can you at least think?
Yeah.
Oh.
My lesbian friends bought me a gold timepiece for my birthday.
I think they got confused when I said, I want to watch.
That's pretty good.
It's really good.
I love it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
We're seeing this together for the first.
It's great.
Don't make so funny than you.
How does that feel?
Shut up.
Come on.
Just...
What do you call the assistant to...
Okay.
What do you...
What do you call the assistant to the assistant, Nutt?
What?
A cocoa nut.
These are not mine.
Thanks.
They're not mine. They're the fans.
They're delivering.
Nice jacket.
Today, Junior.
What do you call an artist with a brown finger?
What?
Pick a asshole.
That's good. That's a good one.
What happened?
Oh, it's funny.
He's a good one. He's a good one.
Genuinely, your friends are very funny.
I'll hook you up with one.
Okay.
Oh, so...
It's very great.
I had it.
You should have TV TV.
Oh, it's...
I'm afraid.
I'm from his own friends.
Dogs can't operate MRI.
Oh, y'all miss that.
He was just staring straight at my boots.
Stop killing that.
Someone get mad some water for God's sake.
I'm scared.
Stop talking to someone.
Are you okay?
He was so loud around.
This is good content. Keep going.
Happy to slap you one time.
Yeah, give me a slap.
Yeah, slap you.
No, because knowing him will just get off on it.
And I don't want to give him that.
Oh, he's okay.
I can't do this.
Have you finished your job?
I don't. I sat at the level that the woman finished.
Go on.
Are you like this one?
What do you call an Afghan virgin?
What?
Never been laid on.
That's pretty good.
Not at all.
How do you embarrass an archaeologist?
Yeah.
Hand them a used tampon and ask them what period it's from.
Ah, it's gross.
Why does the Easter Bunny hide his Easter eggs?
Why?
He doesn't want anyone knowing he fucks chickens.
Man, what did you say?
I don't remember what you said.
He будет I am certain that there's a way to describe the your
mind.
Mission end.
I hope he does this for a moment.
Five lanterns and aまあuf.
He says he's got matchingess now.
difference between male and female guys.
What?
Boo-bees.
There you are.
That sounds like cheese.
Boo-bees.
That's funny.
Oh.
What's the score?
Fuck.
I'm going to try.
I'm going to try now.
Mind you, I'm already quite tipsy.
So the fact that I'm no laughing is really concerning.
Go on.
What do I show you?
I'm going to show you.
Fuck, sorry.
Third time's a charm.
Come on, baby.
You got this.
What do I show you?
Gain ecologist and a puppy having comment?
How did you fuck that up so badly?
What?
A wet nose.
That's pretty funny.
That's great.
This is so much fun.
Yeah, I really enjoy this.
I don't know where they're going.
Okay.
Oh, God.
Oh God.
Why?
Excuse me.
I have a drink.
Okay.
Mmm, ruffies.
So you're just saying,
say, ruffies or ruffies.
Shut up and drink it.
Finish it off, finish it off.
Oh.
What's brown and sticky?
Ungudanesh.
You know what else?
What else?
My Rihanna poster.
That was a fan submitted one.
I didn't know where that was going.
I'll give you another one.
I need a drink.
Watch this comeback.
Watch me win this.
I bought a box of condoms earlier today.
The cashier asked if I'd like a paper bag.
I said, no, I'll just turn off the lights.
Yeah.
Hasn't happened to me.
I'm assuming it happens to you quite a bit.
Yeah.
No.
All right.
Oh God.
Sorry.
What's that?
I will hurt you.
You did that.
I'm sorry.
How did that really take?
What?
I'm sorry.
I don't know.
I'm a pro.
Shut up.
You were a gorilla suit.
That's awful.
That's a difference.
Hey, what's this?
I'm sorry.
I didn't do that.
I was going to do the loop.
No, no.
I'm going to have to eat rubber chicken.
I cut that out, Ben.
We're not putting that in there.
In the beginning.
You just want to see it.
Break you.
I'm gonna give him a little.
No.
I can't.
I can't do that.
Go ahead.
Get your knuckles up.
I can't do that.
Cut all that out, please.
No, please keep that in.
Oh god.
I'm not going to like this one.
Why do they call it PMS?
Why?
Because Mad Cow Disease was already taken.
Uh huh.
Well, that's the...
That's the uh, yeah.
Why is Putin still invading Ukraine?
Why?
Because once he put in, he doesn't pull out.
Topical.
Oh, this, how do you circumcise a hill, Billy?
How?
Kick his sister in the jaw.
Oh, my God.
These are so good.
Why did Andrew get followed by seven dwarves?
Why?
He was saying, selling snow white.
Not bad.
I really like that one.
Why am I taking it over?
You loved it, Bobo.
I got arrested by a female police officer.
Did you grab a boobs?
This is, this, you'll love this.
So I got arrested by a female police officer.
She told me anything you say can and will be held against you.
So I replied, boobs.
My pun client was funny, huh?
What's the difference between women and overs?
What?
Drunkman asked before getting inside an Uber.
All right.
What's the hardest part of a vegetable to eat?
The wheelchair.
Yeah, nice. All right, look at that one out.
All right, here you go.
That's a lot.
For me?
I've decided that we're going to start waiting for you
to take your shots because you really cheat the system.
Why?
Because you'll leave it and then wait for the other person
to tell the joke and then take one shot for two laughs.
All right.
What do you call an IT teacher who touches up his students?
South.
A PDF file.
Is that...
I'm sorry.
Bit slavicular?
You are? You are?
I did laugh.
I'm not a pervert.
No, he's just a pedophile guy.
I'll be a pervert, but you'll die if you lose.
I'm a pervert.
I think we'll die.
All right, go, go.
I'm running out of jokes.
I know I got a bit more.
I'll go.
What is the difference?
Hello.
What's the difference between a pregnant woman and a light bulb?
What?
You can't unscrew up.
Pregnant woman.
I didn't...
It's like I'm just going to rock the pregnant woman.
Been there.
That's...
I haven't really been a stop-same being there.
Yeah.
Because I actually haven't been there.
How do you find a blind man in a nudist colony?
He's the only one without a boughner.
It's not that hard.
Let's close.
All right.
Let's do the barb-sauce.
Yeah, yeah, please.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
All right, all right.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, some of these are in fact.
No, you got ten, you got ten.
No, because I...
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Three more left.
Please go.
Okay, um...
Hold on.
Bleh.
I'm not joking.
That's a laugh.
I've wrote it out blu-ah.
There's not a laugh.
You're back.
It's a laugh.
I also took a shot for no reason.
You've still got a full shot.
That's a laugh.
You've still got a shot.
Take your foot off the table.
I love you together.
Let's have it together.
Cheers.
You're on this chaos.
Everything.
Everything is chaos today.
Mmm.
Ugh.
When does a dad joke come a daddy joke?
When.
When he comes.
Why are you looking at the tongue thing?
I have dry lips.
I'm sorry.
I think you killed it.
I didn't have it.
I think you do it better than I do.
Dragon?
Yeah.
That's cute.
Please make that stop now.
Just be in a killer.
A killer.
Just call me a killer.
She's a very good girl.
K-SOUL.
I have to kill her.
I'm sorry, Rises.
That's so bad.
I always cause up my nose.
I've been to 20 minutes ago.
I was told.
20 minutes ago I was told that I was messing a killer.
It's a shot.
That's not an excuse.
That was genuinely the truth.
Do I look alive?
Come here.
No, you don't look like an owl.
At all.
Do you look alive to you?
Ah, never.
Bitch.
Delicious.
This is how I get killed.
You have to do it.
You have to look like an owl.
You have such different facial structures.
Okay, don't race it.
And I'm like a pervert.
I'm not a pervert.
Still a racist, not a pervert.
It's invisible.
Yeah, this is great.
It's great content.
Please make use of that.
I can't.
This one's great.
What does a homeless woman use for a vibrator?
What?
Two bees in a bottle.
That's funny.
Ah, alright.
Oh, I should probably...
Am I still doing fan jokes?
I would.
Oh, yeah.
I think it's a girl.
I don't know.
I'm a big surzer.
That's it.
What do you call a woman herfuses to give head?
What?
An oba.
Hahaha.
I don't know.
I'm a bit faster.
You're the last thing.
You're a f**king pervert.
I'm not a pervert.
I don't have my voice.
You're a sh** pervert.
I killed her, shut up.
I'm the only brown comedian on this fucking show, okay?
Oh my god, I'm so good.
OK.
Yep.
I don't blind people.
Shut up, you're probably doing it.
Shut up, Akill, no one asked you.
I don't blind people, Skydive.
Why?
Scares the shit out of their dogs.
I'm not a baby.
Sorry, baby.
I'm not a girl, my god.
Yes, I'm a girl.
I'm going to come here.
Oh my god, come here.
I have a problem.
Take the permits stuff.
I don't think anyone will like that.
I'm not a permit.
Sorry, please.