Now my girlfriend's here, I'm not licking people's feet.
This is inappropriate.
No, no.
This is my time with Tony.
Oh!
MUSIC
What a ho ho ho!
Ha ha!
That was the biggest mess.
That was the biggest mess?
Hey.
Is that a candy candy, my pumpkin?
No, it's a massive erection.
Massive.
See, Rob?
Sure.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Ah!
Oh!
Shut up, you're international audience.
You're not fucking anyway.
It's rock, paper, scissors, shoot.
So that's all Americans.
Shut up, Abby.
Oh, Abby.
I want you guys.
Do more show.
All right.
My friend came out of the room with tear-as-rolling daddy's face and he said, it's a boy!
We never went back to Thailand after that.
Oh, no.
That's cute.
That was tiring, I think.
That was tiring.
I think I'm tired.
Why did Santa's little helper have depression?
Right.
Because he had low alpha steam.
Oh!
It's pretty good.
I didn't actually know we were doing Christmas Eve stuff, so I was mostly about...
Right.
Sex stuff.
Oh, my God!
Yeah, a lot of sex offender stuff here.
What about this?
What's Michael Jackson's favorite cat?
He's always got one.
First, Michael Jackson's favorite fast food.
What?
KFC.
It's gonna be five years of interest.
That was good.
How could you do that?
Why did the Christmas decorations have sex?
What?
Because they were missled toly.
Mmm.
Pretty good.
What's it?
Between a lentil and a chickpeat?
Oh.
You've never had a chickpea on your face.
No, I have.
I've never had a led to a lot of my face.
Ah, yes!
Oh, yes!
I've never had a led to a lot of my face.
Ah, yes!
You're the joke, you fucked it up!
I couldn't have worked here, I better!
He's gonna be a free-yellow out there.
Thank you.
Oh, shit.
Cheers.
I'm sounding it out.
To Christmas.
Very Christmas, yes.
What do you call an elf wearing earmuffs?
What?
A c*****.
Relax, he can't hear you.
That's strong.
Thank you.
Collager.
What's the difference between a priest and Woody from Toy Story?
What?
Woody goes limp with a child into the room.
Oh, shit.
Ah, ha, ha, ha.
Ah, ha, ha.
I tried really hard.
I thought you laughed on that one.
Did you?
I thought I did.
I was the best.
You tried.
That's a good joke.
I'm done with the Christmas ones.
Oh, thank God.
Now you're gonna go to the funny ones.
Two Christmas crackers.
Oh.
What do you call two lesbians in a closet?
A liquor cabinet.
That's right.
All right, if we're doing lesbia wads,
why is Drain Johnson the only guy that could turn lesbians?
Because he's a rock.
Because rock bait scissors.
There she is.
That's so creepy.
Look at that girl.
She's so grown up for a egg.
You're there on Sam's 18th birthday.
There she is.
What do you guys do?
Why don't they have toilet paper and KFC?
Why?
Because it's been good looking good.
Oh my god.
Oh, I got one.
Damn, Sammy.
That's our balance.
That's good.
I love our balance.
Like a fortune cookie.
Sam's got some wicked wings.
They wing arrow.
Why don't women rub their eyes with their wake-up?
Why?
Because they haven't got balls to scratch.
This episode of Yehrmad is brought to you by Manscape.com
and their performance package 5.0 Ultra.
Featuring the brand new,
Lormaw 5.0 Ultra Electric Trimmer.
My balls used to be hairier than a gorilla's butt.
They used to be the Lormaw 5.0 Ultra.
They're now beautiful and smooth.
I keep asking people to take a look at them.
But nobody wants to.
Sam.
Thanks.
We're the Lormaw 5.0 Ultra.
They've taken precision grooming to a whole new level.
Thanks to their next gen Juleskin Safe Blade Heads,
including an upgraded trimble and an interchangeable foil blade
for enhanced precision.
Head over to Manscape.com and get your hands on the performance package 5.0 Ultra.
Use promo code Yehrmad and get 20% out.
20% out.
How much did they get?
30%.
What's a pedophile's favourite type of garden?
Is it okay?
What?
A kindergarten.
Oh my god.
Yes, that is good.
That's good.
Slice.
Very nice.
We're getting clicked.
You got to fuck that.
Christmas.
Kindergarten.
What's the difference between Neil Armstrong and Michael Jackson?
Oh my god.
Neil Armstrong walked on the moon and Michael Jackson had sex with children.
I can't look at you.
Oh my god.
That's so good.
This is one small penis for man.
Oh my god.
Look at me.
But you tell a joke.
Jesus.
If this one's really bad, can you please cut it up?
Thank you.
How do you know orphan guys aren't gay?
orphan guys?
Because they have no one to call daddy.
Oh, crossing a line.
How would that be bad?
That's a really good joke.
What vegetable is good for memory?
What?
Kick up.
Michael stuck wet up my ass and I was sick so I never forgot it.
I thought I was sharing my personal history with you.
It's good to get that out.
Why can't two Chinese people have a white kid?
Oh, what?
Because two wongs don't make a white.
Oh, that's so good.
That's actually really racist today.
No, I'm not.
You make it this soon.
You left as well.
Cool.
Tell them to the comments if you're ready.
Seth, you loved that joke.
How can you tell a girl from Tasmania is a virgin?
How?
She runs faster than her brothers.
We'll set it.
How do you circumcise a guy from Tasmania?
Kick him in the teeth.
He kicked his sister in the joke.
I'm making him funny.
What did you say?
I said my punchlines hit that.
They did it in my head.
Why do people with foot fetishes never win?
I know.
Anything.
Why?
Because I like the taste of defeat.
That's true.
I'll do you lick my foot.
What?
What are the odds you lick my foot?
How long are we going to go if I do that?
Do you know how to play that?
You get to choose.
Okay, out of five, I'll count it in.
Okay, you ready?
Five, four, three, two, one.
How to play lick my foot?
What are the odds?
Yes.
Ods of what?
You're licking my foot.
If we say the numbers out of five,
we both have to say number from one to five.
I know, but that's the whole point.
What if I win?
How do I win?
I'm really hyped for me to lick your foot.
No, no, no.
I'm fighting.
I put down from the foot.
If you get the number right, if we get the number right,
I'll lick yours.
Every other number, you have to lick right.
Okay, one in two then.
Oh, you're pretty good.
All right, you ready?
No, my girlfriends here.
I'm not licking people's feet.
All right.
I did.
Okay, fine.
All right, that's two.
I'll count down from three.
Three, two, one.
Two.
Get it back.
This is not for the content.
I don't know what to say.
People are going to walk to this.
You have to go on the other side of the table so that she doesn't get it.
Oh, sorry.
That's the thumbnail.
No, I said, ah!
Just like a rock!
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, my God.
It is that to lick the toe.
Yeah.
It was a lot of tongue.
I feel like things have escalated.
I feel like things have escalated a bit.
Can we get an employment?
Okay, okay.
Hold some jokes.
My way is good.
Guys, we've gone off track.
We should just get back to what we're all about.
You know, pitiful jokes.
Okay.
I can't remember now.
I think it was your turn, yeah.
Okay.
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Yoda lady.
Yoda lady, who?
Stop yoda lady.
Hey, got me.
All right, knock dog joke.
You're one of those?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
I eat mop.
I eat mop, who?
You eat your own poo?
That's great.
Oh.
Okay, fair.
I'm sweating up a storm here.
What's the difference between Santa and Tiger Woods?
What?
Santa knew to stop at three hos.
Okay.
Kids, you were the cheating bastard.
My girlfriend asked me, have you seen the dog bowl?
I said, I don't even know he played cricket.
I heard that one.
That's that one.
You guys just want to do that one.
That's great.
I think people would have liked that one, Matt.
I asked my dad the other day how he felt about abortion,
and he told me to ask my little brother.
I said, I don't have a little brother.
Damn.
You're a trash.
A trash.
They never go out of stock.
They never go out of stock today.
Why can't Stevie Wonder see his mates?
Till his blind.
Because he's married.
Because he's black.
Oh no.
He's free.
Things have gone off the rails.
Okay.
How does it count like it's state cooked?
Yeah.
Rare.
The silly sounding ones always get me.
That's great.
I also loved it.
You loved it too?
I can't get it on the food thing.
I need all the information.
What is my asshole?
What is my asshole and my Toyota have a common?
What?
They're both leaking trans food.
Oh my god.
I'm not a racist.
Can you say that in 2020?
I'm not going to tell you.
No.
I'm not going to tell everyone.
That's quite progressive.
Play it.
No.
I like it.
Two Indian junkies accidentally.
Can I do that again?
Two Indian junkies?
This one won't make the curve.
Two Indian junkies accidentally snort curry powder.
They both went to hospital one in for a quoma and the other one.
For a dodgy dickah.
That's pretty good.
If I had said that, I would have lost it like you.
You could have a shit.
Fuck.
I thought my hat about a control.
He's in a coma.
Very Christmas.
Is it any letter from the queen when you turn 100 now you get a text from Prince Andrew when you turn 14?
Oh my god.
Fuck.
Kill me.
God damn it.
No one will help with that.
That's good dear, right there.
Very Christmas.
Oh yeah.
Fucking blonde.
Why can't Santa have kids of his own?
Because he only comes once a year.
But couldn't he impregnate someone at that one top?
You had one shot.
Wow.
Would say to capture it.
Flood logic.
No.
I didn't know what to wear to my premature ejaculation society.
So I just came in my pants.
That's really great.
That was hip-sand.
Why are retired Nazis?
Oh that's better.
Why are retired Nazis so good with animals?
Because they're veteran Aryans.
What does she do?
I get a very...
Like a star sign.
Aryans with a master race.
I'm an Aryan.
No, no, no, not Aryans.
That was star sign.
I imagine he's like a hero.
Aryan is a star sign.
No, no, no, no.
Did you know it's not nice to laugh loud in Hawaii?
I've said this one before.
It has to be a low heart.
Were you good then?
No, I'm just a rational joke.
What one do you as a original Alan?
She's a bunch of improv.
We just say do weed accents and try and suck your tongue.
Who makes more money?
A drug dealer or a prostitute?
A prostitute?
Because she can wash her crack and reuse it.
I love it, no one's laughing at everyone's clifing.
That's it.
Thank you everyone.
I love it in the morning.
That was good.
What do you call a snowman with a six pack?
The abdominal snowman.
A little bit of web play.
Cute.
What do you call a one-legged Indian man?
What do you call it, Andrew?
What?
I hate that I love that.
What do you call a one-legged Indian man?
Balancing.
Shout out to our massive Indian fan base.
We love you guys.
There we are.
I won.
I've got a loss.
You're ahead of a loss.
What was the score?
11 or 8.
I won.
It's not saying.
Very Christmas.