What's the biggest city in America?
A B city.
What's up?
North chemistry, don't you?
North chemistry.
Should we see the paper right here?
Yeah, we can do that.
Let's go. One, two, three.
North chemistry.
You're going first.
I'll go first.
All right.
Let's start off with a little silly one.
A little silly one.
Why do they call them sausage rolls?
Why?
They don't go anywhere.
They should be called sausage steels.
They come at my ass.
I don't know.
I'm so sorry.
I wrote your silly little joke.
Sorry.
I'll just go with the whole thing.
You silly sausage.
I think I'll start with a silly one as well.
I'll go with a silly one.
What's big and what and will kill you if it falls out of a tree?
Cat.
A fridge.
It's not that silly.
That's not that silly.
That's not silly.
All right.
Did I?
Yeah, you left it the path thing.
Oh, yeah, I did, yeah.
Damn it.
I got so high the other night I gave my cat cocaine.
We did a few lines.
Yes.
Meow.
Nice.
Nice, that's for you.
Yeah.
Dude, I wrote that and I was like...
What's a racist favourite porn side?
What?
Everyone thinks I've got that racist shit?
There's a few actually.
You must be familiar with only clans.
Are these both?
It's not WWE.
It's KKK.
That was...
Forward slash a slave.
I didn't make it.
Two guys are walking down the street
and they come across a dog lick in its balls.
One guy goes,
which I could do that.
The other guy went,
and he should probably just pet it.
Oh, that's great.
No.
We're gonna be maggot, dude.
What do you call a lesbian on fire?
An LGBTQ.
It was just good.
I'm back, baby.
Oh, the sausage.
Oh, the sausages touch.
Oh, right.
I shaved my pubes into a Hitler mustache.
I call my penis the dictator.
That was for me. That was for me.
It's definitely not second size.
Oh, it's a skee.
Can we say it? Can we see it?
No!
It just looks like my film.
Oh my god!
That's what Chee said.
Chee's.
That Chee.
Love you, bro.
Why do sharks never worry about hackers?
Why not?
Because they got Surfshark VPN to protect their finformation.
That's an awful joke.
But if you want to hide your jokes, you can use VPN.
Surfshark VPN will allow you to access internet across the globe.
For any website that you would like to go to, whether it's your favourite shows,
internet that you can't get in your country.
Because I've been looking at a lot of stuff that I don't want my government to know about.
Even Surfshark can't monitor what you do online.
Surfshark will allow you to connect as many devices as you want under one account.
Whether you're using your phone, laptop or robot vacuum, Surfshark has got you absolutely covered
and you don't need to worry about protection.
Jump in a Surfshark today for 30 days.
30 days!
Money back guarantee and full customer support.
What?
So use the code Yeah Man.
Because you can get an extra four months for free using the link in the description below.
Oh, use the QR code.
Floating around here.
That's the...
It's the QR code.
Just get Surfshark.
How do terrorists feed their children?
Oh no.
Here comes the airplane.
And here comes the second one.
Oh, that's you.
That's you, ok Mr. Bob?
Oh, I just got that.
Oh, dude.
Jesus.
Oh, dude we drank this quick.
I might need a bucket bro.
Oh, dude, I picked up my bike.
That was shammer pants.
I didn't actually shoot my pants, but...
It looks like you guys have just come back from safari.
What is this?
An Englishman, a racist and a junkie walking to the bar
and the bartender goes, hey Rory, what can I get you?
That news comment?
A pervert, a brown galley and a loser walking to a bar.
Thank you.
Oh, why is Rory here picking on you?
You said stop bullying me, having an army of Indian followers will comment.
I thought I'm so scared.
Rory sucks!
No, that was good, that was funny, I like that.
What do you call a low budget terrorist attack?
7-11.
My wife got me jerking off to an optical illusion.
I said babe, it's not what you think.
No, I fucked it up, let me do the get.
How is that?
It's an additional punch.
No, it's not an additional punch.
Dude, a shot that goes outside, a kill looks weird.
I'm saying double, I thought I was the best both of them.
Oh, it's just kind of sad.
What is Ireland's favorite indoor sport?
What?
Domestic violence.
I'm scared.
I'm gonna kill him.
I just...
I just need to say that you can't get off there.
They say that sex, during sex, let me start again.
Fuck, man, sex, during sex.
You burn off as many calories as running eight miles.
Who the fuck's running eight miles in 30 seconds?
I'm sorry.
Look, I started running, okay?
I started running and I finally made it to 30 seconds.
What's the biggest city in America?
Obesity.
I'm gonna kill him.
Dude, I need one of these orange ones.
Fuck, you already poured it, dude.
First, you got 100.
I had a horrible week, man.
My wife died.
My dog ran away.
My house spanned down.
Which one of your wives?
That's not a good one.
I had a horrible week, man.
My wife died.
My dog ran away.
My house spanned down.
The only thing positive was my AIDS test.
Dude, I'm one point away.
I'm not laughing, dude.
I'm one point away.
I'm gonna go up to my door and read, dude.
I'm like, what am I going to do?
I feel like New York and the Matrix just dodged in Giggle Stood.
Is that a Giggle?
Keep hitting me, dude.
Why does the Titanic and your mum's food have in common?
A lot of drowns seeming.
Yeah, I was there watching.
I fucked that up, actually.
That was not the right one.
Well, I'll do it to that one.
Dude, you've done like 100 miles of me.
I'm so happy with these.
A lady goes to the doctors with lettuce sticking out of her underpants.
I haven't finished it yet, but I feel like I just won.
A lady goes to the doctors and there's lettuce sticking out of her underpants.
The doctor goes, oh, that's a strange one.
The lady goes, oh, it's just the tip of the iceberg.
Yeah.
Mum, mum, mum.
There you go.
They say that animals can sense disasters before they happen.
That's why my dog always barks every time it sees an Asian getting a car.
That's not funny, I respect Asians.
That's funny!
I just got back from Japan, I love the people.
You head about the disease you get from kissing birds.
Cherpes.
It's untweetable.
What are these places?
You have like a salad on the...
Hi, you're cherpes.
It's an outdated joke, it's called X, now dickhead.
Is it?
Oh, tweet.
I thought the Cherpes is an actual X.
I'm going to back over the X.
Is it you made me laugh from just being a dumb...
This is f***ing the X!
The worst thing is, Matthew Yonsi is coming to this...
She is a heavy scar.
It's like, well, it's like 11th at the morning,
and she's going to buck up in an hour,
and she's like, how is the gig going to be like?
It's been pretty good!
You're...
You're all screaming!
I'm so scared!
It's white privilege.
I need a hype and a hug.
I need a hug.
It's sad.
Oh my god.