Because the last time you guys were on the show together and Anthony and Greg, they did a boxing challenge and in a bit of a shock result, Anthony won.
Isn't it weird?
Isn't it weird that heavyweight champion of the world would beat a biscuit eating comedian?
Let's not do that.
You should have both his arms tied behind his back.
Now, so this time, this time, we've got another challenge.
But the last time, you know those boxing things that you hit the boxing thing.
So that's what we did the last time.
This time, we've gone for one of those fun, fair test of strength machines.
Okay, so if you'd like to bring in the machine, here it is.
Come down now to our test of strength.
Now, two of you are going to stand for it.
You're going to have a bit of a face off in front of it.
Okay. Okay, we're taking it seriously.
No, no, no, we're taking it seriously.
And it is a strength that I believe technique plays a huge part in.
That's all I have.
So, have a look.
Oh!
It's Paula.
Okay.
And now...
Maybe I'll be turning up.
To get us in the mood.
Okay, so, Ken Brown is going to give us a little bit of form before we do this.
You do your face off.
Come on, come on.
Okay, off you go.
Okay, ladies and gentlemen, on the left, they call him the postman.
Because he always delivers.
It's the undisputed, heavyweight champion of the world, Anthony Joshua!
APPLAUSE
Thank you.
And on the right, they call him...
How's he looking at?
They call him the courier.
The courier.
Because he sometimes delivers.
LAUGHTER
Unless he gets stuck in traffic.
Yes?
He is Greg.
Man, mountain, David!
APPLAUSE
So, here we go.
Here we go.
So, AJ, you go first.
I thought that was going to be heavier.
Okay.
You go first.
I would have...
Okay.
Okay, you go first.
You go first.
Mind the cameras.
Here we go.
So, golf.
Oh!
Oh, dear.
LAUGHTER
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
You go now.
I know my soul.
I should ask for that.
So, you're right.
I'm not training yet.
I just am on the wall.
Well, you might miss it as well.
I'm not.
Go.
Hit the bell.
Go on.
Right here.
The courier.
Oh!
Thank you.
You want to go?
Yeah.
I'm going.
Good.
Grab a hand.
Don't make it.
Do this before you go this way.
Yes.
Walk this way.
Okay.
Anthony, why don't you help Judy?
You help Judy.
I should have been a great person.
I'm going to help you again.
You can be open.
Yeah.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Please do tonight.
Just hand in the hammer to Dame Judy Dent.
Come on.
Judy Dent for the bell.
Very heavy.
I'm going to stand.
I'm going to stand very close.
I'll leave.
I'd say you're about to put it there.
Yeah.
Right there.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Are we ready?
Sorry.
Yes.
Oh!
Beautiful.
I'm going to go.
Hey.
Hi, way to go.
I can handle this.
Thank god you are really amazing!
Welcome.
That was funny.
Thank you!
Fifty-chãƒgebz darker.
Actually this is a darker, it's more romantic I would say.
Yeah, I think that was probably true, yeah.
Yes, but there's probably more sex in it.
Which...
More sex?
Yes, Jamie doesn't speak.
I mean, I make noises.
I make noises.
I make like...
American accent that noises, though.
Um, no, there's...
You know, there's actually a question, though.
Do they let you do that? I mean, like, when you're...
When you're doing the scenes, does the directors say...
More vocalization?
I mean, there's often...
There's often...
That's not... That's not good.
No one comes like that.
LAUGHTER
That's all I do.
Where do you...
No, that way, dude.
There's some scenes where...
They will play music, maybe, a bit of...
If it's a wide shot and it's not like...
So...
It's a closest we get to sort of kind of...
Sort of just sort of going forward in one piece.
And they'll play music or something.
And my temptation is always just to try to make the cutalafs.
So sometimes, I'll do things like when there's a moment where I'm meant to, you know,
orgasm, I'll be like,
Doy-dy-dy-dy-dy!
People do that.
Wait.
I'll tell you what.
If they don't, they should.
It's not a Ryanair flight when a Ryanair flight lands.
IsAlexa-idle-do-do-do-do-do?
I don't know.
Oh, well.
Cool.
Well, I thought.
I still say it backwards.
Did we got a prejudice? Yes.
You want to hear it? If you can.
If I can. What do you mean if I can?
Tens of married hoppins, skippon.
Oh, Doshas Ali, ex-veer stick, fragile Kelly Rupus.
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
You know, I agree.
I agree.
LAUGHTER
Just doing that. What's that?
I've never... I'm pretty thick, but I've never understood
the thing that Morgan Freeman said to you that...
Oh, so when I was...
This was about 10 years ago.
I did a film with Morgan Freeman.
It was a really small film.
And the first 10 pages or 10 minutes of the film
are us two just driving together in a car and talking.
And it took three days to shoot.
And he didn't talk to me the entire time.
Like, in between takes, right?
Because he had so much dialogue I learned later, right?
Okay. So he was just...
You know, so in between we wouldn't really chat.
But we were in the car together for three days.
And then, at the end of the third day,
he just turns to me and he goes,
Jonah, Jonah, Bobona, Bonana, Fena, Fafona,
Mima, Momona, Jonah.
LAUGHTER
That's it.
And then it was like super uncomfortable.
I didn't know what to say.
It was one of more weird moments of my life.
And I just didn't know what to say.
So I just said, thank you.
LAUGHTER
And then he said, it was quiet again, and he said, do me.
And what? It was like, do my name.
And I was like, do your name?
And he's like, yeah, do my name.
And I was like, Morgan Morgan, Boborgan,
and Boborgan.
Me, Mima, Morgan.
Morgan.
He went, all right.
And then we never spoke again.
LAUGHTER
The only thing that links our got just everyone started very young.
Now, the last time we were here, we enjoyed very much
your early work on the voyage of the Mimi.
Yes.
We're not going to show any more.
Thank you.
Do the blitz, because it is worth seeing.
LAUGHTER
Look at that slide.
No, what's he got?
What's he got, could he?
That is very good listening bass.
Very good interested listening bass.
Yeah.
Tell me more.
That is.
LAUGHTER
No, seriously, you really need to Google it.
And seeing it, you started, was it modeling you started?
You were quite young when you started modeling.
I was a sure, and so, like, no, I mean, yes, but not like proper.
No, not like that, either.
No, I just see.
What in proper modeling?
Yeah, just draw a veil.
I did a bit, yeah.
And then Emma, you did some extraordinary work as a child actor.
I mean, take this, Merrill Streep.
Oh, look at that.
What is that?
It's a prosthetic.
No.
That's amazing.
That's a prosthetic.
I did a kind of Egor G. Robinson thing where I was like,
oh, where?
It kind of was Merrill, jeez.
It's genius.
But tonight, with La La Land in mind, we are going to focus on the early dancing career
of Mr. Ryan Costing.
Oh, well.
Oh, yeah.
Let me see.
It makes sense.
We've got only video you have tonight is.
Yeah, there's this.
So the dance troupe you were in, can you tell us about it?
Apparently, young dancers, they could be quite vicious.
It's a cutthroat business.
I had to get out.
I was on some kind of Canadian star search, and I somehow made it to the finals.
And my main competition were these two twins who were tap dancers, and they were dancing
to Phil Collins' two hearts.
Oh.
And they had big heart-shaped bows, and they were the ones to beat.
So I remember wishing them luck and going on stage, and I was getting ready to start.
I was dancing to everybody dance now by CNC Music Factor, of course.
And I'm getting ready to start, which is this is how you started.
A winning dance number, if you want to know.
You're getting out of your hands, but you know how I go up.
And I look up into the just off stage, and the two twins are standing there.
They're like the twins from the shiny.
And they're just going like this.
And I was like, I was like, all right.
This means more.
Why?
I just shimmyed my way all the way to that trophy, to that tiny little trophy.
Is this the same thing?
I was going to say it's an all-girl troop, but obviously it's not.
You're in it.
But you are the only boy in it.
Yeah, that was the...
That was the point.
That was the gimmick.
They let me dance there for free because I was a guy.
Because if you had a guy, you would win.
Oh, OK.
So are you ready to see the dance styles?
I believe you're dancing to Kathy Dennis' classic Touch Me.
Did the troop have a name, Ryan?
It was Elite Dance Studio.
And how old are you in this one?
Old enough to know better.
In joy.
I wish I could say someone said, here, you have to wear this.
That was my idea.
I thought, I have a vision for this number.
That's the typical and silver hammer pants.
The silver hammer pants are...
I don't think we know, Joe.
We gave them enough of a shot.
We gave up with Hammer, but I think we should have kept them going.
We didn't give them...no.