The expectation, the hopes for this will be how
really Scott's involved, Harrison, you were involved.
But presumably, this isn't the first time I just involved him.
You're in it! You're in it!
You're on the poster!
APPLAUSE
But, okay, my question is this.
So it must have been mentions of a sequel between...
It was 1982, wasn't it? When it came out.
So between then and now, so why now, why not before?
I guess because Ryan wasn't available.
LAUGHTER
For many years, he wasn't available.
Yes, well, not for 30 years.
But they were waiting for me to grow up.
But they decided they have to go ahead anyway.
No, they finally came up with a good story.
I read it and I thought it was awesome.
I thought it was great.
And as I read it, I read about the character that...
Ryan?
It's Ryan.
LAUGHTER
I came to play and I said...
And with great enthusiasm, I called up the producers and I said,
this is great. I can't wait to give up.
And a great part.
Why don't we see if we can get...
Ryan.
Ryan and Gosling.
And they said...
Oh.
I don't know how to rosy.
Rosy.
Yes.
Ryan got that on tape.
And I said, why not?
This is a great part for Ryan Gosling.
LAUGHTER
And they said we've been talking to him for months.
Now wait a second.
They'd only been talking to me for weeks.
So, at last I'm sure you're all too.
It was promoting a film.
She didn't know who she was playing in the film.
It was finished. It was in the cinema.
It was a long time after we'd filmed it.
You might have checked before you came on a chat show.
I really love her. I know she is.
I have no idea.
I don't know why this...
They also...
...contractually know a fence, but it was sort of asked to come.
No, I thought...
But I love you too.
No, no, no.
Wow.
She doesn't mean that.
I don't know.
You see why...
She doesn't want to be here, Liam.
No, no, no, no, no.
I love Graham.
But I do wonder why they asked me to do it.
I don't help. Do I?
No.
No!
I... I... I...
I... I...
I...
So, who did you meet at the Golden Globes?
Ah...
How long you got, man? It's just like...
Oh, so...
Did you meet these guys at the Golden Globes?
No.
I met...
I met her before.
It was a woman's governor's...
She was really cool when we just spoke about stuff.
It was really nice.
And then her...
I met... I met...
I met her...
Good story.
It was really nice.
It was really nice for us to meet.
It was cool.
It was really nice.
I kind of believe he was English,
because his accent was so flawless and get out.
And I was like, oh my god.
And anytime I meet anyone who's English,
I'm just immediately like, I love London.
I miss it.
Do you live there?
Ah, I do.
So you talk about London?
Yeah, yeah.
Which I was like, yeah, I'm...
And then I met...
I met...
What happened, yeah?
I met Denzel.
Ooh.
I met Denzel...
I met Denzel in Oprah at the same time.
It was...
It was this segue.
It was just like...
I don't know.
Like, African-American excellence segue.
I don't know what happened.
I'd say, Denzel came up to me.
I was like, oh, he came to me, English accent.
He was like, yeah, mate.
Cheers, mate. Cheers, mate. Cheers, mate.
And I'm like, what...
What's happening?
How do you know who I am?
And he was like...
And then he went to his wife like,
he thinks I don't know who he is.
And then he goes, come meet Oprah.
And then I was like, oh, come meet Oprah.
Let's meet Oprah.
And then I just...
Yeah, I'm a hugger.
A hugger is so tightly in there.
She felt so good, man.
She felt good.
Apparently she smells weird.
She has an amazing smell.
She smells amazing, Graham.
I swear.
Oprah is just premium.
Can the risk of the crash?
Have you got some more, Oprah?
I thought she smelled amazing.
I've never met Oprah.
But when I do, I'm gonna hug her for sure.
I'm gonna smell her.
At the Golden Globes, but she was too far away.
You go out in hell deeply.
I'm telling you we're walking.
We're walking out in hell deeply.
I'm just sniffing there.
No, I know why.
That was suddenly such a nice smell in the room.
Yeah, sure.
No, she was really cool.
It was really strong.
Now, I hate to pick on Eddie.
Come on.
What?
Eddie, your...
Well, we were just saying, your sexual awakening
was sort of...
Was it two-dimensional sexual awakening?
Oh, God.
No, it's true.
I was once interviewed and I was like,
who would it your first crushes?
And I did...
I loved the Lion King when I was younger
and I had a weird obsession with Nala.
That's for you.
Look at her face. She's so sweet.
That's your thing really well.
That's wrong.
That is so wrong.
Is it true you like made Marion as well?
Yes, that is true. She's a foxter.
What, I have that too.
Well, do you?
Oh, there's...
No, no, no. But in Eddie's...
In Eddie's defense, they draw them really sexy.
What is do you like Robin Hood?
I heard what he's got to say.
The thought Robin Hood, there he is.
And that tunic is worn very low, I notice.
Yeah, you mean he's packing.
My first attempt at Standard Comedy.
And what happened was I...
I'd always wanted to do Standard Comedy.
I didn't have the guts to do it.
I got very drunk. I had a go at doing it as a blue coat.
My mate said to me,
just copy all the other comedians at Pontings
and steal their jokes
and basically talk to the front row.
So you're supposed to say, what are you from?
Scotland, you say, who paid for your holiday?
Where you're from, Wales?
You make an always like a sheep. Rubbish jokes, all right?
But I said, that's terrible.
He said, don't worry, you're just padding.
What you're doing is you're looking for comedy gold,
which is, where you're from, they say Kent.
And you say, what did you call me?
Now at Pontings, this used to take the roof off, right?
So I tried it, but I was very drunk.
So I go on stage,
and I say, where are you from?
I'm from Scotland. I can't remember the joke.
I say, hello.
Then I said to, where are you from?
The guy says, Wales.
I'd black out and I go, hi.
Hi, panic.
And then I say, anyone in from Kent?
And this bloke shout's out me.
And I said, well, you're a f***er.
LAUGHTER
So I miss him.
I'm trying to walk him.
I know people always end these things,
but I swear to God, that's a true story.
That is the baitsome.
It's still in practice.
Hello.
Hello. Hi, yeah.
What's your name?
My name is Eileen.
Eileen.
Yep.
I'm guessing you're from Ireland.
I am from Dairy.
We're from Dairy up to the north of the country.
And you live there or here?
I started here.
I live over there.
Oh, what are you doing?
Clostum design.
Clostum interpretation.
There will be subtitles on Friday.
I don't know.
Right now, only I can understand the meaning of it.
I can't understand that too.
I know.
I can't.
No.
So far you're not missing anything.
I've never heard of costume interpretation before.
It's like costume design, isn't it?
Except fancier.
Fancier, it's fancier, Frank.
Oh, yeah.
All the labour.
LAUGHTER
OK. I'll be going.
Right.
So lead up to Christmas.
I was back home.
And I had a good night.
Exactly.
Right.
Did you get any of it?
Something about Christmas.
Yeah, Christmas.
That's the only good detail so far.
Because you said, just pick out where it's you'll follow the story.
Let's say blah, blah, blah.
Christmas, blah, blah, home.
I went into the shop and I had to get milk and bread.
LAUGHTER
So I literally was really stressed.
So I was like, I want to get the groceries.
Let's go.
Told my boyfriend to do a lap and just pack me up.
No need to park the car.
So as planned, I came out, you know, perfect timing.
Silver people's car are casually drifted by casual speed.
So without hesitation, I sprint across.
When my groceries jump in the back of the car, screaming and thumping the back of the chair,
and go, go, go, go, go.
But taking a mind, it was Christmas, and I had like a scarf up here and a hat.
LAUGHTER
I got, which was my boyfriend, torn going to be this middle age, like, 60-year-old woman.
Scoring men.
Jesus!
I pushed her foot on the accelerator and then I was doing a little post.
Oh!
He's found a selection of poor and sometimes, frankly, essentially, lazy translations into English on foreign menus.
So imagine we're all in a restaurant together and I turned to stand.
I said, what are you going to get?
And Stanley might reply, well, I'm going to get the sausage and the father-in-law.
LAUGHTER
Look at that possibly being!
I don't know, but the images that conjures up...
It must be some sort of told in the whole.
Yes.
It's getting worse.
This, this is it, I mean, really.
I mean, I don't think anybody...
It's a fake relative, isn't it?
Yeah, I do.
And I don't think anyone wants this German-type sexual harassment.
LAUGHTER
Yeah.
But I don't think it can go wrong with a nice place of...
hand-shredded ass meat.
Oh, everyone's favourite towards the more.
Just another handful.
What do we have next?
What's going on with that?
Stanley, you'd know what wine goes with it.
Wine, damn.
I think a wine pairing menu.
Oh, this is a special brunch for the weekend.
I might have the fresh-allowed potlify of a variety of opinions.
I like that.
You can almost imagine that in a menu.
Yeah.
Under a magic costume.
That's like parliament.
I mean, they serve in parliament.
But then sometimes people are just a bit lazy.
So this one, there's bigger menu.
There's some smoke cow feet.
And then they just cow something.
LAUGHTER
I looked it up.
There wasn't there.
Just cow something.
I don't know.
Just...
I knew it.
It's beef in it. Just have it.
But that person took a bit of trouble.
This next person couldn't be bothered at all.
Item number two on the menu.
Whatever.
Food in it.
Food.
Have it.
It's only you did.
Now you meet again.
Forever.
We move on to dessert now, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh.
Let's all have a bowl of...
No, sweet scum.
What's next with scum?
You can get strawberries with scum as well.
And we really want to push the boat out.
Why not have some chocolate puke?
LAUGHTER
Everything...
We would put it in the tank.
I'm looking for a tap.
And finally, is there anyone who live who doesn't like sweet tight push?
Sweet tight pussy.
LAUGHTER
Well, all the band he translated through.
Isn't it true?
And this seems unlikely that you own a single piece of every bit of memorabilia
that they produced for Lord of the Rings.
Oh. Well, that's half true.
So I've got a few things from the actual films.
So I have the ring, I have sting, I have a map from Bilbo's study
or the living room in Bagend.
And I just recently, because I went back and did the final bit on the Hobbit.
And they gave me the book that Bilbo writes in.
He writes the Hobbit there in Mac again, a Hobbit's Tale.
And then I finish it as Lord of the Rings.
They gave me that red volume, which is beautiful.
Yeah.
And with my last day in Hobbitin, it was pretty magical.
Oh, no.
It was amazing.
Hobbitin.
And then...
Oh, come on, you're in the Hobbit City.
This is a set.
It's a real...
It's a real place.
They've actually...
I think no, it's not.
It's a real place.
It's like a real tree.
Don't you screw up your tree.
So they've...
His feet are big too.
They've actually built it.
We built it for Lord of the Rings.
We took all of the facades away.
And then it's since been a tourist attraction.
And now it's been rebuilt for the Hobbit,
but with sustainable materials, with real woods.
So it'll always be there.
So from now on, you'll actually get to see Hobbitin and visit it
as a real place.
And we'll be...
Oh, can you...
Can you stay there?
You can't stay there.
No.
But they are turning the green dragon cub into a visitor center.
Oh, no, be too big for a tree.
You want to help people coming in?
Where's my bedroom?
Please, Vicer.
Here's the jacuzzi.
Let's see how we go.
Let's get it going, my baby.
Wow.
Hobbitin.
So people are going, yes, we're going to Hobbitin for Christmas.
I turned 19 when we first went to Hobbitin.
And I was 30 now.
I was talking to Pete when we were there on my last dance.
And you realized that I had my 19th birthday in Hobbitin.
Yeah.
And wild?
Wild.
So you put some things into perspective.
Yeah.
I mean, people can say that I had my birthday party in Hobbitin.
Hobbitin.
I don't circumcised it Disneyland.
It's even no one could have known.
But it was going to take off and become a real place.
Stop it.
It's like a real place.
It's a tourist industry place.
So that's...
It would look getting into New Zealand, asshole.
I know.
What's your next turn?
A super-dominant.
What was it going to be?
I want a theme.
It's Graham Norden.
Come on, Graham. Good luck on you.
Yeah.
He's a Hobbit denial.
He doesn't believe in Hobbit.