You had the tooth knocked out this time.
Oh, yes.
I had a concussion, whiplash, stitches in my hand,
dislocated shoulder.
Yeah, there's been a lot of breaks and sprains and concussions.
I think the most psychologically damaging
was when I broke my penis a few years ago.
I was trying to backflip a motorcycle
and I can't ride a motorcycle.
And I came off the ramp.
I let go of the bike.
It goes 20 feet in the air.
It comes down and breaks its handlebars off in my crotch.
So, yeah.
You know, straight to the hospital in surgery.
But that was like over three years ago
and I still have to catheter twice a day.
Like a 15 inch tube,
about the size of a number two pencil twice a day.
Wait a second.
A 15 inch tube?
Lucky wife.
No.
That's not true.
I got to be honest.
A two inch tube would probably get the job done.
So, it still isn't healed.
Not completely.
But I have a 10 month old son.
So, it still works.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
Well, listen, I was a...
I was a...
The mashed up penis is a very impressive injury.
About 600 people in our audience tonight.
So, let's see.
Let's see if we can do better than that.
We'll see who's hurt what?
I don't hurt feelings right there.
But...
Have you heard anything? Have you broken anything?
No.
Never.
Horse riding, anything?
No, no, no.
Bungie gone wrong.
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Can't help you, Johnny.
Oh, you broke something.
Maybe I've broken something.
What were you up to?
I broke my nose. I've walked into a tree.
I've broken a hole.
A tree?
I walked into a tree.
I'm sensing drink was involved.
Is it a good thing?
Actually, it was my first week in high school.
I was on school camp.
It was an introduction to our new peers and new life at high school.
I was blindfolded and it was a trust game.
I...
I like the people you went to school with.
That's a really fun again. Trust me.
Boof.
Anyone else that anyone broken anything?
Oh, you...
Yeah, I did.
I had an injury.
I got a rubber stuck on my nose.
LAUGHTER
No, it's...
No, it's not.
LAUGHTER
OK.
And it raised up.
I heard something else.
Yeah.
That would have been a really good injury.
LAUGHTER
The...
How that happened bit of the story would have been...
It was his first time.
Did you do it yourself?
My brother dared me to put a pencil up my nose.
And you know the yellow one to the pink one.
Yes, do you know that?
Yes.
I told me I couldn't take it out because it would have raised my memories.
LAUGHTER
Oh, wow.
How old were you?
Six.
Oh, no permanent damage.
It depends on what you call permanent damage.
Well, I'm proud of all the injured people.
Very good.
Yes, sir.
Is it really one of the things that attracted you to Aussie
was that he doesn't lie?
No, it doesn't.
It can't lie.
And it's like we'd be at business meetings and I would, you know...
Lie.
Well, I just embellish things, make them sound better than they actually are.
And he'd be...
Why are you saying that?
And then I'd be kicking him under the table.
Stop kicking me under the table.
LAUGHTER
And I've got my hair in his foot.
What's the matter with you?
I don't like...
Oh, f...
But you'd like to hear him, haven't you?
Oh, loads, God.
Yes.
Yeah.
What was the thing about you rode a motorbike?
Oh, God. That was when we were first together
and I wanted to be kind of like hip and happening.
And I told him that I had a Harley-Davidson
and like I would ride it on a Sunday down to Malibu, you know?
No, you were good with the dogs and the pelagon, you know?
Oh, shit.
What?
I wonder where the pelagony rejects a couple of months ago.
She got...
I thought she was going to be wrapped around and trade with these dogs,
but she was just trying to carry on
if she'd done it all her life.
I'll translate.
LAUGHTER
Oh, God.
You're out of your face.
What are you talking about?
I do know what you're talking about.
Okay.
Yeah.
Look, you were in a jungle in Junkies with Jack
and you went to Pasagolia.
So you understand me, you know?
Yeah.
What's the matter with you?
Oh.
Thank you, sir, because you have diversified in your life
into all these different areas,
into the film and the business,
and is that because realistically,
it's kind of harder to make money out of music now?
Yeah, that is, but I mean, just my personal interest
in the storytelling process,
and I've been working on it for three minutes long,
so you've been only creating descriptions.
The film projects allowed me to develop cause and effect,
and identify to be able to make it visible
to the person's defects.
And where do you stand on this thing?
Because people talk about how, or TV,
with American Idol and X-Factor,
I've now got a stranglehold on music,
that number one, every week, seems to have something to do.
I mean, because of the viewership,
the viewership is so high, I just did the X-Factor.
I had to go in there with them.
Surely you've done enough.
I was like, no, I'm a performer.
Do it.
Did you get any votes?
I'm not sure if they voted, but they saw me.
Did you meet the X-Factorians?
Yeah. All right.
So, did you see them before?
I did. I did. It was a Marco,
Yovanna, and another girl.
There she goes.
Oh, no, the X-Factor in Italy.
Someone just stole it in my ear.
Yeah. That's what I call Marco and Giovanni, in thing.
Oh, sorry.
It's my...
Did you see how politely though we handled that?
Because we thought you would lost your mind, though.
Yeah.
Oh, that's so good.
Oh, it's cool.
Game between Cuba and Mexico.
Oh, my God.
It's my favorite.
You should have just looked like, don't worry, he's been shot.
Thanks a lot.
I think I might quit, too.
No, I like to make 50s that's arrived in Europe.
I'm in Europe.
I don't want to hear you go Italy.
It's a suburb of love.
Your own Paris.
Yes. No, I do...
How many? How many do you have?
I've got two... two Paris.
And Maluck and Cockatoo and a Triton, Cockatoo.
And then...
You like a Cockatoo, don't you?
Yes.
Even I.
You're saying I'm sorry.
It's even I.
We're walking down the corridor.
And there was a doormark in you window.
Shall I open it?
No, I shall.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I am.
You're just dotting the eyes, you're crossing the teeth.
You're Maluck and...
I can't say the word now.
The Paris.
Yes.
There's a known...
And there were rescue birds that we got from a rescue centre.
We only take on birds that...
For whom they've already had several owners.
And do you exercise your bird?
Yes. We do.
Well, in the wild, Paris, particularly Cockatoo's,
will forage on the forest floor rather than to fly out.
And so they love to run and forage in the ground.
So we would take them to Richmond Park and put them on harnesses.
And just walk them around.
But the dogs don't want to kill your parents.
The sides of their beaks.
Right.
These dogs...
There's some sort of evolutionary sort of light bulb going off somewhere.
And we go, yeah, maybe not.
I've seen the footage of Stephen,
and that bird's going to get on my head and try to get the wax out of my ear
and get off its face.
You've got some top tips in the gym.
Well, I got inspired.
I think most people, you go and waves,
we're like, this is going to be the time where I'm going to get in that crazy shape.
And I went to the gym and I was working out.
And I had chosen a day when all of a sudden, randomly,
Arnold Schwarzenegger walked into the gym that I was doing.
Oh!
Yeah, and he was like, you know, this is when he was the gum.
I knew I was in the right gym, right?
I tried to put some more weights on,
so I would look more impressive.
And he knew the gym owner or something,
and he was taking a tour or something.
And he approached me, and I don't know if he knew me as an actor
or just he was like, you know, he's the governor,
like, hello, citizen.
He said, what are your goals with your workout?
I was so on the spot, but I retreated to this just very little boy place.
And I was like, well, to be honest, Arnold, I...
If I could have anything, I'd really like to have...
Did you ever see the movie Fight Club?
I really liked the way Brad Pitt's abs looked in Fight Club.
And he said, without hesitating, he said, that's all diet.
You have to eat a lot of carrots.
And I didn't know... I was like, okay, of course in my mind.
I'm like, Arnold Schwarzenegger, he was like, Miss Universe.
I'm Mr. Universe, not Miss Universe.
What a career.
I'm not even going to know if he was all so Miss Universe.
There's so many steroids, but I...
So I ran home and I bought a shit ton of carrots.
I was eating them for weeks, but nothing ever happened.
No. Very nice to see you all.
And we're excited to see all three of you.
But I have to know that Cameron, you were very excited to see Sir David.
I am so excited. I am, yes.
I told the prep says you were making Sir David up in Barrel Sandwich.
But he's the meat in the middle of our sandwich right now.
Leave you to it.
Where is slices of bread?
She's not French steak, and I'm an old male ovis also.
You're gonna be too gritty.
Because you wouldn't be as well-dissueologist.
I did want to be a sociologist.
That was what I thought I was going to be my entire life.
I wanted to study the...
That's a teacher, so I've learned a lot from you already.
Things that I picked up on backstage were not going to mention though.
But I ended up studying the behavior of animals.
It just happened to be human animals.
Really?
Yes, you know, as an actor, that's what I do.
I study human behavior.
And lots of discovering.
Yes, lots of discovering.
Big, big.
I like doing so many more surprises when I watch your show.
Yeah.
You should see the outtake.
I would love it.
You want to be a re-can-arrange of you, yes?
I know.