I'm gonna be honest.
I nearly threw up.
LAUGHTER
I'm gonna do it.
Pops, hop, pop!
Ho-ee!
Pop!
Yeah, very good.
It's fair, good, fair to us.
Payton, how about now?
I'm good, how you're?
I am thirsty.
I'm thirsty too, but not as thirsty as you always.
What is that supposed to mean?
I can't find out.
That's trying to hide his erection.
OK, should we...
...do it as his...
Yeah, you...
Yes, sure.
Would you just want to go first?
No.
See you, sirs.
Pay for a rock.
Oh!
You can kick-sad us.
Um...
So, might say, sir, I stole my cow the other day.
And I said it's all good.
It was just a bit of a case of mistaken identity.
He's a good star.
What?
Oh, shit.
Fuck, OK.
Oh no.
OK, well, cheers to my funny joke.
Cheers to you.
Um...
Um, Mexican magician...
...saying he could disappear by counting to three.
Who knows?
Poo!
He disappeared.
He was gone without a trace.
Ch-chase.
I was so mad.
One of those trace.
Who knows?
That is...
That is trace.
Fuck.
Why is he so big Spanish?
I'm not gonna lie.
I was like...
Is this how you pronounce it?
The most fuzzy way to do that is all my life.
Trice.
And a rustic...
Trice?
I can't get out of this.
All right, lunch.
I'll have to eat that ice.
Yeah.
Oh.
What's the matter, Saf? You're allergic to good jokes.
I just rocked up, like, but it's still waking up.
Look at it. It's all cozy there.
Anyway, shh.
OK, my old high school teacher told me I'd be terrible at poetry
due to my dyslexia.
But it's so crazy, because I've already made like two vases,
two jugs and a nash tray.
It took me, it took me a saver down there.
I'm not even saying that he doesn't get it.
But it's back to the bed.
My pottery, right?
Yeah?
Sweet, we did it out, I just wanted to make sure.
But it's...
Thanks, Kat.
It doesn't count.
OK.
I punched one of the seven dwarves.
No, I didn't.
Ah!
I'm scared, I was all right. Hang on, wait, wait.
All right, so I'm in the drug and then we'll drink.
I...
I punched one of the seven dwarves.
Yeah.
It wasn't happy.
Why was it so much funnier when you just said you punched someone?
I don't know, I hit it with the...
You're not touching down.
LAUGHTER
OK.
So why wouldn't they let the dog in the UFC?
Because his bark was worse than his bite.
Everyone's like, I didn't kill it.
I don't think I could...
No, I didn't.
I don't think I could.
OK, so the silence was just...
It's bad.
I was telling you, what's the reason I thought I was in this game
because I don't laugh, Rory.
Hey, Peyton, you heard a hot girl summer?
Have I ever?
We'll get ready for smooth sacs summer, baby.
That's right, you hear it, McLeary's.
It's time to whack those sacs back into shape.
And what a better way to do that than with the men's scape of former's package,
5.0 Ultra.
Inside this package, you'll find the true MVP of the summer,
the Lordmower 5.0 Ultra.
This fifth-generation trimmer comes with two interchangeable skin-safe bleed heads,
making it the ultimate sacwacker,
but without the pain or the pubes.
The package also comes with the weed-wacker 2.0.
Oh my God.
You're going like a two-point-o?
The weed-wacker 2.0, the crop-reviver, and the crop-reserva.
If you soon have been smooth legends, wanted more,
the package also comes with two free gifts,
the Shed 2.0, the perfect place to keep everything in this package secure.
It also comes with the Boxer 2.0,
to keep your package secure.
So if you want a silky smooth sac this summer,
jump on a man's scape.com and use the promo code,
yeah, mad.
You'll get 20% off plus international free shipping plus two free gifts.
What?
That's 20% off plus international free shipping plus two free gifts
when you use the code, yeah, mad, at men'scape.com.
Wow.
How many Mexicans does it take to screw in a light bulb?
Dressed.
Just one.
not just one.
Not just one.
Right.
Fuck.
What does a piece of delivery man in a gynecologist
have in common?
They both can scrape some cheese off the box for a quick snack.
Oh, fuck.
I'm vous.
Fuck.
No, that's.
That's it.
Too early.
I guess Sylweth got it, that's it.
I get so excited, don't you?
Shut the fuck up, bro, are you a day for art?
It's for sure.
I'm not to talk to someone in private, but I'm...
Sorry.
What's one thing women always support?
Going.
A man's right to shut the fuck up.
Oh, you...
Oh, man, hands right to shut the fuck up.
You know something came with a back set.
Something popped up right set, you say?
I don't talk to say that.
Have you seen the movie about a little fish with cancer?
Finding chemo.
I had that so bad!
A little fishy.
Holy hell.
You grew up a shot.
Fish out, friends. Bad dead.
Cheers. Cheers to the fish.
Cheers to the...
Cheers to the little chemo.
How do you make an idiot say how?
How?
Oh, my eyes are like...
My heart's racing.
That's what I feel like.
Hey, hey.
You're a fucking idiot.
That's the opposite.
Point of case.
Fuck.
That was great.
Okay, class members say what?
Okay, sorry.
All right, all right.
I just want to let the record show...
I did not laugh at that one.
No, I thought that was a pretty average.
What did you...
Did you not get it?
That was so great!
Yeah, you held that so well.
I was so surprised.
I was like, Matt will lose his mind.
Well, to be fair, the instant regret was instant.
How about this?
Hey, Peyton.
Hey.
Why aren't blots?
Hey, it's the real blot here.
Come on.
Why aren't blons good cattle herders?
Why?
They can't keep...
Fuck, I'm pissed.
Wait, what's that?
You're too huge.
We're going to take another show of that.
Thanks, Ben.
Hey, Peyton.
Why aren't blons good cattle herders?
Why?
Because they can't even keep two calves together.
I don't get it.
Like the legs?
Two calves.
Not together.
Matt!
I did that.
Continue.
All right.
I hate when people joke about the Holocaust.
And frankly, I won't stand for it.
That's right, I'm not even going to live.
God, he's good.
There was like an inaudible...
Stop, stop.
Okay, thank you.
What the hell?
Have you hit the real mat in the attic?
What do you call...
Sorry.
What do you call Winnie the Pooh's grandmother?
I don't know.
Poonernie.
I was just waiting for one, Benjol.
I was just...
Poonernie.
I have a Winnie the Pooh.
I was just saying this.
I have a Winnie the Pooh little...
Come on!
Oh, shit.
Chess.
It's a very fun part.
Put the bananas to put on this.
And then he's...
Cheers.
How are you?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
And Frank, shut the fuck up.
I feel like...
But she has not got a mouth like...
Who on earth said it again?
Hey, knock knock.
Who's...
Eo.
Eo who?
I'm an Eo your ass to that.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm so sorry about that fucking party.
Holy shit!
I'm sorry, but that was fun.
I'm sorry.
Did you hear about the toy who caught public transport?
No.
It was bus like you.
What type of bus crossed the ocean?
What?
Columbus.
That's... that's it. That's still the bus, boss.
Fuck!
Oh my god, hang on.
We just couple of people having a little bit of fun on the set out.
A little bit of bus fun.
Piggy bus fun.
Cheers.
Go, bus girl.
This bus girl, baby.
Hang bus.
We just wait for the background.
Come, come, did...
What did Helen Kellaget for Christmas?
Nothing. She had everything.
Okay.
Do you know who Helen Kellaget is?
No idea.
Helen Kellaget is deaf, dumb and blind.
Is Kat turning into me? Like, just hang on.
That's my job.
Oh my god, we got more?
Oh my god.
Oh, shit.
Here you keep a blonde busy.
What?
A blonde busy.
Fuck yeah.
I can't even know what it was.
I was like, what the hell is going on?
It's very artistic comedy.
I'll just give it a shot.
You don't know how to play a boy.
It's a story with you, baby.
Are you ready?
It's a punani.
What do you call a bunch of white guys standing in the line?
The new cast of Yamat.
You're all white.
You're all right.
I mean, I've got to go.
I said, I said, I got to go.
Right, that's your first fucking warning.
That's your first warning.
Anyone know that?
You're done.
Right?
I was born in Germany.
I'm sorry.
You're just winning.
Do you know what that is now?
I can't.
I'm okay.
Just...
This is why people hate you back.
So necessary, you've ruined it.
What kind of STDs do fish get?
I don't know.
Clam media.
They also can get...
Hepatitis C...
...and also, murm aids.
Um...
You having fun?
I have having fun.
Fuck you, man.
Fuck you, let's go.
Let's go.
Take two more, that one.
Being more genuine.
That's really...
Okay, so what's white and always outside my window?
Path.
Is that a wrap? Is that a fucking wrap?
Siss it out of your boys and girls, that says, get us a kiss.
One, the hell was smart and straight out of nowhere too.
I didn't realize you could see me.
Sorry.
It's like this beach was over there.
It's on me now, Pat.
Four times.
Four times. We all hear the punchline.
Okay, that was a lot.
It was gonna be Matt.
He couldn't see over the bridge.
Rock him, fucking. See you right now.
Oh, wow.
Look at TV. Do earthquake.
Man, that goes down as my favourite moment on you, Matt.
It felt ever...
It's like, it's snappy, like, good to me to do it.
And then he comes on and gives the worst, best performance ever.
Oh my god.
Anyway, back to the game.
Hey, Payton.
Hey, what?
What was Tigger in...
What was...
I could talk about you saying Tigger.
Yeah.
Let's start that again.
Hey, Payton.
Hey, what?
Why was Tigger in the bathroom for so long?
He was jumping.
He is the only one.
What?
He's jumping.
Tigger like, bang, bang, bang.
Can I get you this fucking taking a poo?
No, don't make them sexual, please.
Sexual poo.
What is this taking a sh**?
What the f**k?
No.
What's that you mean? I'm creating some buskets.
Don't.
Payton is jumping, though.
So that's what we're doing.
We're only one girl and one couple away from a fantasy completed.
Hey, what do you call a man who loves little bicycles?
Teenie tiny?
A petal file.
Think that.
Oh, okay.
Um.
It's such a silly thing.
My boyfriend said fucking joke.
Oh, love, fucking.
You did love.
I did not love.
Bra.
I know.
Do you know what the past is living animal on earth is?
Sorry.
Do you know what the fastest living animal on earth is?
Fast living animal on earth is.
It's an Ethiopian chicken.
Why?
Look, Payton, you had a great run.
I'm sorry.
It's so much rubbish.
How do you motivate a slow female rabbit?
I know.
Energize her batteries.
Is that meant to be funny?
That's terrible, but you face this a lot.
I'm gonna be honest.
I nearly threw up.
Are you okay?
A little splat?
No, I'm sorry.
I'm a little...
Bra.
Okay, what?
Take healers now.
Good for you, man.
Try not to laugh, man.
Try not to laugh.
You're...
No, no, no, no.
I'm sorry.
What is Osama Bin Laden's favourite football team?
Tell me.
The New York Jets.
I'm a fucking idiot.
Man, I just...
Fuck, it's always hit twice, you know what I mean.
Fuck, that's bad.
I know.
It is what it is.
We should have a look at it.
This is so bad.
Hey, welcome.
Go Payton!
You're the show.
I got one more.
What is it, too?
I punch at the wall.
A.