Did you hear about the Asian girl with the last name China?
No, what happened?
It was her maid in name.
Music, good boy, music, good boy.
Ah, the fuck.
Sorry.
Ah, this is a Halloween episode.
What?
This is a Halloween, yeah, man, Halloween episode.
You used to be wearing some coral dress.
You used to dress...
Happy Halloween.
Happy Halloween, everyone.
Yes.
I think you used to dress up.
You two dress like racists?
No, I'm not wearing the white one, too.
What do you work?
Joke cartel.
Joking off horses?
You have four hours, could you clue?
Oh!
All right.
What do you dress up as?
Huh?
I've missed the memory.
I don't know.
I'll have to get dressed up either.
Oh, shhh.
All right, should we do this?
You guys just missed our great riff.
Yeah.
You guys happy?
Can you guys happy?
I couldn't, I couldn't, I couldn't.
I couldn't.
Oh, I'm glad you did that.
Let's do this.
This is a paper rock.
OK.
This is a paper rock?
Yeah.
See this paper rock?
Yes!
What the f-
Cookie, it was a cookie.
No, that was scissors.
All right.
So Halloween theme jokes?
Yeah.
All right, let's go.
Why do witches wear no panties?
Why?
For better grip on the broom.
Tsk!
I don't know how I'm carrying them out.
That's good.
What's a vampire's favorite fruit?
What is it?
A nectarine!
What is a vampire's favorite part of sex?
What?
E-draculating.
That's good.
And what are you going to do to the voice, Elsa?
E-draculating.
That's good to know.
Oh, roll!
You're funny.
E-draculating.
Really good drunken.
Yeah, pretty easy.
Ugh.
What?
How do two mummies...
How do two mummies settle an argument?
How, Ellie?
They have a rap battle.
Why?
No, I'm no.
That's fine.
The Asian voice?
They have a rap battle.
It's going to get so much worse.
How do you mean alcohol, again?
He's been a hard boy since birth!
So, do you think you're different from the old man?
To do the voice!
Oh, boy!
It's going to be a joke.
No, no, no.
No, no.
Let me cook.
All right.
Why did the vampire break up with his girlfriend?
Why?
He tastes like garlic.
Oh, fuck.
It's unofficial.
No.
What do you call an Asian chihuahua?
What?
A kunichiwawa.
Kunichiwawawa.
You laugh!
Oh, god.
Did I?
Is that kane as a laugh?
I hope there's some peanut butter in that.
I'm sweating.
You're going to be sweating on your upper lip.
There's a good boy.
Look it off.
It was like soy sauce.
Should I have one of different costumes?
Maybe I'll lab...
A lab shade and an enjoy...
I'll cost you.
With some spring rolls tied in my hair.
Some sushi?
Yeah, yeah.
All right, get on, go.
Sushi, what on my...
Oh, sorry.
Oh, sorry about that.
It's really hot.
Oh, my god.
That's a killer.
Oh, gr-
Hey, do you try to do that?
Yeah, I can't see.
Growing up as a fat kid was hard.
The only thing more embarrassing than your parents,
dressing you up as a summa wrestler,
is when you can't fit in that costume.
Oh, this is bad.
What kind of dog likes having a bath every day?
Sexy dog.
A shampooodle.
Well, I heard it was poo.
Yeah.
All right.
Did I?
Yeah.
Like, look at the bit that said it.
Give him your bath.
What?
Ready?
Why did the vampire leave his job at the blood bank,
and get a new job at the sperm bank?
Because he was tired of sucking next.
He wanted to suck some fucking shit out.
That was so bad.
I'm going to ride off the shore.
What was that rise?
I'm going to come on.
Yeah, I'm on.
Do you like that?
Yeah.
Do you like it?
Err...
What do Americans and Asians have in common?
Do Americans have a good life?
Yeah.
Do you like it?
Err...
What do Americans and Asians have in common?
What?
They both love hot dogs.
It was a pretty hot dog yourself.
Do you want to eat me?
Yeah, I want to nibble you up.
Eat my ass.
Oh my god.
Put you in a Yulung festival.
Yulung dog festival.
Yeah.
I fucking keep talking to her.
Fuck you.
Oh, jeez.
All right.
Okay, okay.
That nose won't be there.
That's what.
I carved out a pumpkin to look like sats head.
But I wanted to make it really accurate.
It's completely empty inside.
Did you paint it brown?
Yeah.
But I didn't have any brown paint, so I used a piece of shit.
All right, I'm done with the Halloween jokes.
Back to regular racist jokes.
Back to regular...
Yeah, mad racist jokes.
Did you hear about the Asian girl with the last name China?
No, what happened?
It was her maid in name.
No.
The general pant...
Yeah, I'm over with the Halloween stuff as well.
Sorry, I couldn't leave that many.
The general pants near my local Westfield is getting a big upgrade.
It's becoming a sergeant pants.
That's good.
I like that.
It's not a page of jail jokes, but it's...
A general's a higher rank than a sergeant.
Yeah, that's what I was doing.
Or would you know about a government?
You fucking...
You fucking criminal.
What do you...
What do you call it when a criminal stops an Asian from shitting?
What?
Constop Asian.
Is that your ghostwriter?
Yeah, that's really good.
You're the one joking.
I'm throwing a big Halloween party at the Sydney Fish Market.
Or as other people call it,
I'm going to get a new one.
I'm throwing a big Halloween party at the Sydney Fish Market.
Or as other people call it,
Abbie's vagina.
Yeah, what's up, man?
We're saving a lot of money on the cobwebs.
Different Abbie.
No, that one.
An old Asian man ordered 42 coffees
and the waiter said, sir, are you sure?
And he said, yeah, that's what I want.
So the waiter said it?
Yeah, yeah.
The waiter started pouring seven coffees
and the Asian man shouted, stop, stop.
I said, 42 coffees.
What?
Steven, Steven.
Let's just...
When they go low, we go high.
The race stuff.
So this isn't me going high.
The homeless guy on my street
is going as Britney Spears for Halloween.
Or at least I think he's going for Britney Spears.
I just saw him outside a centralink dancing with knives.
We're pretty old!
We're pretty pretty, bitch.
Yeah.
I don't get it.
Exactly.
That's toxic.
Well, I don't get that anyway.
Yeah, don't worry.
Fucking shit.
What do Asian cannibals eat?
Um...
I don't know what I don't know what.
Roll man.
They're grounded.
Can you take of you?
Whatever that is?
Why?
I want to see eyes.
So you can make fun of me for them?
I want to see your eyes, so I can pull them back as well.
And make these jokes a lot better.
Why did the vampire order the extra spicy curry?
Right.
He wanted something with a bit of bite.
Why can't Asian men never masturbate to Asian fun?
Why?
Because everyone looks like their sister.
I know, man.
I thought we were just telling some wholesome Halloween jokes, but...
Like a genre of fishmonger.
Oh my god.
Oh...
I like this one again.
Asian guy is driving his girlfriend to the beach, right?
Yeah.
And she whispers in, is he, let me give you some Edwell you drive.
So...
Where?
Where's the she said, let me give you some Edwell you drive.
So she goes to Um zip his pants and she goes, is it really true what they say about Asian men?
And he goes, unfortunately, yes.
And then he crashes and they both die.
Oh my god.
Do you ride that?
Ah!
I do.
I tried that at the laugh in zero laughs.
I like it.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
I'm technically Asian.
What happens when a gay person gets tired during the Maddie Grah parade?
They have to drink a gay to raid at the gay parade.
You know what?
I like it.
I did ride that.
You look like a Ryan Vincere.
Why do you now Asian kids don't believe in Santa?
Why?
Because they make all the toys.
You need fucking pieces of shit.
You feel good about yourself?
Make the white people laugh?
Yeah, let's make all the white people laugh without racial humour.
I'm so afraid.
Can we rap battle?
Sath is so creepy.
His version of unwinding is uploading revenge porn.
Oh!
Alright, cut that.
Don't ever do that.
Don't ever use that.
The audience was asking for a specific type of humour
and I appealed to them.
I don't want to get into it.
I might want to retract that later.
Alright, why can't Elvis parallel Pock?
Why?
Because he's dead.
That's funny.
That's why.
That's why he's so aggressive at all.
Yeah, cut that out.
Why is my girlfriend like a maths exam?
Why?
Because I'm cheating on her with an Asian.
Well, as punishment,
I have to eat you now.
Because you would dress like a dog.
Oh, no!
Oh, you're a bit of a...
Oh, yeah.
You're a bit...
Eat me.
Eat me a lot.
Eat him.
You're a bit...
Alright, but if I stand on this, will it break?
Yes.
I have one.
What?
That's what I'm saying.
What's he doing with my girlfriend and mouse?
What's he doing?
That's what I'm saying.