Slickdog's a new album, Bush.
And a very sexy bit of PR.
Of course, the mighty Farell, he co-wrote...
Do you write a whole song?
He produced the whole album.
Produced the whole album.
Yes, sir. Wow.
Now, is it true that Farell,
he was the one encouraging you
to be a bit more family-friendly,
a bit more mainstream-wise?
Yeah, yeah, he made me change.
So in words, I had a song called So Many Holes.
He made it So Many Proves.
LAUGHTER
Well, that certainly toned it down.
On prose, just prostitutes.
No, they're professionals.
Oh, I see.
LAUGHTER
Silly me.
The ladies in the video still look quite like hoes.
LAUGHTER
They're professionals.
They're in a video.
And then, Farell, is it true that he...
I mean, I'm sure he enjoyed working with you,
but he did have some difficulties working with you as well.
Yeah, and when we were working on a particular song
called California Roll,
Stevie Wonder, he came up to the studio,
and Farell had called a secondhand contact
from being in the studio with me,
and he kind of froze.
He didn't know how to produce it anymore.
He was stuck. He was like...
Might have to explain what the...
Yes. So Farell was in an environment
created by Snoop.
LAUGHTER
Farell was no longer the same Farell.
It's not gonna be so.
You can't say.
Yes.
He was... He was now someone else.
LAUGHTER
He was not... He was not the greatest producer in the world.
He wasn't the greatest producer in the world.
He was just a guy in the room.
LAUGHTER
So was Stevie Wonder trying to talk to him?
Stevie Wonder was in the mic, both.
And you know, Stevie can't see,
so Stevie was waiting on some direction.
And Farell was giving you no directions
for Stevie was just in there just...
LAUGHTER
Well, Stevie Farell said,
can you sing this part?
And then Farell said,
can you play the harmonica?
So I had to basically take over,
because Farell was stuck off a space cookie.
He was in another place.
LAUGHTER
I was Farell happy with his work on that track.
He was happy a couple of days after.
LAUGHTER
And then you did go to one of those clubs.
You went to the ping pong clubs.
We did, yes.
We did in our spare time.
But we also shot stills there.
And I had a very unfortunate experience
with the ping pong ball.
What happened?
I was trying to be, you know, a show boat.
Mm-hmm.
And I opened up my mouth to pretend to catch the ball.
LAUGHTER
And she called my bluff.
It was amazing.
I'm totally confused.
LAUGHTER
OK, so you thought the MTV story...
...was on the screen.
Yeah, off you go, Bradley.
You tell us what the nice lady did.
LAUGHTER
So you could pay to watch women eject various objects
out of their vaginal cavity.
Is that probably...
She played a nurse on the arching house with your truck.
That was technical, yeah.
So, like, darts, sex, darts, ping pong balls, sort of kites.
And stuff.
OK, the ribbons to kites.
Kites?
Yes, like, ribbons, ribbons in the end of kites.
If the kites had flown out of there, we'd have...
LAUGHTER
So in the precision with which you could do it is incredible.
This one, very talented young woman.
And, um...
And so we were all sitting there in the monkey,
chow, myself, and stew.
And I was like...
I mean, it was a really good one, Todd.
Get this one.
Wouldn't it be funny?
Yeah, it's just like...
BOOM!
LAUGHTER
That's your...
It's...
It's crazy.
And I was zik-a-git.
LAUGHTER
That's weird.
And, Jenny, you generous creature.
I know you're very busy, but you've already made us a lovely gift.
I did a cake.
And I've got the cake here, before you're just saying it.
This is the cake you made.
I don't know how long you spent making it.
There it is.
LAUGHTER
I've got a cat.
Now, I don't even ruin night jello, but it looks like shit.
Taste it. It's delicious.
Come on first.
I'm sad on it.
Well, you're going straight for the shit.
I'm for it.
Who does it?
I thought I might try that...
Do not cast the first stone straight for the shit.
Look at that.
Ooh.
That doesn't work.
LAUGHTER
What a cruel joke we've played on you.
Thank you.
Self-dried.
I could eat on, but I'll save some room for leisure.
That's right.
Now, that'd be nice if you'd visit us round for Christmas.
Of course.
Christmas is coming.
It certainly is.
Are you looking forward to Christmas?
Always.
Really? Are you really into Christmas?
No, I really am into Christmas.
Mm.
Are you into Christmas?
I love it.
LAUGHTER
Seriously, are you?
Yeah.
Last year, Christmas, I spent alone.
Oh.
LAUGHTER
Come to mind.
Oh, but not jealous.
No, but as a child, you find Christmas quite traumatising.
Did I?
Yes.
Who does?
Won't you win an activity play?
That was Christian school.
On Christmas, I would steal the baby Jesus'
and the black wise man.
I tried to create some sort of coup in South Florida
where they would start a ruckus
where, and I wrote a letter,
the white man is falsely plasticised,
the white Christmas, and I went on and on,
and then I replaced the baby Jesus with a ham.
LAUGHTER
He thought I was arguing with that.
No.
I'm sorry.
Not because I'm knitted in a teen.
There's like...
Nice.
LAUGHTER
And what are you doing for Christmas this year?
Um, not going to my girlfriend's house.
Yeah, because you've quite a young girlfriend now, haven't you?
Yes, you do too.
Girlfriend? Unlikely.
LAUGHTER
Well, here in Britain, many people will be getting...
I noticed there's an open space in the back of your seat.
Wait.
Yes, the rain.
Oh, it's...
Yeah, at any moment, Christmas could come.
LAUGHTER
The world living in the world of glamour.
You know, it's next in the city, New York, to...
David doesn't.
LAUGHTER
Back to where you were in Buzar.
I mean, maybe on paper, it sounds worse than it is.
But is it true you still live in an ex-council flat?
Uh, yes. Yeah.
Well, you must be making quite a lot of money,
Gordon has made the houses nice and cheap.
Well, yes, and that's...
Well, that's neat. I live in a flat I bought six or seven years ago,
is fine, but, except, it's much more unpleasant than it was when I moved in, obviously,
because I've been living there.
LAUGHTER
But I sort of...
The prospect of...
The last time I moved was, I think, the most stressful day of my life ever.
And the prospect of moving in is terrifying.
Now, houses are getting cheaper and cheaper.
I've got another excuse not to move.
And I actually... I hate the fact that I have to take pride in where I live.
I... I... I hate... It's all on the television the whole time.
Everyone's like, oh, I... You know, I couldn't stand this living room.
I'd have to change that. I'd have to change...
Why do you have to change all these things?
All you need is a roof heating, a TV and a fridge.
And you're sorting.
Now, what sort of shit old do you live in?
LAUGHTER
It's not that... It's, you know, it's perfectly functioning.
Is it so-or else on the floor?
No, there's carpet on the floor. It's fine.
But the thing is that you... Everyone's got to get such a massive shit
about their domicile.
Why?
Because it's a nice thing to surround yourself.
But if that's your hobby, fine.
But why is there so much pressure on me to be bothered to move and tidy up
and paint the place and worry about that bit over the cooker that's melting?
APPLAUSE
You see, there's a lot of other sluviny people out there.
When we get round to it, we will speak.
You've got to give in the celebrity version about cleaners your house.
I keep an agi, I've got to come round. We've just got to go, oh my god.
Why wouldn't let the...
I mean, why would I permit that? Why doesn't anyone permit that?
I mean, why does anyone quit that?
Apart from they do clean your house.
You're curious. I've never felt my house is so dirty
that I wouldn't mind public humiliations.
I mean, just either do it yourself or pay someone.
You say, no, I want it for free and I don't mind the whole country thinking I'm a slug.
I'm going to leave you to do a cartwheel, I reckon.
Yeah, I'll leave you to it.
It's no good, sheerie.
How could I put on six plus seven home?
I'm going to do it with it. You're all in proportion.
You're not all in proportion.
That's why you should know about me.
I bet you could do it one after a few times.
Definitely.
Don't keep it in your mind.
You're staying in Richard Graham, not on what life is.
You said, no, I can't wheel. Why are you doing cartwheel?
I think the ladies' den have been like...
Oh, my god.
You've done a lot of work.
Why are you pushing your car wheel?
I've done a lot of work. I've done a lot of work.
I've done a lot of work.
Why would I do a cartwheel to pick up a gun?
I'd just pick up a gun. I wouldn't...
No. No, no, no.
No, you wouldn't.
Because they're firing at you, right?
And you can't run.
Because they're shooting head height. You go, oh, I know.
I'll do a cartwheel that I'm shooting my legs less important than the head.
Right?
I'm picking the gun up.
Crumble, because they've shot my legs.
And then you shoot them.
Problems straight away.
Go on, I'm mid-cartwheel. They're shooting at me.
Glasses come on.
I'm a car.
Now I'm shooting at you.
I have a problem without equal answers on.
I can't. I don't know what had to do with a car wheel.
I'll give a thousand pounds to charity if you do a car wheel.
The guys have got to be the charity.
He could point his neck.
He could take the numbers.
He could point the check.
I don't think I can get up in the air.
Just go through your head.
They're going to see so much junction tomorrow if you do that cartwheel.
I died.
This is a shot shot.
Oh, I'm mad at that.
I'm mad at that.
Why do you need air?
Because they really, they like the medallady and wheel.
Oh.
This is going to be brilliant.
I should have ironed more than the front of my shirt.
Oh, I'm sweating.
I don't know how to do a car wheel.
You're probably safer to do it behind the sofa.
No, no, no, no.
We're like, yes.
We're having the sofa.
Oh, here we go.
Oh.
How do you do a cartwheel?
Do you know how to do a car wheel?
So just pick your arms out for her.
I think that just makes her careful.
Just, just, just, just do that.
You get the arms out.
Just do that.
No, it's a cartwheel. It's straight ahead.
No, no, no, no. It's sideways, isn't it?
Sideway?
You've one hand.
King of Jim.
Yeah.
How am I going to get my legs up in that far?
You kick a middle heart.
I don't know how to hit something.
It's a meant to be bent.
Yeah.
Why did you put a banana on the floor?
Well, I thought it was just picking up a gun.
I wouldn't run before you could walk.
You need a bit of momentum.
So you go back there, right?
And then look, so look, so you're going to run up here, right?
You're going to put your hand there.
And your legs are going to go up.
It's going to be amazing.
They're going to go, we're going to slow it down.
I think it's possible.
You've made me believe.
It is possible.
Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
Okay.
So, one more.
This one.
Oh, excuse me.
Is it that hand on the ground?
That hand on the ground?
Yes, that first.
That hand on the ground.
I'm going to kick that leg for all your work.
Yes, for all your work.
Okay.
Oh.
You can.
Okay.
That was good.
That was excellent.
I know.
You and Matt Damon, very excited to see you.
Lucky me.
Yes.
It's the two of you.
He plays a congressman.
And I play a contemporary bellad answer.
I know.
You and Matt Damon, very excited to see you.
Lucky me.
Yes.
It's the two of you.
He plays a...
He plays a congressman.
And I play a contemporary bellad answer.
Do you?
Yes.
It's Matt's made in heaven.
Yeah.
You were doing lots of exterior filming.
Oh, yeah.
Which is actually a problem when you're shooting with someone like him
because he's vastly famous and wherever he goes, people are like,
like, they're brain smelt.
You know, when you look at someone's face and you realize their brains just melted.
And we were having to do...
We had this awful day.
We were having to shoot a very emotional scene.
Lots of crying and, you know, begging with each other where we're outside
at a very public place.
And there are about 350 people crowded around watching us do this emotional scene.
That's mortifying.
Oh, it's really, really hard.
So Matt was just managing to squeeze a tear out when someone from the crowd went,
Matt, look to me, he's not loving it.
This is the worst day of my life.
This is it.