What do Lord the Rings?
What does Lord the Rings and broke back mountain haven't common?
What?
Someone's ring got destroyed
Hello
Good afternoon good morning good morning good afternoon good morning Matthew. How are you good morning?
Yes, I am very good. I'm so excited. Yeah, I'm very good. I'm very very good. I'm excited. I'm nervous. I'm horny
Well, I am now
And you take me higher
Yeah, you're right. I'm gonna still doing that. I always see his paper rocking. Yeah
Sizzes paper rock
You're going first you can get first you can you can you can oh no I just see the yeah
Walk into that one more part of a vegetable can't you eat?
The breathing tubes
That's a good stuff
That's a heavy star is a big star
Oh my god, I think I was a gig. I'm gonna be honest
Yeah, just give me a second here on the cell will push
What do you call a woman who sets fire to all her bills?
What Bernadette
You're
I got a cute little joke about
Does that
I'm gonna feel
Cheers, God bless you
That's the second one after no no no no
Okay, oh my god. That's the spasit what do a random hero from the street who saves a family from a burning building and I
Have in common
Should I do it?
What the what does a random hero from the street who saves a family from a burning building and I have in common what
We both don't care for using protection
Matt didn't get it
That's too many words
There's a fire
Here we go
Damn it all right
It's gonna be a very good day today
How many people died on the Titanic
A by-law
That was really good. Thank you. That was really good. Mm-hmm. That was really good
What did you back a say to Princess Leia when they had sex?
Happy days cheers
Know what the movie is the Titanic and I see dead people having common what I see dead people
That was an assist
Why was this time there's a lot of Titanic stuff and I like it man just it yeah
Do I look good? Yeah, yeah, I lost about four kilos recently. Mm. I got circumcised
Fucking Jesus
Anything I made these shoes
The new balance for skins
That's crack up why are women so bad at parking? Why because they have been lied to about how big eight inches is all the time
Tell that
There's no how much four kilos you saw
Can elephant
Oh
Okay
How many sets of your
Send it down. Send it down. Thank you very much. I'm trying to try buddy. We're trying to work over here
Must be big. I've got it. I've got to do the job
Full skin survey gets a five skin
Maths jokes too early
All right, okay
Here we go. Ready. Mm-hmm talking about circumcision. How do you circumcise a burden?
Kick his sister in the jump fucking hell yeah, yeah, I think we're not new to this
Wow, can I get it? Let me do it. I got it
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. What's the number one bird? What's the number one bird that you'll find on Epstein's island?
This is number one bird is a number one bird the number what's the number one kind of bird you'll see on Epstein's island a
Cockwood's a
Indian minor
Oh my god
Lord's the apple's on ya
That's the second time someone said that to me this morning
What did they call the German dictator when he swam a dolphin?
Yeah, that's good dammit. It's so hot and trying so hard that's a lot to
Yeah, hit it with the accent I need more shots
Yeah
Okay, you go all right, so it's yeah, let's put it's nice. It's nice. It's nice. It's like
Oh glad okay, how many potatoes would it take to ruin island?
Apparently not
Yeah, that's good. That's good. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you very much
You know that as a four-year-old a certain German dictator
Was saved from drowning by a local priest
Goes to show that a lot of problems would have been solved if priests could just keep the hands of kids
No, that was good. That was good. Well done
Do I not use in the name because the tic-toc won't be like all the YouTube's or whatever the social muffins
We're using we aren't gonna be like who's down Hitler's
Well, I guess like an user from here on in really love saying that
All right, well, I'll bring this one out with the Hitler names on it now
Here we go
He'll symbol is not that thing
That's a little bit simple. Oh, okay, you're gonna I think is it trouble? Yes
What do you call saff on Bondi Beach?
Oh
Please engine back
We'll do it again do it again. Okay. What do you call what do you call saff on Bondi Beach?
Next week on Bondi rescue
Oh
Tae Chicken
Modes
I known I
I don't know.
A priest.
Sounds just waiting for the priest.
I don't know, man. Shut up.
What's Hitler's favorite part of fixing a Russian computer?
What? Uninstalled?
Uninstalled? Uninstalled?
Fuckin'-
No!
Yes, dude, that's gonna give me back on top.
I'm sure I'm winning now.
Well, where do we onto? 20. Let's go.
Four more.
You know Wales.
Yes.
Good.
Have this second largest penis in the ocean?
Yeah?
When I'm swimming.
That's so fun.
Even after the circus.
That's right, it's only...
Well, you know shut up.
You're like...
You're like an idiot.
I'm just looking at...oh man, it was such a good time.
Through it!
Yeah!
Come on!
They already did.
Yeah!
Oh, no!
Fuckin' buzzard.
Oh, this is good shit!
Oh, that one tastes like medicine.
A dazs.
That's the one with kitty.
Okay.
What was Hitler's favorite sex position?
69!
Hit that hot.
Do you imagine Hitler doing sex?
That was really good.
You're like...
He's got a lot of bad stuff.
That's the sex thing.
Really grueling disrespect.
You know what?
You know I was standing on the comedian, right?
Dolphin.
Don't do a snake attack on me.
Because that was funny.
I didn't say it coming.
Okay.
There were just one comedian show I couldn't get through.
Bill Cosby, I kept falling asleep.
Good.
I'm gonna do one with you.
I'm upset.
I thought I had that.
Yeah, that's 1212.
He nimble.
I mean I'm funny.
He does it to his very boring.
He's particular.
He was sitting on...
That's Bill Cosby.
Bill Cosby.
That's Bill.
Who's he?
He's a girl.
In general, he should be actually...
Oh.
Welcome to the party, baby.
Then why didn't you get me in this area?
This is so much fun, dude.
What the fuck?
We miss one.
No, that was the best one.
He was the same.
Two years of gush.
Oh.
That's the idea.
Where is the six-wet up?
Stop there.
It gets real dark after that.
That is...
That's sad.
That's the winner, everyone.
Um...
Hey, what's German?
What's German tea?
I'm just fucking saying it, right?
Oh, he was...
Four-digit pin number.
Nine-nine.
It was seven-three-two.
Yeah, yeah, he fucked up.
He never got into his accounts because it didn't exist.
Oh, blah.
Yes, he was nine-nine-nine.
Not the fuck.
Nine-nine-nine.
I win 13.
Okay, but they're here.
No, no, no.
I go one-the-one.
I can't fucking prepare.
Okay, okay.
I'm gonna keep it, man.
You just did one.
Huh!
Uh...
What's something...
Something that would take a 24-year-old around the world
but do absolutely nothing for a 25-year-old.
What is something that would take a 24-year-old around the world?
Yes, but do absolutely nothing for a 25-year-old.
Wow.
He's birthday.
Leonardo DiCaprio.
Yeah, that's funny.
Yeah.
He like him, young.
What do Lord of the Rings?
What does Lord of the Rings and broke back mountain haven't common?
What?
Someone's ring got destroyed.
Hey, hey, why did Bilbo have a boat or any sphere?
He has old hobbits die hard.
Thank you.
Let's get deep.
Congratulations.
Yeah!
We're the Aswan Opa!
What do you mean?
That doesn't happen.
I got two from two.
You sat on there.
Every teeny-luck, what happened at the end of this?
Come here in the section.
Cheers. Great game, man.
I can love this place.
That's good fun.
All right.
Thank you so much.
I'm going to go lie down for a little bit.
No, I'm not.
Let's keep going, baby. This show ain't stopping.
So lunch now?