What do you call an Asian Dwayne Johnson?
What?
The walk.
Hey.
Hi, killer.
Oh, fuck.
What's this?
Food.
Oh, my God.
Great.
Another girl rejecting me, great.
Hey, you lost your chance of being my soulmate.
Well?
Is this you morning?
Well, it was another soulmate as well, but we don't have to talk about it.
How have you been?
You've been good?
I'm great.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
No, it's now.
All right.
This is paper rock.
Yes, it's paper rock.
Oh, my God, we're so in secret.
No, we're not.
This is paper rock.
Yeah, you can go first.
I don't kill this VL for the same wrong.
She's got stone.
They say an apple a day keeps the doctor away.
Not the doctor that was fucking my girlfriend.
I don't think it was a real doctor, I think.
Oh, what do you...
Fuck me.
I can't eat apples anymore.
Sorry.
What do you call a woman who loves small dicks?
Sam?
Please be Sam.
Oh, that's me.
Yeah.
What's the answer, Sam?
Hope for your girlfriend.
My girlfriend.
Yeah, I know.
That's what I don't know.
I was just...
Oh, fuck.
Oh, okay.
Hello.
Hi.
You know, boyfriends are like a box of chocolates.
They will kill your dog.
I'm just joking around.
I'm joking.
My girlfriend's dog died, you know, so I got her another one.
She's like, what am I supposed to do with two dead dogs?
I'm just joking around.
Oh, yeah.
I'm joking around.
It's all right.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, take it.
Oh, it remind me of who kicked my dog.
I didn't know.
I didn't know what I wanted to do.
Oh, fuck.
You want to do the accent again?
You want to gas?
Just do the accent.
Bro, what project?
I want to play a good play-due, bro.
No, so say I'm pleased with the spirit.
We edited it out.
No, put it in.
You know what I said?
Is there any...
She's got it.
You're great.
Do I do?
I didn't hear it.
You have my permission.
I have permission from some part of you.
Fucking just over.
Who kicked my dog?
It's not Razor because it's such a bad impression.
It's good.
What?
Sad leader.
You kicked my dog.
It's not a bad impression.
It's not the same joke.
Yeah, it's good.
It's good.
Is my good?
Okay.
What do you call a horny cow?
What?
Beef jerky.
I sucked it back up.
Fuck!
What do you want?
Oh my god.
My, erm...
My girlfriend left me because she caught me in bed with some pasta.
I've been feeling cannelloni.
I mean to some weird stuff, some fetishini.
Yes!
I wrote an anti-capitalist pasta sauce book, The Communist Manipesto.
You're so good.
I've been trying.
I'm killing all of you.
Karen.
I'm just calling you Karen.
I don't want this in the edit.
Oh my god.
Hammy, we've done like three blocks.
It's all one block.
Who, who what?
Mark.
He's definitely not by way.
What do you call an Asian dwayne Johnson?
What?
The walk.
Erm, that's funny.
That's funny.
Yeah.
Keep doing the race, don't.
See what happens.
You got the drink sandwich.
You just did little chicken slap.
Little people.
God, this table is gross.
Is yours full of alcohol?
It's empty.
Would you like some?
I'm okay.
You know what?
I'm glad my girlfriend broke up with me.
Yeah.
My girlfriend, Lorraine.
You know, because I can see this other girl,
her name's Claire Rake.
Fuck.
I mean, you know what?
I'm glad.
You know what?
I'm glad my girlfriend, erm,
Lorraine broke up with me.
Because I can see Claire Lee now.
She's better, you know?
I can see Claire Lee now.
Lorraine is gone.
Oh my god.
I can see you.
He wasn't worth it.
Yeah, drink.
I don't know you do all of you know yet.
Yeah, this is kind of good for him.
Yeah, like what is the best for him?
Well, he's already emo now.
He can bring him down.
It will be deep.
Like the cup.
He was so come back to it.
They say rejection is a hard pill to swallow.
But it's just practice for the 60 pills later.
Oh shit.
Oh my god.
That's the kind of thing.
Don't worry, calm my dance deep rejection.
Rose is a red violet, so blue.
My girlfriend's front door.
I left a poo.
And that's my uncle, our poo.
Dinesh is cousin.
Didn't help with the girlfriend's situation, but.
Sticky situation.
You go for a third shot.
Yeah, I don't laugh.
I don't know why you bought this chocolate.
Oh, sorry.
But, you eat it up.
Cheers.
Here we are.
What's your candle?
It's the lid, Abby.
It's filled in dead jokes.
Why do emo kids?
Why do you eat my poop?
Are you cheating again?
Cheating.
Just like her.
Sorry.
Why do emo kids hate high fives?
Why?
Because they're always left hanging.
What?
What's so dark?
You know, my girlfriend and I, we had something special, you know?
The first time I said I loved her, everything changed.
Her name, her address, the locks on her doors.
A tender.
I love they, them.
Cheers.
Oh my god.
All right, let's fucking see what you come up with.
You fucking dead jokes, bro.
What the fuck?
This is too light-brap for me.
Oh my god.
I'll tell them all these.
You'll be all news.
New brown king on the safe.
Fuck.
Why?
So I'm gonna get this good.
Get me good.
Why don't Indians play soccer?
Why?
Because every time they're out of corner, they open a store.
Oh, it's like a Indians.
That's good stuff.
No.
Just when you're dead, oh.
Oh, my god.
What?
I feel like I'm dead.
I'm so drunk.
Who's that?
We heard about him.
Three of these.
No.
All right.
What is purple and red and goes round and around and around?
Round and all.
No.
My dick.
When I put it in a blender.
I'm going through some of these.
Give me the towel.
Where's that fuck fuck?
This will get him.
Oh, it's good stuff right here.
It needs this one more thing.
A week.
Oh, these are heavy hair, bro.
Who doesn't have hair?
I don't see any food.
Oh.
Don't be like the way that means to jump in.
Yeah.
That is so much fun.
It's all good.
Like this.
Gotta go.
All right.
I don't know anymore.
Oh, my gosh.
I can't believe you're right behind yourself.
I did.
Thank you.
I'm so obvious.
What's the difference between a sweet and an emo?
No.
A sweet is harder to cut.
Think about it.
No, don't laugh.
I have more.
Good.
This.
Oh, no.
This bald.
I'll look shot after.
This.
Take a breath.
All right.
You bet you're a penny guru.
Man.
It's not good.
I'll be honest, it's not good at all.
All right.
I'll give you a blowjob and install all my money.
He said, you've been sucked by.
You've been sucked by.
I was moved.
Criminal.
Oh.
I love this.
You were actually very good.
I feel like you should do the damn.
It's like proper.
That's not smooth, throw a good one.
No, like make one up.
I'll feel a joke.
It's not bad.
I'm angry with the president.
That's supposed to be jokes.
Okay.
What's a condom and a coffin got in common?
What?
They both hold stiffs, but ones coming and ones going.
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
No, no, kill it with this weird look.
Is that supposed to be raisins?
What?
What's a good news then?
It's like well.
I.
I, um.
I bumped into the Channel 9 weatherman the other day.
And he's like, I've got some good news and I've got some bad news.
And I'm like, okay.
What's the bad news?
He's like, well, your girlfriend's having an affair.
Okay.
What's the good news then?
It's like, well, it's clear skies for the rest of the day.
And I'm fucking your girlfriend.
Whoop-de-doo!
Oh!
Oh no!
Where the man is having sex with my girlfriend?
I got that.
I got some legal ones.
I got some good ones.
Oh.
Where is my girlfriend?
I don't know why he put the girls to you.
Yeah.
I got the rules.
He gets coming up to the wrong.
Fuck yeah, I'll get to the wrong.
Oh, you have to send me up to this.
What's the difference between a penis and a bonus?
What?
Your ex-girlfriend would have blown the bonus.
No.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
My granddad always said he was proud of me.
But I couldn't tell if he actually liked me.
Or whether he was because of my humongous
horse cock.
Oh, fuck it.
Oh, shit.
Oh, that's a weird.
Yeah, and that's on the internet now.
Anyone's gonna make fun of me?
Yes.
I need one who's gonna hook.
I'm gonna make more.
Little day.
No, shit.
No.
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I'm sure.
Okay.
That'll help it.
Yeah.
We just ended to Seth.
Oh, yeah.
That was so weird.
It's a good one.
No, no, we need to go one.
I killed the one.
Woo!
Great high five.
You should've.
I killed the one.
Great high five.
You should've.
Oh.
I killed the one.
It's gone.
Oh.
In the bitch.