Here are the makeup sponges you asked for.
Oh thanks, I thought I had more.
Mmm.
Damn, you've got more makeup than I do.
You've got better makeup than I do.
Yeah, I'm borrowing this.
Hey, hey, hey.
This is my Comic Con makeup.
I love you, but there are some things a man doesn't share
with his girlfriend.
That's a wise policy.
I once borrowed my sister's makeup for costume contest,
got terrible case of pink guy.
Yeah, but luckily I was going as a zombie.
I went second place.
I feel like you guys just went to Comic Con.
That was San Diego Comic Con.
This is Baker's Field Comic Con.
Is that better?
It's a lot smaller.
It's more about the comic books,
the way these conventions used to be before they went all Hollywood.
So they answered your question?
No, it's not better.
Well then why are you going?
It's a comic book convention.
Yeah.
It's like pizza or particle accelerators.
And stinky ones still pretty good.
All right, well you guys have fun.
I guess I'll see you Sunday night.
Yeah.
Hang on a second.
Hold this.
What was that for?
To show people when they don't believe me.
I know she loves playing the harp.
So I found this beautiful music box that plays one of her favorite songs.
Now Amy already has a real harp.
And they can play any song.
What are you trying to pull here?
No, I just thought it would.
Next.
Okay.
I know she's a fan of the Cantiburi Tales.
So I found this cool map that illustrates the characters journey through England.
I thought we could put it in a really nice frame.
But she's got Google maps on her phone.
I don't know how to respond to that.
But I hope it's with a third good option because these first two.
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, luckily I saved the best for last.
Since Amy's a neuroscientist, I did some research and found out that Santiago Ramón y Cajal,
the father of modern neuroscience, did lots of hand drawings of brain cells.
And I managed to find this signed print.
Wow.
Oh, this is truly remarkable.
Thank you.
I think I'll keep it for myself.
What about your girlfriend?
This is too late. I called dibs.
Excuse me.
I'm eating a goliwa. It's kind of a first date in a library.
She and I are both a little awkward in social situations.
So it seemed like a good idea.
People say I'm a little awkward too.
Man, join you?
No, you can't join us.
Just go climb back up whatever beanstalk you came down from.
You can do better.
Oh, we're eating here.
We're having a texting date.
I love that.
As you're reading, it will help you remember I have it a door of a laxand.
Anything I can get for you?
It's some apple juice, some gelo.
No, no, thank you.
But I do have a favorite to ask.
Name it.
Well, I'm booked to do a children's party tomorrow.
And frankly, I don't feel up to it.
Oh, you're not.
You look awful.
Thank you.
Anyway, I mean, you know my act better than anybody.
I was hoping that maybe you know, maybe you'd fill in for me.
Are you saying that you want me to be Professor Proton?
Yeah.
Oh, my! What an honor.
Oh, this is like being asked to ascend Mount Olympus and dying with the gods.
Or a Korean family in Elambra.
How proud of you, Amy, your first bikini wax.
Yeah.
So how you doing?
Oh, little sensitive, but not bad.
You always take that long.
No, they don't usually have to go out and get more wax.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, now pull your car into the spot and let's get out of here.
Wait, I'm leaving my car here?
Yes.
And be sure and put on the emergency brake really makes these things tough to budge.
Before I park, come in the back seat.
I want to show you something I had done today.
All right.
Color me intrigued.
What do you think?
I think you're high on paint fumes.
And boy, that's a lot of band-aids.
The first 43 parallel universes I've checked proved to be empty.
I see no reason to suspect Universe No. 44 will be any different.
Oh, my God!
Sleep crowd!
Oh, you're getting my face!
I sheldon.
He's in my spot.
You'd later make a stop being naked in my spot.
How are you doing?
He wasn't using it.
And I needed a nice cool piece of leather to wiggle my naked ass on him.
Get off there.
Give me back my iron man helmet.
Give me back my parking space.
You don't need a parking space. You don't have a car.
But if you don't need an iron man helmet, you're not iron man.
Well, we appear to have reached an impest.
And I have to say, I thought you'd be more upset that your laptop is sitting on my junk.
I didn't pick up on that. That's a nice stunt.
You guys need me to call someone. I'm guessing your mom's.
Thanks, but we've got to cover.
Okay, I just talked to my mom.
She arranged for a scatter rental car.
Great. We can send me a gift to Comic-Con.
Are you kidding me?
You're always been through. I just want to go home.
Don't be like that. Come on. How are you talking to him?
I'm with Leonard. I'm done.
Fine.
And I guess it's two against two. How do we decide?
Actually, it's three against one.
What? Well, what about the mission?
You said we were real life landing party.
Well, we're not.
We're an imaginary landing party.
We have real life garbage thrown at us.
By real life strangers, you think we're idiots.
I'll tell you the truth. I'm sorry. I'm to feel like one.
I want to go home now.
Okay.
Did we at least rent the car from Enterprise?
Get it? Enterprise.
Screw you. That's funny.
Whatever you got me, you can return.
No.
No. After everything you didn't do for me tonight, I want you to have it.
What's this? Read it.
Sheldon Cooper, Caltech University employee information.
At the bottom.
In case of emergency, please contact Amy Farrah Fowler.
And there's my phone number.
This is the most beautiful gift you could have ever given me.
Well, I thought if I have a stroke or a kidney stone,
who would I want to share that with?
And you picked me.
It's like you said, you're my girlfriend.
Oh, Sheldon.
Okay.
Stop ruining Valentine's Day and order my pizza.
I can't believe I ditched work for Disneyland.
What did you tell your boss?
Oh, I was very clever. I did it in stages.
At seven last night, I called about a problem at the lab
and casually mentioned I was going out for seafood.
At 9.30, I called and told him that one of my scallops tasted weird.
At 11.30, I called and said I was throwing up like a fire hose.
At 12.45, I called and made nothing but dry heaving sounds.
And now I'm going to Disneyland.
Penny, what did you say?
I work at the Cheesecake Factory. I said bye.
So what are we going to do first?
I don't know about you guys, but I'm going to make a beeline for the place
that gives you a princess makeover.
Oh, that sounds like fun.
You're kidding, right? We're not just going to get drunk and go on rides.
Come on, do it with us.
All right, whatever. How does it work?
Okay, so you pick your princess, sleeping beauties, no whites, Cinderella.
They give you hair, make up the works.
Guess it would be fun to be Cinderella.
Oh, I want to be Cinderella too.
Yeah. We can't all be Cinderella.
Then how do we decide?
Well, it's simple. This was my idea. I'm driving. I'm Cinderella.
You bitches got a problem with that. We could stop the car right now.
It's really you.
Mr. Jeffers, I am so sorry. We should have told you about the broken elevator.
I agree.
Professor Proton, it's an honor to meet you.
Just call me Arthur.
Leonard.
Did you hear that?
Professor Proton said I should call him Arthur. That means we're friends.
No, a friend would have told me about the elevator.
Look at me.
I can get as close to you as I want without my mom saying it's going to ruin my eyes.
Is he dangerous?
Actually, he's a genius.
I am.
That doesn't answer my question.
Mr. Jeffers, I'm Leonard. This is my girlfriend Penny.
Hi.
Hello.
Well, I hope I haven't kept the kids waiting too long for the show.
Oh, no, there are no kids.
No, the show's for me.
Come on, Aracia.
Arthur.
Is the blonde girl really your girlfriend?
Yes, sir.
You're the genius.
You find yourselves in an overgrown old forest.
Before you is a giant oak tree with a face on it.
That looks a lot like Nicholas Cage.
He says, travel with caution.
These woods are home to the bones of many of all and hero.
I want to see how it's just as good a dungeon master as I am.
As good. You just got pounced in the school yard for eyes.
Come on, guys. Focus.
Oh, my dear Nicholas Cage tree.
We thank you for your warning, but we are brave warriors and nothing short of death will keep us from our goal.
Oh, Lucifer, after all. See ya.
Hey, hey, hey, you can't leave. We just started.
You're right. I should finish the game.
I take my plus one long sword stab myself on the face with it. I'm dead. I've got to date with the girl. Bye!
You'll be fine. Watch.
Suddenly, a spectral shape rises from Kuthrupali's bloody corpse and says, don't worry, buddies.
Ghost Raj will help guide you through the forest.
Well, I'm just a tree, but if I were you, I'd listen to your goves, friend.
Would you like to hear a classic Sheldon Cooper factoid?
What do you think? Great.
I've been doing some reading about vehicular safety.
Did you know that the highest number of drowning accidents happen on or around boats?
Interesting that you would bring that up when I might go work on a boat.
That's the thing about that, Lloyds. They're interesting.
I know what you're doing.
You don't want me going on this research trip because you're afraid to be alone.
Well, I'm not afraid to be alone on land.
I'm the sea. It would be terrifying.
Because of all the drowning.
So, babe.
Now, fine. No more drowning talk. I'll change the subject.
Who do you think would win in a fight?
You or a shark.
Look, I appreciate your signature blend of concern for me and incredible selfishness.
If I get the chance to do this, there's nothing you can say that's going to stop me.
Very well.
Things between you and Penny have never been better.
I hope four months apart doesn't change anything.
I should have opened with that, huh?
I haven't Stephen Hawking played a word.
The guy's a genius. Maybe you weren't challenging enough for him.
Not challenging. I was humiliating the man.
I was thinking of writing a book called The Brief History of the Time I Made Stephen Hawking,
Cry Like A Little Girl.
Here's the problem.
You can't beat Hawking like that. He hates to lose.
Everyone knows the guy's a big baby.
Forget the wheelchair. He should be in a stroller.
Really?
One time when I was working with him, he said that Johnny Depp was in the Matrix.
I told him he was wrong, but he kept insisting.
So I looked it up online and showed him.
Well, the next day, he had a pizza party, and everyone got invited. But me.
Then he was all, you're a rehabilitation.
Instead of got out in law, I was doing the Matrix.
Good Lord.
What have I done?
Good Lord. What have I done?
Terrible.
Alright, hot shot. Let's hear your Indian.
I can't sit on that elephant. My ass is on fire from eating or it is curry.
Okay, yeah, that's pretty good.
Why are these staring?
Who cares? Just soak it in.
Hello boys.
Oh, hey.
Can you please stop staring? They're just girls. It's nothing you haven't seen in movies or in drawings.
Hey Stewart.
What brings you guys here?
We're looking for a recommendation about comic books.
Oh, well, I recommend you don't open a store and sell them.
No, we're just wondering why the guys like this stuff so much, so we thought we'd give it a try.
Oh, okay. What do you think you might be into?
Superhero, fantasy, graphic novels, manga, I swear I will turn a hose on you.
What kind of comics do the guys like?
A little bit of everything. Mostly superhero stuff.
Alright, well who's the best superhero?
I can't ask a question like that in here. You trying to start a rumble?
Bernie, home.
You have fun today?
Yes, and I have a surprise for you.
Please be center, hello, please be center, hello.
Well hello, Prince Charming.
Well lady.
Hey, how was it? What?
I can explain, I played hooky with the girls and we all went to Disneyland and got...
What are you doing? Just ignore it. Go on and listen.
Sheldon, all snow white needs is one little kiss to wake up.
Hergy the first time.
We're all here tonight because we have no one to be with.
But it doesn't make us mutants.
The only mutants here are in these comic books.
You gotta stop defining ourselves worth by whether or not we're in a relationship.
You know I see you in El Corral?
I see you're room full of great people.
Don't I give ourselves a break? We are a community.
And as long as we have each other, we're never truly alone.
That was cool, what you said.
You really think so?
Yeah, I do.
Thank you.
Do you like to get a cup of coffee?
Okay.
Later losers!
Let me say if I have this straight, you two are our physicists.
And you and you want me to do a children's science show.
Yes.
And if there's time, take 12 pictures with us in seasonal clothing.
You know I'm a real scientist.
I have a PhD from Cornell University.
Yeah, it's great.
Did you bring your puppet?
No, no.
I hate that puppet.
Oh.
No, how could anybody hate G-no the neutrino?
It's nice, huh?
I got him for 20 bucks on eBay.
Including his shipping!
I'm awake, right?
This is happening.
Here we are.
Really gonna miss you.
Gonna miss you too.
Penny, we're in the red zone.
The white zone is for loading and unloading.
We're breaking the law.
There's no space in the white zone, so.
Anyway, we can email and I think the phone connections are pretty good.
All right, you have to get out of the car right now. I'm not going to jail for you.
You just relax.
Oh, I see a space in the white zone.
Quick, circle the airport.
Did you bring enough inhalers?
Yeah.
And extra dramelline?
You remember what happened on its small world?
No, I'm covered.
Okay.
Oh dear lord, a police officer is clancing in our direction.
We've been made.
Calm down, I'm getting out.
Something I want to give you.
I'm a winner.
All right, it's just a heart shape lock with a picture of Leonard's face and he got them all on clearance.
Now move, move, move!
I love you.
I love you too.
Don't worry officer, they just love each other.
We're not smuggling drugs.
This cushion experienced a nude revenge wiggle.
A wet, a naked man set on it.
Now here's my concern.
His diet is rich and fatty deli means.
What tests do you have to detect lipid residue?
Lipid, what?
Lipid residue.
An anal autograph.
A colon calling card if you win.
Tuesday okay.
Now don't rush it, we may be dealing with befalma, don't at molecular level.
Let me write you a tip.
Did you never play dungeons and dragons with girls before?
Oh don't worry sweetie, no one has.
What do you say?
I'll leave it up to the dungeon master.
Satanic fungus that looks suspiciously like alpichino.
Rises from the forest floor and says,
You're playing D&D.
This whole apartment.
It's playing D&D.
What are you doing in our dungeon?
You shall die.
Literal goosebumps look.
What do you do?
I draw my broadsword.
I read my quarter staff.
I drink my potion.
I see we attack the big one.
You know what, give me the dice I want to roll.
The dungeon master's festival.
Yeah well I'm supposed to be in Vegas throwing up on a shrimp buffet, I'll give it.
Alright what do I need?
15 or higher.
15 is the point, the point is 15.
Give the little lady some room here it is coming out.
16!
Please tell me we're playing for money.
No even better than money you gained experience points.
More potion please.
Hey you don't need Leonard in his app.
You can make one with me.
With you?
Seriously I have a great idea for what?
Was it better than your idea to move to Los Angeles and become a famous actress?
Okay look when you see some of wearing shoes you like you just snap a picture of them and the app goes on the internet to find out where you can buy them.
That's your app idea.
You don't like it?
I didn't say that but no I don't.
Okay these are hugs.
These are crocs.
These are knock off monologlonex.
Board.
Look you said it yourself we have to create a database before you can write an algorithm thingy.
Algorithm.
You see Penny Allen touring defines an algorithm.
Board.
Okay these are Steve Madden's.
These are Nine West.
These are Target.
Oh but don't they look like Chanel.
These are my-
Oh but it knows.
It's a boxy.
These are such shells.
I'm making the donation to your department regardless of what happens between us.
Really?
Of course there's no quint pro quo here.
You and your colleagues are doing remarkable research and you deserve the money.
Oh.
Then what was last night about?
I took a shot.
So many.
Oh.
You're a very handsome man Leonard.
Thank you.
It was foolish of me to think someone your age might ever be interested in someone like me.
Oh don't say that. You're a very attractive woman.
Oh please.
No it's true.
Well aren't you sweet.
Just for the record?
You'd remember a light with me for the rest of your life.
I'm sure I would.
But why why exactly?
You're a very smart man.
How do you think I laughed is that you're rich husband?
I hadn't really given him much thought.
Well think about it.
You mean...
Yep.
I'm that good.
But what the hell?
You used what I wonder about zombies?
Oh.
What happened to the con get any human flesh to eat?
The con stuffed to death they already dead.
You take this one I spent an hour last night on how do vampires shave when they can't see themselves in the mirror?
Well groomed vampires meet in pairs and shave each other case closed.
Yeah okay so zombies.
I guess it depends on the zombies.
Roger we talking slow zombies fast zombies like in 28 days if those zombies didn't eat they star.
Yeah you're thinking of 28 days later 28 days is where Sandra Bullock goes to rehab and puts the audience into an undead state.
Hey don't back on Sandra Bullock.
You think it makes you look cultured but you just come off as Bitto.
Nice shot.
Thank you.
My father taught me archery as a child.
It's odd how the activity brings back the smell of Kmart bourbon.
Perfect.
I know.
What an elf I would have made.
What do you think you're doing?
Shooting at a target?
With what?
An arrow.
Really?
I didn't see you draw one from your quiver.
I'm not gonna do that, Sheldon.
Get Leonard the people at Nintendo can only go so far in helping us recreate an actual athletic experience.
We have to do our part too.
I was uncalled for but I'll play along.
Ow.
I got something I want to ask Bernadette and I can't think of a better time than when I'm with all my friends.
Oh hold on Howard there's lots of better times.
Leonard please the man is talking let him get it out and let the chips fall where they may.
Thank you.
Bernadette, Marianne, Rust and Kowski.
Oh God what's happening?
I know things haven't been perfect with us and we've had our problems but I just have to tell you from the moment I read.
Let me just stop you right here.
This is it.
Yes.
Yes what?
Yes I will marry you.
You will? You will?
I will.
I love you so much.
I love you too.
Congratulations.
I'm so excited.
Tonight is pizza night.
I'd like to refer that to my attorney.
According to what I see here, those are Frank Coney's pizza night.
Yes and when Frank Coney's went out of business we switched to Graziano's.
It's interesting can you just switch restaurants like that, Priya?
The question Howard, turns out you can't.
According to the document you drew up, Sheldon, the selection of a new takeout restaurant requires public hearings and a 60 day comment period.
Were those criteria met?
No.
Oh God!
This is Greek food Leonard you hate Greek food.
Not as much as you.
No!
Shake it man shake it!
Boy, tell the undying shoulders.
You out to dance?
I'm sorry.
I'm in game.
How about you?
Oh what the hell?
Leonard are you in the shower?
I can't hear you I'm in the shower!
I asked if you were in the shower but that's moved now.
I'm moved rendered unimportant by reason to dance.
I can't hear you I'm in the shower!
I have to skip the chit chat.
Emergency.
What kind of emergency?
Mathematical, 32-ounce banana smoothie, 16-ounce bladder.
You might not want to do that.
Well I sure you I do.
I'm not alone in here.
Go what?
I look sheldon.
What are you doing in there?
We she can't be in here.
We're in here first.
You can't be in here.
According to the roommate agreement paragraph 9 subsection B,
the right bathroom privacy is suspended in the event of force measure.
And believe me, I'm experiencing a very measure force.
Come on you can't wait two minutes.
Leonard let the men be.
Penny.
What?
Move, move, move.
Good news.
I finally have a handle on my idea for three person chess.
That is a good news, bye.
Do you know how I solved the balance center combat area problem?
Five words.
Transitional quadrilateral to triangular testellation.
That's brilliant.
It's what I do.
But wait, there's more.
I also invented two new chess pieces.
The serpent and the old woman.
Okay now I have to ask what do they do?
With the serpent slithers to an opposing player's piece,
that piece is considered poisoned and will die after two more moves.
All right.
But unless it gets to the old woman in time,
in which case she sucks out the poison,
turning her into the grand impress.
A piece combining the power of the night, queen and serpent.
Alligant.
That's because it's simple.
Preage has made a snide comment about your acting career.
What the hell did she say?
She thinks it's cool you're following your dream no matter what.
That bitch!
How do you want to handle it?
Um, okay.
Tell Bernadette to tell Priya that I'm on my way to Prague
to shoot a movie with Angelina Jolie.
Got it.
Is it going to be in 3D?
What? I don't know. It doesn't matter.
I'm going to say 3D.
That'll let her know the studio has faith in it.
You're kidding, 3D?
That's what I hear.
Well, studio must have real faith in it.
Why shouldn't tell me?
Have you been spending time with your ex-girlfriend?
No.
Then why you surprise she didn't tell you?
Well, it's not as much a surprise as you are.
You know, the other thing.
What other thing?
If you...
I don't...
What's the word I'm looking for?
I'm not going to help you. This is hilarious.
Let's see if this drug works.
Forgive me for staring, but you're very beautiful.
Thank you.
That's a great accent. Where are you from?
India.
Oh, cool I've always wanted to go there.
It's a beautiful country. You'd love it.
May I join you?
Uh, okay.
Sure, why not?
My name is Dr. Rajesh Kutrupali and this is my friend, Dr. Sheldon Kupur.
Hi.
Oh, there's no need to interact with me. I'm just here to observe.
What's he observing?
We're scientists. We observe everything.
Here, go buy yourself a scone.
All right.
I'd like to buy a scone.
Oh, I'm sorry we're out. We have muffins.
They sound delicious, but this money is earmarked for scones.
What are you doing?
Well, just getting comfortable.
So, I don't let you live in Los Angeles.
I... they were out of scones.
Oh, Sheldon, I'm talking to someone. You're being rude.
I bet you're an actress.
If not, you should be. You have a very expressive face.
Oh, my God.
Wait, where are you going? We're doing so well.
She never even got to see my penis.
I must say, Penny, this is great fun.
Glad you're enjoying yourself.
Until I met you in Bernadette, my trips to the bathroom have been entirely focused on elimination.
Now they have a delightful social aspect.
You must have been in the bathroom with other women before.
Of course I have, but they were strangers and seemed off put when I engaged in friendly stall to stall chit chat.
Some women don't like to get chummy when their panties are down.
You okay in there, Bestie?
From fine.
The reason I ask is that many people experience bladder shyness.
The inability to pass you.
Yes, and I'm fine. Stop talking to me.
She always does crabby when she urinates.
We really not that close.
Screw it, I'll go later.
And I'll be right by your side.
Do you like her? She's great, huh?
She's a lovely girl. Who does a button?
That's good to hear, because I've got some news.
I hope it's good news, because I've got nothing but disappointment in here.
Bernadette and I are getting married.
Ma.
You too busy bearing down.
Oh my gosh, Ma.
Stand back, I'm gonna break the door down.
Stop it.
It's time for bitch.
Help!
Finally.
Oh what, fresh hell is this?
Wait, you can't leave here, you've been exposed!
No, I haven't.
It's all good.
Mountain elf.
He takes the elf from off the shelf.
How handsome.
How handsome!
Colossal certain.
My god, a colossal serpent right here.
Must you!
Sorry, I'm just trying to cheer my buddy up.
Rotting zombie.
Sheldon's new Facebook photo.
Sandor Wizard of the North?
Ha, I win.
She skipped the part of upping under a two week quarantine
because you were exposed to a deadly disease.
Absolutely.
That's my water.
What?
My water, you're drinking it.
Beer, lord.
Have you been drinking it?
Yes, it's my water.
Well, that's it then.
I'm dead.
Here we go.
What, I'm sorry?
Do I really need to connect the dots for you
with the backwash into this glass?
Is every pathogen that calls your mouth home sweet home?
Not to mention the visitors who arrive on the dancing tongue
of your subtropical girlfriend.
Hey, that's my sister and my gun to you talking about.
Then it may have defiled one, but I won't have you talking smack
about the other.
You guys ready to order?
Yes, I'd like a seven day course of penicillin,
some syrup of Ipacaque to induce vomiting and amint.
I don't understand.
He drank from Leonard's glass.
Words will be carving into my tombstone.
That's actually my napkin.
Oh, this is a nightmare.
Where are you going?
To the bar to sterilize my mouth with alcohol.
Game by, dead man walking.
To friendship.
Would you booze, hound, please stop that inferno, blink back.
And the answer with elephant.
Oh God.
Okay, look, this never happened.
Do you understand me?
Really? Still can't talk to me?
Do you go on many dates?
Oh, yeah, I wouldn't say money.
A few.
What's...
Your characterization of approximately 171 different men is a few.
Where did you get 171 men?
Simple extrapolation.
In the three years that I've known you, you were single for two.
During that time, I saw 17 different suitors.
If we work backwards, correcting for observation bias
and postulate an initial dating age of 15.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I did not start dating at 15.
I'm sorry, 16.
14.
My mistake.
Now, assuming the left side of a bell curve peaking around the present,
that would bring the total up to 193 men.
Plus or minus 8 men.
Remarkable.
Did you have sexual intercourse with all of these men?
No.
Although that number would be fairly easy to calculate,
based on the number of awkward encounters I've had
with strange men leaving her apartment in the morning.
Plus, the number of times she's returned home,
wearing the same clothes she wore the night before.
Okay, Sheldon, I think you've made your point.
So we multiply 193, it minus 21 men before the loss of virginity.
So 172 times 0.18 gives us 30.96 sexual partners.
Let's round that up to 31.
Okay, Sheldon, you are so wrong.
That is not even close to the real number.
I'm gonna need a drink over here.
What about your predominant?
Don't have one.
You have telematics in your shoes connected to an iPod?
No.
What do you do?
You just go out there and gamble about like a bunny?
No, I just run till I'm hungry and then I stop for a bare clock.
Why are you doing that?
It's good to stretch your muscles before you run.
All right.
All right, let's start with a toe touch.
Okay, you do it.
I am doing it.
Oh, wow, good job.
Okay, um, can you do this?
We'll never know.
Okay, let's just warm up on the run.
Okay, let's go.
Yeah, I've been reading up on biomechanics.
I think you'll be surprised.
Am I?
Oh!
Oh my god, are you okay?
I think so.
Hey, where may help you up?
Thank you.
Oh, Sheldon!
If it makes you feel any better, Thursday is no longer cruciferous vegetable life.
Together in this car with my enhanced capabilities, we're like Knight Rider.
Except a Knight Rider, the car isn't a Yammering Sphinxer.
You mock the Sphinxer, but the Sphinxer is a class of muscle without which human beings couldn't survive.
There are over 50 different Sphinxers in the human body.
How many can you name?
I was wrong.
This is exactly like Knight Rider.
Perhaps you'd be interested in a different game.
No, this is a photograph of the 1911 SoulVay conference on the theory of radiation in Quanta.
Using Photoshop, I've introduced a few anachronisms.
See if you can spot all 24.
I'll give you the first one.
Madame Curie should not be wearing a digital watch.
And go.
That's it, bye-bye.
Bazinga!
I have an override switch.
I almost died.
And I'm safe and sound in bed.
Who's crazy now?
I'm still gonna go with you.
I'm sure she's the best fit for our little...
That's what we call it, Rebel Alliance.
Oh, I've never identified with the Rebel Alliance.
Despite their tendency to build death stars, I've always been more of an empire man.
Yeah, not my point.
I know what your point is.
You're intimidated by Amy's intellect.
To that, I say, fuck up.
Okay, let me just get right to it.
Amy is judgmental, sanctimonious, and frankly, just obnoxious.
So?
So we already have you for all that.
Are you suggesting I terminate my relationship with Amy?
No, no, of course not.
Just have your relationship someplace else.
It's called counterfactuals.
We postulate an alternate world that differs from ours in one key aspect,
and then pose questions to each other.
It's fun for ages 8 to 80. Join us.
All right, I like a good brain teaser.
Give it a whirl.
You're in luck. This is an easy one.
In a world where mankind is ruled by a giant intelligent beaver,
what food is no longer consumed?
A BLT where the B stands for beaver.
Leonard B. Sirius, we're playing a game here.
I can figure this out. Let's see.
Well, beavers eat tree bark.
The only tree bark I know that humans consume is cinnamon.
So I'll say cinnamon.
Incorrect. Obviously the answer is cheese Danish.
What?
In a world ruled by a giant beaver, mankind builds many dams
to please the beaver overlord.
The low-lying city of Copenhagen is flooded.
Thousands die, devastated the Danes never invent their namesake pastry.
How does one miss that?
Man.
Surprise.
Man, what an unexpected pleasure.
Man, that's a powerful smell.
I'd like you to meet Oppenheimer, Frisch, Penowsky, Feynman, Wieskopf.
Yeah, I get it. You got a lot of cats and you gave them cute Jewish names.
Cats make wonderful companions.
They don't argue or question my intellectual authority.
And this little guy here, I think you'll find to be quite zazzy.
You should've called soon.
Howard, if you want my help, I've got to know what happened.
But it's embarrassing.
Yeah, that's what I'm counting on, spill.
Okay, well, you know a world of warcraft.
The online game? Sure.
Did you know that the characters in the game can have sex with each other?
Oh God, I think I see where this is going.
Her name was Glissinda the Troll.
Bernadette walked in on me while we were doing the cybernasty under the bridge of souls.
Oh, you're right, that is so embarrassing.
Would you talk to her?
Bernadette or the troll?
Bernadette.
She was so mad at me she wouldn't even listen to my side of the story.
What was your side?
Well, Froino, Glissinda the Troll wasn't even a real woman.
She could've been a 50 year old truck driver in New Jersey.
Really, and that didn't make her feel better?
Spin class worked up quite a sweat.
Joy, this is Leonard, Leonard, this is Joy.
Hi.
You don't look like a genius.
Go ahead and say something smart.
Ah, time's up.
Just kidding.
First thing you need to know about me, I'm hilarious.
Yeah.
So Bernadette tells me she knows you from the self-defense class?
Yeah, it's really Krav Magal, lots of fun.
Basically, a hundred different ways to rip a guy's nuts off.
Wow, wouldn't think that'd be that many.
Number 42?
Whoa!
Isn't she a parent?
The slops do is good on the way down and the way up.
Should be, it's $30 a pound.
Hey, this is a date, right?
Yep, it is.
73!
Excuse me, I have to go to the little girls' room and take a wicked wizz.
I'll be the king.
Fair warning, I have the asparagus.
My pee is going to stink up the place.
That's okay, you can just sleep here.
Oh, good, a slumber party.
We'll do makeovers, initiate phony phone calls and have spirited pillow fights in our frilly nighties.
Oh, gosh, Amy, I don't know if I would call this an actual slumber party.
Oh, that's disappointing, I've always wanted to be invited to a slumber party.
Oh, you never were? Not even when you were a kid?
Well, there was the time I had my tonsils out and I shared a room with a little Vietnamese girl.
She didn't make it through the night, but up till then it was kind of fun.
Okay, well, I guess we're having a slumber party.
Pillow fight!
The thing I drew this up, what's that?
I present to you the relationship agreement.
A binding covenant that in its 31 pages enumerates, iterates and codifies the rights and responsibilities of Sheldon Lee Cooper,
here and after known as the boyfriend, and Amy Farah Fowler, here and after known as the girlfriend.
It's so romantic.
Mutual indemnification always is.
Why don't you start perusing while I set up my notary stamp?
Section 5, handholding.
Handholding is only allowed under the following circumstances.
A, either party is in danger of falling off a cliff, precipice or ledge.
B, either party is deserving of a hearty handshake after winning a Nobel Prize.
C, moral support during flu shots.
Seems a bit restrictive.
Yeah, feel free to retain a lawyer.
Hey, Cedar, how's it going?
I'm not so good, we have to talk.
Oh, so serious.
Okay, here it is.
I met this girl and I kissed her and I feel terrible about it, but it's done, it's never going to happen again, and I am so, so sorry.
Not on, life's okay.
It is.
These things happen. They happen to everybody.
Oh my God, you are amazing.
I don't deserve you. Well, what do you mean everybody?
Leonard, I didn't know if I should tell you,
but I kind of cheated on you too.
I, kind of?
A couple of weeks ago, I slept with my ex-boyfriend.
So I guess we both messed up a little.
No, no, I messed up a little, you messed up a lot.
Well, there's not a competition.
Oh, we had it, and you won.
Good morning, handsome.
Morning, mom.
It's me.
Yes, it is, and you're so pretty in the morning.
Your mom and I need your breakfast.
Wow, so you guys are getting along?
I guess. We're very different people, Howard, so communication's a little tricky.
Does he like the pet pet?
He didn't try them yet.
Is there any butter?
Butter flavored syrup.
Stop what's the word!
He wants butter!
It's butter flavored syrup!
I just told him that!
I don't need any butter.
If you want butter, I'll get you butter.
I guess I'll cut these by myself.
Be sure to check the mail.
How many times are you going to tell me?
Nothing.
It's about suspicious that I'm fixating.
It's consistent with my personality.
Right.
More Halloween candy than she just bought a bunch of it yesterday?
Oh, yeah, that's gone.
It's a rough month when Halloween and PMS sit at the same time.
But Leonard doesn't have time to chat. He has to get the mail.
When you relax, I'll get it in a minute.
Hey, I was work. Open the mail.
Excuse me.
Couple of circulars. Nothing important.
What's the pin?
Hang on.
You might be from Texas, but I'm from New Jersey.
Test my ringtone.
Rock is mad!
That really is a good song.
There's a reason he's so old and John, they don't make you a night-feriting wake me up before you go, go.
How are you coming down for breakfast?
I told you I have a video conference with NASA. I said don't bother me.
Oh, let's have a picture of astronauts.
Yes, please, let's have a picture of astronauts.
Hey, good morning.
Hey, Howard, thanks for getting up so early.
No problem, Dr. Masamino.
The guy's here call me mass.
That's a cool nickname because force equals mass times acceleration.
Yeah, it's just short for Masamino.
Anyway, the plan for this morning is to go over to the...
Sorry, my phone.
What is that? Is that rocket man?
Yeah, my ringtone, kind of my favorite song, Rocket Man.
How are the Jeff Froot loapting getting soggy?
Not now!
What's that?
My mom, sorry.
No problem. Fruit loops.
I am... I'm lovable.
That's just the booze talking.
It's not I, but I had a drink since last night.
You're talking to me?
I am.
I'm crying for a whole different reason.
So, I guess what I'm saying is I get where Lucy's coming from.
That's great. Do you want some wine?
No, what is fine.
I've been thinking about it a lot and I totally see why Lucy did what she did.
I pushed too hard, but you know what?
If I back off, maybe give her enough space. Maybe this is in the future for us.
The funny thing about life is that sometimes something you think is going to be good.
I have a very shat ah.
And it turns good again and that means it's better than if it had never been bad for a while.
I know you are.
You are now things aren't good.
They are in fact very, very bad.
But at least my heart is trying to heal.
It was slowly but surely...
How I cried, it was like a little laugh.