What country's capital is going to fastest in the world?
How do you not know this?
You really don't know what?
Ireland. It's Dublin.
You're a comedic genius.
I don't know about...
Somebody's about to make the set.
Welcome to Celebrity Dad Jokes.
I am Nick Cannon.
I'm super dad. Today we're going to be telling some dad jokes with the one and only Kevin Hart.
Hurry up, Nick.
Another super dad.
And we're going to be talking about his new show. Another show.
This show is very special. Little cat.
There she is, man.
I'm really excited about it.
We're going to get to it.
And you know how this works, man.
The rules are you laugh you lose.
We're going to be doing some dad jokes.
So the goal is not to laugh.
Not to laugh.
But if it gets you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We being...
King of Corny.
I got it.
This is what I do.
I got it. I got it.
I'm a famous dad joke.
So I'm just...
You ready?
I'm ready.
You go for it.
What do you call a musician who's bad with money?
Sorry, funny.
What do you call it?
Broke Eropocity.
Go.
You next.
All right.
All right. Did you know it was illegal to laugh loudly in Hawaii?
You didn't know that?
No.
Yeah, you got to keep a low-haw.
Stupid.
Low-haw.
That's good.
All right, good.
All right.
Oh, boy.
Did you hear about what happened to the vampires in New York?
No.
Got killed with the cheese steak.
Okay, come on.
To the heart.
All right.
That's stupid.
Now, that's dumb.
That was dumb.
It's on the car.
No, that's dumb.
That was...
That's cheese steak.
Did you do it from Philly?
We talked about that.
Yeah, that's why that was stupid.
That was stupid.
That joke.
Okay.
That pizza man stuck in the press.
No.
Well, probably didn't hear it because there wasn't mushroom.
Let's talk a little bit.
Congratulations.
Thank you, man.
It's animated.
I mean, you are always on the cutting edge in doing things that people don't get to do.
I mean, tell the world about...
Let's give them an overview of what audiences can expect.
Look, this is one of the things that I gotta be honest is a passion project.
I've been trying to develop this for over seven or eight years,
and try to figure out a way to get into the animation space
from a perspective in my point of view,
but to where I could also highlight my city in a way that nobody else could.
I feel like, you know, when you talk about the hood
and we talk about our environment that we grew up in,
it's always painted with a crazy bad overview.
Right.
People always highlight the bad,
and I was like, there's so much good in the bad.
You know, like when you talk about the neighborhood,
with the people that aren't necessarily at the top of the food chain in life,
but they serve a valuable purpose to the community.
This animation is about uplifting those people.
You know, the guy that's on the corner, the people that are on the stoop.
The neighborhood knows the woman that's in the window watching the kids,
and that responsibility to tell on the kids to their parents,
and how many people actually are raising a kid,
like in a community like that. It takes a village.
So just kind of showing what that village dynamic was for me as I was coming up.
That's dope, and when I look at it, even the animation style is nostalgic.
Like it feels like the cartoon we grew up watching,
like without purposeful, like...
All all intent.
All all done with the strong intent to be different,
go back to the times where I was a kid,
things that I gravitated towards, the reason why cartoons were special.
You know, I wanted to feel that,
and I wanted the kids today to feel it.
You know, and my test was my kids, you know, giving my kids.
They rock with it?
Yeah, that was it. That's the big test.
You passed the test and you're like...
So it was like that.
This is it.
So have do...
No, they had this funny.
Like when it goes...
Because they are a top audience.
I know your kids.
Your kids will be like...
We're no longer cool, which is why this is what I get.
Oh, this is why it gets working.
This is very much fitting right now.
I'm fine with that.
Yeah, I'm fine with that.
Let's get right back to it.
What do you call a moose with no name?
I don't know.
A Nana moose.
Okay.
Alright.
Because he's a...
I get it.
You don't know his name.
But he's a moose.
I get it.
Instead of saying a Nana moose.
Yeah.
You just put moose.
I get that.
I urge you.
I got it.
Yeah.
No.
Okay.
What do you call beef cropped against the wall?
Whoa, this is a family show.
What do you call...
I want you to know you like that.
A lean meat.
That's a lean meat.
Right.
Propped against the wall.
You got to beef.
So that's a lean meat.
That's what that is.
Because lean it against the wall.
Against the wall.
Okay.
I thought that was good.
Yeah.
I'm getting a little bit more riskate.
Bro, that joke.
I was definitely dead jokes after dark.
Alright.
Oh.
What does Sylvester Stallone and Lil Kev's upbringing both have in common?
It actually is real question.
They both were a little rocky.
That's why you were a community.
Did I get it?
You dead?
Yeah.
Right there on the call.
I just really wanted to take for it.
I was like, you tell people I could have been a good student.
I just took a while for me to figure it out.
I get it.
Yeah.
I struggled with the work they was giving me.
We all did.
They was giving me stuff like this.
Eight plus.
Yeah.
The teachers were stupid.
Alright.
Why did the patient refuse to pay the proctologist for her butt lift?
First of all, what's the proctologist?
Well, that's problematic.
You need to know what that is.
That's good to get.
Okay.
The big word through me.
Why did the patient refuse to pay the proctologist for her butt lift?
I don't know why.
Come on, man.
She said it still had a little crack in it.
You got it.
They laughed.
I'm not paying for this.
It's still a crack in it.
Why do I have a crack in it?
You got it.
Explain it.
It's what he said.
Yeah, because it's imperfect.
It's a crack in it.
It's damaged.
I'm not paying for that.
Okay.
Alright, man.
Let's talk about the character.
How close is he to me?
The little Kevin Hart.
Oh, man.
Very.
Very, very.
Very, very, very.
The experience is when you open the story.
The story's in the real, real, real upbringing, real mom and dad moments.
You know, my mom and dad were never together.
So that separation and that stitching that relationship that they had through my upbringing
was special.
Funny.
Now I can look back on it and grab all the humor from it.
But that dynamic of love, hate and problem was one that I was like really in the middle
of.
You know, having the older brother, having my uncle, you know, and having my mom be the
spiritual but strict and forced it as she was.
Right.
You know what I mean?
Like where I fit it in the school, where the bullying came in, how I got around it, all
of those things are really coming from the mind of remember.
So I think the audience is going to respond to it because it's relatable.
It's relatable and I think, you know, anybody coming from the culture and from the
environment of the hood, you're going to be able to go, oh, I had moments that were
the same if not equally alive.
Now are there any specific memories that influenced the show?
Absolutely.
You know, I put the teacher bit in there.
Oh, the cousin.
Yeah, when I went to custody, I was a teacher.
Clath, but they have the whole scene in there.
Whole scene of me going in and why and how I got the cousin out the teacher, my mom didn't
have to come to the school and mess up what she said.
She said and her saying it, but being honest and then her cousin to teach her out because
the teacher said some stuff that she didn't like.
You know, my first fight with the bully and how I had success in throwing the first punch.
Right.
I thought because of that, the fight was over and then the bully went on to whip my
ass out and you found out that the bully could fight and then vice I got from my uncle
was wrong, which was just hit him first.
Don't know bully expect you to hit him.
Swing on him first and watch everything change.
You literally are one of the greatest storytellers of our time and for you to take the stuff
that we have known for and your stand up and hearing all these amazing stories and now
to see it animated man.
I mean, that's the next level.
Thank you, man.
All right.
What do you call it if low-cav gets beat up by a group of elderly people?
What do I call it?
Low-cav gets beat up by a group of elderly people.
I mean, a bad day.
What do you call it?
A heart attack.
Okay.
They own.
But you're very hard.
They attack you.
That's what I get.
That's not what I get.
What country's capital is going the fastest in the world?
How do you not know this?
You really don't know what.
Ireland, it's Dublin.
You're a comedic genius.
Somebody's about to make the sit.
What?
Alright.
What do tires reminisce about?
The times when I used to roll the good year.
That's actually good.
That's good.
I don't think about the good year.
Right.
Again.
Alright.
I don't know if you've heard the DJ use, is this belong?
No, I just don't.
There we go.
That public school education.
Oh no.
It's belong to Jeanine.
That's not how you spell belong to Jeanine.
What?
What did you say?
You used ball of Naga.
Ball of Naga?
No, it's belong to Jeanine.
Look at that.
He's better.
Never seen it.
You're not a neat boy.
I don't hate belong to you.
This is news to me.
I'm going to write this down.
Ballon, you got a personal.
Why did the DJ use Ballon instead of albums on his turntables?
Because you wanted to have a cold cut.
No.
Oh shit.
Yeah, that's actually right.
Because he wanted some cold cuts.
Yeah, that's good.
See?
I really didn't know that he's spelled belong.
That's the sound.
I wasn't thinking there.
That was a real dumb moment that you captured on camera.
It's doing what you want with that.
That's all you said.
Why now?
Why anime?
We both dads.
I mean, I always love when I can do content that my kids can enjoy.
I've seen you around your kid, you know?
Amazing father.
What's that?
Yeah, I mean, look, you're in the time of our lives where everything you do is for your kids.
Right?
We're out of the stages of caring for ourselves.
It's all about what can impact, what can impact, what will they like and enjoy.
Yeah.
So the more that you can do for them, the better.
You know, if this takes off and it gets to a place of merchandise, lunch boxes, backpacks,
you know, toys, anything in that space, I'll achieve an amazing goal, a personal one.
And, you know, to have them possibly be in a position where they can play with the things
that are reminiscent of their father or their father's old times.
It'll be huge, man.
So it's definitely kid-specific, you know, with a touch and passion of like my personal desire
to tap into all spaces in the entertainment business just to say that.
Yeah, and it's dope because it is a family show.
So the parents can't enjoy this as much as the kids.
Absolutely.
This style of humor that we got going right here.
What do you call...
There's some personal items.
What do you call low-cav with glasses?
What do I call low-cav with glasses?
I don't know.
Short, siding.
Okay.
I know you heard that, though.
That's what I know.
That's never heard that.
Because you short.
No, I get it.
Because it is near-siding.
I know what you're saying.
And it's far-sighted.
But you'll know, I get it.
Short.
I get it.
I get it because of the loud-cheek.
No, I'm not laughing, Nick, because it was stupid.
Okay?
That's why.
You know, I try to start a conversation with an elevator,
but it just let me down.
That's stupid.
It's delivery, then.
It's all the delinquents.
You got the good delivery of jokes going land.
Ain't no such thing as a bad dad, dude.
Oh, wow.
This is me.
No, no, you're right.
Okay.
What's one thing an orphan can't take?
Oh, God.
Oh, shit.
I'm sorry.
Family photo.
Oh, come on, man.
Come on, man.
I wrote this one.
It's evil.
That can't be a dad, dude.
This is a bad joke.
I'm not worried about the dad joke.
There's one thing called orphanage.
A family.
He's just crazy.
A bitch with dad.
What is that?
What are we doing?
What is it?
We're ruining kids' lives.
There's no dodgers sign the Kool-Aid man.
You didn't know that?
I did not.
That's crazy.
He's a pitcher.
He's here because the Kool-Aid is in the pitcher.
Nobody?
Oh, yeah.
Busting through the wall.
That's a pitcher.
The Kool-Aid man is the natural pitcher.
You ain't got it.
I'm not a pitcher.
It's waiting to meet you.
That's it.
You are a comedic.
Get number one fan.
Come on.
I could do this all day.
Besides, a little kid.
Who's your favorite character on the show?
Besides me, why do you like this?
Why do you like this?
I like this.
You know, I like this.
Of coursetekin won't be in the show because it's an amazing
talent that she is.
But seeing what Wanda was able to bring to the character.
I mean, that's dope man.
And you know, the world knows this.
They've seen us together for what?
Almost 30 years now.
And I didn't get a call or audition for a voice or no shit.
Because everybody knows what you sound like.
Everybody knows what the sights sound like.
I didn't think about that.
It's supposed to be my best friend for it.
When you say it like that, I'm like damn.
I can't be the voice of the dog.
I can't.
Now, now, let's you say that.
I got kids too.
I just said, but now did you say the way you said it?
My kids want to enjoy this.
My kids are friends.
No, I got to get it.
I'm going in the tank tank.
You ain't doing it.
No, because what you just said, everything I do, I include him.
No, and this is where we got to get better.
That's where we got to get better.
Yeah.
No, I got to get back to the dance.
OK.
I'm ready to do it.
I'm mad now.
I'm going to do this.
I'm going to wait.
Rightfully so.
It's supposed to be my best friend.
For sure.
I just, I don't know where I found out that he had a car.
Turned his, I was turning on the TV.
Nobody let me know.
What's black and funny with curly hair that can be used
to start a barbecue grill?
Black, funny.
Curly hair can be used to start a barbecue grill?
Sure, I'll end it.
What?
What's the answer?
That's exactly true.
You can go up your ass with saying that.
It's amazing.
A Dion Cole.
OK.
The sure one was funny.
Because that was a black.
No, OK.
I'm doing this.
I thought that was real.
OK.
All right.
Here we go.
Who's DoorDash's main competition when it comes to deliveries?
When it comes to deliveries, you don't notice?
DoorDash's main competition when it comes to deliveries.
Who's delivering more than DoorDash?
Nick Cannon.
It's a boy.
It's a girl.
Twins.
That's a real adage.
I got a lot of kids, deliveries.
I did it.
Yeah.
That was good.
But you didn't say it.
Because I didn't get it at first.
I got it when you explained it.
All right.
That's probably the worst one of the show.
I don't know if you would say that.
That was horrible.
All right.
One, nothing funny about it.
Why are you talking about my kids?
I'm seeing this was supposed to be a good episode.
I'm coming here to support my friend.
Now you want to talk about my personal life.
I have a lot of kids.
That's not funny.
I didn't write the die joke.
I'm reading a Zona God damn paper.
Somebody going to be fired.
Make fun of me.
I'm a good father.
I got to pick up some kids after this.
I think you're grateful.
Why didn't Lil Kav give a cheese steak to the woman
who had her purse though?
He heard she needed a hero.
Okay.
That's it.
You done?
I'm going to do one more.
You're getting a...
Okay.
All right.
Oh Nick, this is crazy.
You know I saw a baker break up with his girlfriend.
Yeah.
A baker.
A baker break up?
It broke up with his girlfriend.
It was just crazy.
Right.
Yeah.
He said he needed space.
Think about it.
I mean need it.
Yeah.
No.
It's not gonna be good.
Yeah.
Give me one more.
We overdeam ourselves with this.
These are ladders.
Those are two that's last one.
Yeah.
Why didn't the bicycle go to the club?
Why?
Because it was too tired.
That's not that.
That's too tired.
That's not bad.
Okay.
We owe.
We don't go to the club no more.
Too tired.
This is my culture.
You know what?
I saw my bodybuilder a friend trying different sauces the other day.
I guess you could say those were weighted dips.
Bodybuilder.
There we have it ladies and gentlemen.
This has been an amazing episode of celebrity dad jokes with my so called best friend.
I want to talk to you about some stuff.
We're deadness.
I want to talk to you.
No cat.
No cat, man.
Make sure you guys go watch it.
Go streaming on BET Plus.
Yeah.
Dropping March 6th.
Man, you got to love the hustle and bustle of my amazing neighborhood.
Hey, hey, hey.
Get ready to be amazed by your boy, little kid.
My little boy is growing up.
Get your stinkin' hands off of me.
Hey, that's my little brother Kevin you laughing at.
You got to be talking to him.
Hey, what's up?
This is M-C-E-R.
Coming at you live.
Remember break it down.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
It's going down, man.
I'm not in it.
Oh, well, come on, man.
That's ridiculous, Nick.
That's ridiculous.
But guess what?
Season 2, huh?
I can audition.
Well, we could talk.
Let's talk about what.
Sorry, guys.