There's only one thing that beats a girl with an amazing voice.
And that's Chris Brown.
MUSIC
Oh my god.
She's so fresh.
People say I can't get a white woman.
She gives the best head.
Sorry I was in the studio.
And that's the intro.
Is this paper rock?
Sure.
Nice to see you by the way.
All right, you can see is this paper rock.
Is this paper rock?
All right.
You and me.
I'll go first.
What do we have today?
Nice and easy.
Have you heard of the new Russian movie streaming service?
I have not.
Nyetflix.
Just straight off the bat.
I'm going to try on this one.
I'm trying.
It's another one.
Get away and start.
I'm going to do it.
You got to do it.
I'm going to bet.
Yeah.
Did that bottle of Patron ever?
Yeah, I just went for better pay-be.
It's much faster.
For last one.
This isn't going to go down well.
OK.
Here we go.
Where is she going?
Give it a hug.
It's going to be a rough day.
What's the difference between Paul Walker and my grandmother?
Oh, God.
What?
Paul Walker made it to 100.
Oh!
I don't know who.
Yeah.
All right.
That's not...
That's not dark.
I got a key one.
So Mary gave birth to Jesus, right?
And Jesus was the Lamb of God.
So technically, Mary had a little Lamb.
That was really good.
That was fucking gay, though.
Thank you.
Gay.
I think that's good up for you.
Yeah.
Oh, what's that one?
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
What's that one?
It's like...
It's like, um, like, medicine.
Oh, yeah.
It looks like a lot of love.
How do you like it?
Kind of cute, but...
How do you say sub-dog in Japanese?
Sub-dog?
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry.
I love an accent, I love it.
That one...
I have been that a little bit before I was like this.
Yeah, tell me the punch, though.
Um, can you chew awa?
Oh, cute.
Is that real?
Is that just real?
No.
Oh, can you chew awa?
No, it's alright.
How was your age in accent filming?
I practiced in the mirror every night.
You're gonna be more black accent.
Go on, do it.
Go on.
It's so hot.
It's really good.
And Ian has reached his word quarter for the episode.
I got another cute Jesus one.
A cute Jesus one, and we'll be...
What's the difference between Jesus and a prostitute?
What's that?
The sound they make when you're nailing him.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
Oh, no.
He's going wild.
Oh, stop talking.
Thank God we're going to nail him in the couch now.
He's going to go crazy.
What spell did Harry Potter use when he worked at Planet Parenthood?
What?
He is deletus.
Beed...
Beedeth deletus.
That's good.
I like that.
Beedeth deletus.
I like this one.
Did you know that coconut water is great for hair growth?
OK.
That's why my pews have been growing like crazy.
Oh.
And that's why I used the Manscape Performance Package 5.0 Ultra.
And we're packing.
We've got the Lormo of 5.0 Ultra, the 5th generation trimmer.
With two interchangeable skin-safe blade heads.
Which makes it the ultimate sack worker without the pain or pews.
The package also comes with a weed worker 2.0.
The crop preserveer and the crop reviver.
The shed 2.0, the perfect place to keep everything in this package secure.
And the box is 2.0 to keep your package secure.
So to keep your nuts silky smooth, use the promo code YeahMad at Manscape.com
and you'll get 20% off free international shipping and two free gifts.
Go to Manscape and get rid of pubes fast.
How do you know Mike Tyson is anti-religion?
Anti-religion.
Because he always punches people in the faith.
In the face.
Ah.
I like you.
Does Pat explain to Pat and please explain to Pat.
There you go. He has a boxer. He's got a list.
He's got a list.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm good at chickening.
I like getting one.
Do you like getting one?
Is it better, are you sure?
I think it's better.
Oh my god.
I mean, I think she's a little funny.
One point to Rory.
Don't fight challenge.
Why is that so funny?
OK. OK.
OK.
What do you call a gay man in a wheelchair?
What?
A fruit roll up.
Oh my god.
Oh jeez.
That was good.
Yeah, I think it's good. They're getting dark.
We got to dark off.
What's the best thing about being a test tube baby?
What's that?
Woon with a view.
Checked out.
What's the suicide bomb as biggest fear?
What?
Dying alone.
Jesus Christ.
To catch so fucking heck.
I'm the thing.
Suicide bomb as.
I love anal sex.
It's right up my alley.
I wrote that either.
I'm sorry.
I'm a little right up my alley.
Yeah.
I like to wear you said you like that.
You laugh.
Oh shit.
I'm getting close to that point as well.
It's not good.
Oh, this is just not nice tasting.
It doesn't taste nice.
Oh.
Oh, okay.
You got this, you got this.
You got this girl.
What was the difference between a pregnant woman and a lot more?
What?
You can't unscrew a pregnant woman.
You're a jack.
That's a good jack.
How was that?
I know.
Yeah.
Um...
Why do police get to protest early?
To beat the crowd?
Yeah.
You need a bit more from you guys.
Good energy, I mean.
Thank you.
You never...
What's the difference between a car key and a kid?
Oh god what?
A car key doesn't turn pad on.
That was good.
That was such a snuck and a felt in tummy.
That was bad, bad, bad, bad, bad.
That was disgusting.
Have you heard about the disease that only affects terrorists?
I haven't known.
Covid-9-11.
Oh my god.
And that joke was brought to you by Taliban Airways.
Always making sure your flight is a blast.
Oh my god.
Can you edit it like an ass?
Please do say it.
That's a good thing.
That was bad Airways.
Always make sure your flight is a blast.
Use the code shaft to get 20% off your building.
It's a bad thing.
I don't want to go away with it too.
Oh what's it?
No, no, that was a mistake.
Oh my god.
Oh, okay.
Oh.
You're the bomb.
No, you're the bomb.
A compliment in the US, but an argument in the Middle East.
Oh my god.
That's pretty good.
You don't know that.
That was good.
That was a good joke.
I love.
Did I love?
No.
No, good.
Hey, are you an American school?
Because I want to shoot some kids into you.
Oh my god.
I need no even to pick up minds.
I want to shoot some kids in you.
That's the French life.
What do you call an necrophilic gangbang?
What?
Cracking open a cold one with the boys.
Oh Jesus.
Oh my god.
He shoots.
He'll...
Catherine.
Oh, through.
That's the ghost of the dead guy.
Er...
What's pink and covered in cobwebs?
Madeline McCann's bike bicycle.
Oh, dude.
Oh, oh.
Yeah, that is dark.
I had another punch line for that one.
What's pink and covered in cobwebs?
Cat Spagina.
But I didn't want to say it.
He's like, no, I couldn't do that.
I couldn't do that on camera.
I didn't want to say that on camera.
I think that's too rude.
Look here.
I didn't say it on one camera.
I didn't want to say it on that camera.
That's...
That's good.
I didn't say it on camera.
That's bad.
It's the ones that the security guard...
Oh, no.
The security guard comes over and bar and goes...
...blossom jokes for you mate.
And just list them all and sat there.
I was just sharing a funeral once.
And it probably wouldn't have been so bad if the ringtone wasn't another one but it's the dust.
They're like, oh, do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do.
They were polyphonic.
That's funny. That's good.
Do do do do do do do do do.
That's fucking...
That should be the walk out song for this episode.
Oh, there's a goo in.
There's only one thing that beats a girl with an amazing voice.
And that's Chris Brown.
Oh my god.
Shit, that was good.
Yeah, that's really...
Oh.
I'm back baby.
I love that, Jake.
Rub it, sir.
What did the cops say when they shot a ginger person?
What?
I guess orange is the new black.
That's great. That's good.
This one's for sound daddy, Dad.
Yeah. Yeah.
Why do Indian women have a red dot on their head?
Because they never fucking listen.
Sam, that's...
Yeah.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, I go.
What can you say at both a birthday party and an execution?
What?
Wait, let me go get the knife.
All right, last one.
Matt, I'm gonna need your help on this one.
What happens when the Pope goes to the toilet?
Holy shit!
You can't open it!
No!
How about this go?
Oh, 50.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, shit!
I was so worried he wouldn't be be asleep with something.