And is it true that you are mistaken for Daniel Radcliffe?
It happens a lot.
And he's mistaken for me and apparently signs my name.
Because cheeky.
Yeah, apparently.
It's a Jew the time.
You're busy.
I was in an elevator once.
This was many years ago.
But I was in an elevator.
And you know that thing when you're in an elevator
with one other person and there's that kind of awkward silence.
And you're both kind of looking busy doing not like
at the buttons and at the phone.
And so there was that.
And I could tell that this by this guy's energy
that he wanted to say something.
He was working it up, working it up, working it up.
And then all of a sudden he burst out and said, Harry Potter.
And I was like, no.
So funny.
Well, let's see how it could happen.
Let's put a look at some examples.
There you are.
Now, it's a turdful face.
Smile.
It's not, you know what I mean?
I do sort of see it.
Let's try another one.
I'll try another one.
OK, turn to the side.
That's not so good.
Let's see one more.
How do I?
How about Kim?
I'm kidding.
That's great.
You're both in your own ways.
Sort of sex symbols.
There are...
Well, you are.
Don't laugh at that.
I think I'm...
Encourage the guests.
Oh, no.
You're sex symbols.
Don't, yes.
This lady's dead with a moon.
It's true.
You get the attention of the ladies.
Yes.
You get...
They don't want to shag me, though.
They want to...
They write to me and say, oh, you seem nice.
Would you like to come to the Gilderming area for a pint?
LAUGHTER
That's quite a lot right there, isn't it, of...
Ordnance.
It's quite enough.
When I did a play here, a long time ago, almost 20 years ago,
in 1990, called Burnness.
I saw that.
And I kept...
I had... I don't anymore.
But I had a whole collection of the letters I received.
Many of which had accompanying photos.
And many of the photos were sort of along the order of either...
This is me on my beach vacation last year in Croatia
on the Dalmatian coast that happened to be a nude beach.
LAUGHTER
This is what I don't get.
This is me with my puppy.
LAUGHTER
No, I'll just crack one off now, then.
So, if it wasn't that sort of photograph, what sort of photograph would it be?
A full close-up of it.
LAUGHTER
Well, a few dendor or the puppy.
No.
The Croatian coast slide.
This isn't me, though.
This isn't me.
Oh, no.
That in an envelope from Mr Mac.
LAUGHTER
This is very good.
He's like this.
LAUGHTER
OK.
Yeah.
We'll go to the comments and then 15 copies were all my favourite.
LAUGHTER
Well, just a little bit more again.
Yeah, a little bit more.
To get replies without a bat.
LAUGHTER
Oh, I've licked it better this time.
This is a beautiful job.
LAUGHTER
That's a beautiful job, yeah.
That's beautiful, darling. That's beautiful.
LAUGHTER
I wasn't even one of those first snow moves at this stage.
No, no.
I want you to do one of the curtains.
No curtains.
I'm not going to look back.
I mean, he were here now.
LAUGHTER
And, you know, you just...
What do you say back to them?
LAUGHTER
In a way you say,
thank you, it's lovely, that's very, very kind, it's fascinating.
But I'm more anal.
LAUGHTER
You know, people thought you'd about the lever...
You're either a potter or a lever.
You're either somebody.
If you're asked where your keys are, you'll say they're where I put them,
in which case you're a good human.
Or you'll say they're where I left them, in which case you will die of dysentery.
LAUGHTER
In relationships, you always get one with the other, you always get a potter with a lever,
because two potters will kill each other.
LAUGHTER
And two levers.
And it's justified, you know, because I've always been the potter.
So I've always been the one going, no, that goes there and that's please, love me.
LAUGHTER
It is interesting this thing about quirky rules for living,
because we've tried it with all these four, because we thought, oh, this'll be funny.
And so, when people laugh at you for your rules,
or did they kind of go, yes, you're so right, we do need rules for living.
Yeah, no, it's a bit of, but I make sure that everyone I talk about,
people will at least see the logic behind.
I don't want to be the nutter on stage, she's going,
I can only eat blue ones.
LAUGHTER
So I like to feel people, not everyone had your attitude,
couldn't everyone have something, even if you don't know.
If you, you'll be at someone's house on the toilet,
and you will turn their toilet roll round, without even knowing you've done it.
And everyone's got a little, yeah, you see your old brother in the kitchen.
What's your, do you have a quirky habit?
Do you have a rule, do you have a quirky habit?
Like a habit?
Yeah.
I used to have some crazy pre-performance, like quirks,
that I've decided to get rid of all of those,
because on the personality type, if I decided I'm going to start needing things
before I go on stage, it's just going to escalate to the point of being completely intolerable.
But in the first two or three years of my career,
I decided in my own crazy mind that I couldn't go on stage,
unless I had some kind of, like, patterned or colored socks and underwear.
I know, crazy.
But I could not have white underwear or socks.
If I go out on stage in white socks and underwear,
it's going to be the worst show I've ever had in my life.
So I would actively find, like, polka dot underwear,
that's where I'm stage, yeah.
So already I'm thinking, you're right, white socks are wrong.
That's right.
White underwear is so good, but white socks are wrong.
Plus a white underwear in a situation of high stress is also...
Maybe that's subconsciously, that's what I was thinking.
Catherine, what do you...
Yeah, no, the thing I still do,
but I think it's related to superstition.
You know that thing they say you should never cross on the stairs.
Well, I do cross people on the stairs,
but I always say in my mind when I cross someone on the stairs
or they cross me on the stairs,
I wish you luck.
No, no, what is it? Oh, shit, oh, god!
No, here it is.
When someone cross me on the stairs, I go,
you give me luck, I bring you luck.
And that's what I say in my head.
I don't wish!
I do it and I can't not say it.
I can't not say it in my head.
David, you crazy?
Do you know something?
Something that I'm aware, I've conquered one.
I used to spend a lot of time...
If you...
Blooks tend to have lots of black socks, right?
And I had to get the right black sock with the right black sock.
And I would spend hours with socks green.
Yes, we got this little bit of ribbing on that.
Is that the same ribbing?
That's not quite the...
But look, great, look, look.
This has changed my life.
Oh, no, no, no, what?
I'm so excited that I can't get my...
Look, this will change my life.
With the hidden pattern.
Oh!
I must do this.
So you can tell...
I'm super-mysecreted in your shoe.
Is the answer to all your...
And these ones will be better, because these ones...
Tell you what day to wear them on!
Yes!
A genius.
You've changed my life.
You're not fit for your husband.
But really about you.
You kind of think, oh, growing up in California must be lovely.
But your school was quite rough.
Yes, my school was...
I grew up in pretty much like ghetto.
I know it's the blonde hair blue eyes that...
That tricks you, but then you hear me talk.
And then you go, what is...
What's wrong with this person?
Don't you get into proper fights?
Yeah, well, you had to be a skinny white girl.
I mean, that's...
You have to be able to defend yourself.
Yeah, right?
Yeah.
Do you have a hood name?
I did.
I can't...
I can't get a...
I'm blind.
I was always back in.
You want to show them what you're packing today?
No, I tapped it.
Oh, you mean this?
Yeah, you're telling me.
She's trying to use something else.
We have a...
I tapped it.
What are you trying to tell us?
We have plenty of things on.
I know.
Clearly, I will say anything for a while.
I got the costume on, so...
Yeah, I do.
She says it's just packing.
We met lift loss.
Now, we're talking about your...
Going to school.
Because your parents weren't very strict.
And your granny...
Your granny was like a bear group.
My granny would have put you to shame.
I'm telling you about your granny.
Okay, my granny was like...
She lived off the land.
I mean, literally, she raised everything that she ate.
And...
And made all her own clothes and everything.
And during the summer, she would go to Arizona.
Where she lived in the valley in California.
That was...
It was about 100 degrees in the summer.
But it was too cold for her.
So she had to go to Arizona where it's 120 degrees during the summer.
And she would walk around with just like her skirt on.
And a pair of sandals.
Topless.
And now this is a woman who has six children, okay?
They were like...
They were down here.
Yeah, they were...
The bad teacher would not have worn them on.
They were like, kind of below the waistband probably.
Or they go off.
That's what the Florida tent is.
Where you could just like flip them over the shoulder for the baby over that.
Well...
That's what they do in Africa, right?
They do.
That's why boobies are supposed to sag,
so that you can put them over the shoulder, wrap it under.
So the babies on the back can eat suckle and you don't have to stop working.
Yeah, a little lessen, right?
I'm all done.
There we go.
So this is...
Is your granny did that?
So my...
I don't know if she ever actually did that.
It's a good one.
But she would go hunting in the desert with a machete and she would come back with a rattlesnakes.
And my uncle said that his...
One of his visuals of his mother is like walking up with sandals, skirt, topless,
bedded snake and bloody machete.
And a smile.
And a spinner.
You have loads of hair.
Yeah.
Absolutely.
Is that amazing?
Yeah.
Because you're...
Now you're...
You had snake.
I have had snake.
It doesn't taste like chicken.
No.
They only say everything tastes like chicken, but it doesn't.
Survival food doesn't taste like chicken.
No, I had...
I had chicken one time at taste like cat.
It was pretty sure that it was cat.
From the end.
Yeah.
Maybe a taste like cat.
I was like cat.
Yeah.
I was like...
That's not a chicken leg.
That's not the biggest chicken leg up there.
That's chicken head of poor.
Yeah, exactly.
Stars in lovely gowns, all dressed up.
That's your...
That's where you...
That's your home.
Yes.
Because now the ostrich...
You're doing the red carpet this year.
I did the red carpet this year, and it was...
You aren't there.
You've been working.
Busy.
Yes.
Hi.
Who are you wearing?
Or who the fuck are you?
I don't have a hair...
Oh, no.
Next to you.
What's this?
Air Forward business.
This is called...
Anybody can say this?
Oh, you can say that in English television.
English television.
I wish that.
Yeah.
I wish I could go for it.
No.
Oh, see.
Oh, God.
It feels wrong to me.
Really?
What can't you say here?
F***.
That's cool.
So don't say it, okay.
The thing is, I see you on the red carpet,
and you see fearless.
But I look to your website, and there you actually go into
the things you'd like to ask people,
but you don't have the nerve.
Well, there are certain rules that you just don't ask people
certain things to their face.
Okay.
So some of the stars, you have Britney.
What would you like to ask Britney?
Well, I would love to say, why not the eyebrows also?
I'm going for a bitch, do it.
And then, of course, at Katie and Tom.
Now, what would you say to Katie?
What would you say to Katie?
Looks like it popped out of a can.
I shouldn't say it.
What would you say to Katie?
Katie, what would you say to Katie?
The whole thing about the baby, he's there for the birth.
And I said, what's he there for the conception?
I'm at the birth.
I was.
It was fun.
No, I remember when she was pregnant, the New York Post
and the big headdine said, mission impossible.
And finally, at Pinnitabay cruise, what would you be asking
Pinnitabay cruise?
You love her.
All the men love her, yeah.
You do, I think, don't they?
It's kind of a mesh outfit, too.
It looks like it kind of just goes into one.
I'm just looking for the nipples.
You work now.
Look at the nipples now.
A job well done.
If you want to see mine, you want to see mine,
nipples, look at my toes.
Oh, my goodness.
I'd actually love to see your nipples.
I know you would.
She's so beautiful, but I would love to say to her,
do you understand yourself?
I don't know what she's talking about.
But she's kind of cute.
Oh, she's got, she was the prettiest at the, at the Oscars.
You think she was the prettiest?
Oh, there was no question about it.
Who was the worst dress?
Oh, two, Nicole Kidman.
We had long red dress with that white face.
She looked like a ketchup bottle.
Oh, my goodness.
Which end is up, I guess, that's the best.
She and I, oh, and I love her so, Meryl Streep.
Oh, when you're on a ride or another stone that dress,
it was Jess.
She looks like a Chinese lesbian.
She just...
Why, why was she wearing that outfit?
I guess you get to the point where you go, why not?
I mean, how many times has she been?
I guess if you're not going to win, you're new, Helen.
And it's the 30th time there, and you're kind of feeling a little different.
And, you know, what kind of necklace looks quite heavy though, that.
It looks like one of those pensioner alarm things.
Doesn't it, you know?
Meryl knows health was on its way.
Full, half a down the red carpet.
Yes, it looks heavy, doesn't it?
I fall, I can't get out.