What's the difference between Batman and a black man?
Don't know.
Yeah.
Hey, everyone's going off, baby.
Hi.
Nice to see you.
It's nice to not be fighting each other.
I know.
I'm going to give you little legs under here.
Let me get you.
That's tarry good.
OK, let's start the line.
I'm going home.
I'm this guy.
Yeah, we're putting the BJ and BBJ.
That's a really good start.
OK, let's go.
Says the better rock.
Yeah.
Says Pay, per rock.
Fuck.
All right.
Do you want to go first?
I'll let you go first.
OK, here we go.
All right, you guys know the rules.
Let's kick it off.
I'll go first, joke.
I think you're going to start off with a joke about jump ropes.
No, hang on.
I'll skip that.
That was very good.
Thank you.
That was very funny.
That was, yeah, a little awesome.
The delivery could be better.
I'm glad someone explained it to me because I didn't know I knew.
Why did they call them sausage rolls?
Why?
They don't go anywhere.
They should be called sausage steels.
That's that dumb.
I love it.
You love to achieve fat.
What's that?
Which one's fat?
I can't walk you in on this dad masturbator.
What the fuck?
What?
Oh, I don't know why I'm laughing.
It just reminds me of my childhood.
What's a dad?
OK, a boy walks in on his dad masturbating.
The boy goes, Dad, what are you doing?
And the dad goes, I'm masturbating.
You'll know about it soon.
And the kid goes, what do you mean?
And he goes, well, my arm's getting tired.
Oh.
Hit it, foul, Pat.
It's a family thing.
What the family joke about messy baby?
I still don't know.
I still don't know what they like at.
They like it.
Get out of here now.
Good work.
All right.
Hey, girls.
Hey, how are you?
Welcome to the table.
Thank you.
Hello.
Do you want me to go first?
Yes, for sure.
I got an air fryer the other day.
Wow.
I couldn't figure out how to make it work.
Because I was just holding it up in the air.
Nothing was frying.
Classic pain.
Really good.
Thanks.
I loved it.
What did the Mexican photographer name his daughter?
What?
Cameradillas.
I don't know.
The same algorithm of jokes.
Why do Americans eat like their health care is free?
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Why?
That's the joke.
That was unreal.
Yeah.
Yay.
Why?
I love it.
Two America.
Murr.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Maddie's out.
It's my ring.
Maddie's ring.
It's not a girl.
Yeah.
That's the joke.
Let's try the recording.
Oh, shit.
No, that was like a...
Shit, redhead.
I was saying, as well...
Your wig is looking really nice today.
It is.
It's your wig.
It's not a song.
I thought I sang it out of there.
Not me.
Sorry.
What's the female equivalent of tea bagging called a flappuccino?
That's how you feel.
That's so weird.
We're so outnumbered.
It's not funny.
It's cool.
Hold it together, Maddie.
That's cool.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
That was a little mooseball.
Yeah.
He had to flat-life.
Oh.
I'm not.
That's not a long black.
All right.
Okay.
What does Ted Bundy and the cast of your mad have in common?
Which one tell me?
They love a cold one.
Oh.
Yeah.
It's for me.
That's a man.
I was waiting for him to go out.
I wrote that.
I did.
I wrote it.
How did the park get his lesbian sister laid?
I don't know.
Yeah, someone does.
Is there me sister?
I'm sorry.
I can't hear you.
Oh, dude.
Cheers.
That's very funny, Maddie.
That's very funny.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you.
Great job.
Any normal alcohol with you?
There you go.
I think my head is looking good.
Your head does look great.
Don't hurt.
Yeah.
And it only took eight hours.
That's when I get done.
You sound like the parrot on the parrot.
Hey, you know the cracker.
That's good.
This is how it's not taking sass.
You know the cracker.
Oh, my God.
Let's see what we see.
You're cold.
You're locked.
It's a lock.
That's a lock.
Sit over there, I'm going to keep rolling with the pirate jokes.
What's the difference between a casual dinner party and a pirate orgy?
One of them, you come as you are and the other, you are as you come.
You are.
Errrr.
Is that how you guys do it?
I hope not.
It's too many words for me, so it's a bit.
It's actually a myth.
There's a mail-on going on.
How many is it?
Yeah, never happened to.
What do you call a prostituted wheelchair?
Park and ride.
What?
Park and ride?
So when my uncle Frank died, he wanted his remains to be buried in his favourite bear mug.
His last wish was to be Frank and Stein.
That's really good.
What an innocent.
A Stein is what you drink beer out of him.
Stop man's playing with me.
I'm actually blind.
What's a disabled kid's favourite swoon?
Stroke.
I know this one.
I don't think it is because I cooked this joke already.
What?
What's a disabled kid's favourite?
Sit down there, Ross.
It's gone for it.
What?
He's a disabled kid's favourite.
Don't interrupt me.
I don't think it is.
What's a disabled kid's favourite swooning position?
The stroke.
No, it's not.
It's run-off ride.
Is that an Asian disabled kid's run-off ride?
That's going in and behind the scenes.
That's not making a real one.
That's a different one.
Out of the segment or out of your mat?
It's all big.
Reading today is not good.
I met out with someone who smokes.
I call it my nicotine passions.
That's really a sicker.
I like it.
It's a lie.
I don't like it.
Push his leg.
What did one saggy boob say to the other saggy boob?
If we don't get the proper support, people are going to think they're nuts.
That's good.
Do you know how to make a water bed more bouncy?
You put in spring water.
It's just getting the balls breaks.
Oh my god.
Is that a laugh?
A laugh?
I don't know which piece.
Don't drink me, be gentle.
Every time you drink bobbierin.
You deserve it.
You've knocked out two people.
We're going in dog.
This is yours.
Yours is the cold one.
Thanks, bro.
I'll pray shake you.
Why does it look like two of the sound guys are telling jokes to each other?
My not really reported.
You're up.
I got a job as a senior director at Old McDonald's Farm.
Yeah, I'm the CIA.
That's too loud.
That was cute.
I would've loved to hear Timmy tell that joke.
Timmy spells his name with a one.
I'll start as well.
It's the one backwards.
I'll challenge it.
I'll get a long one for you.
There's a teacher in the classroom.
Today we're going to be spelling words that end in eight and eat things.
One guy goes alligator.
Teacher goes fantastic.
Another one goes calculator.
Teacher goes no, that doesn't mean anything.
Doesn't work.
One kid goes vibrator.
Teacher goes look, that doesn't work.
It doesn't eat things.
The kid goes well, my mum says it chew through batteries.
I'm at 80 HD.
That's a good one.
That's still the first one as well.
That's still singing it here.
Yeah.
That's just how he got an adult joke.
Every word of a duck, a duck, a duck, a duck.
Okay.
I was like the Lord of the Rings of Jokes man, that was fucking forever brother.
Back again.
Hello Patrick.
Where does someone go if they injure themselves during a game of pickle boot?
I see you.
I hate that I laughed at that.
That's good.
Cheers.
You're a baby once a day.
I see you.
Welcome back to the table.
I met a guy from North Korea and asked him what his country was like.
Yeah.
What's it like again?
She's about to tell you.
Well he said he can't complain.
I knew it.
That is really, really good.
What's the difference between Batman and a black man?
Batman can go out at night time without Robin.
That's a good joke.
That's a great joke.
I just want to let everyone know that another white guy told me that.
So it should be fine.
Yeah, it was Robin.
I got fired from my job for prank calling 911.
My boss told me it was just plain wrong.
That's a great joke.
They don't get it.
None, 11?
Yeah.
That's always fine.
It's a plain joke.
Well done.
Well done, man.
Thanks guys.
A grasshopper walks into a bar and the bartender says,
Hey, we've got a drink named after you.
A grasshopper says, you got a drink named Steve?
Did you like that one?
Oh, yeah.
It was the delivery.
It was great.
I really liked that joke.
It was good.
Cheers.
There you go.
That was very well done.
Thank you.
Back once again.
Bye.
Oh, oh, oh.
Do you want to go first?
I want me to go first.
I feel like you're loaded with one.
I'm not really.
Okay, I'll go first.
Okay.
What does a Tasmanian chick say after a good rude?
What?
Happy Father's Day.
Oh, my fucking God.
She a whole bar.
That was great, Maddie.
Thank you.
That was great.
Say all you want about pedophiles,
but they always drive really slow in a school zone.
I just had another lesson.
But you walk real slow.
You got this, babe.
You got this.
You're driving bombs.
Go Maddie.
Slot jokes are just horrible.
Holy shit.
You're holy shit in yourself.
You're gonna do that.
Holy shit in yourself.
Holy shit.
Oh, I missed it.
That was a really good one.
I took a sip of that again.
You were really good.
That was a really good one.
See?
Hey.
Oh, my God.
You're crazy with me.
Yeah.
See you next round.
What's your score, man?
Six.
Six existem.
Six all.
Yeah, man.
You were really, man.
You were really good.
Yeah, what do you call a Stone Kid with Down Syndrome?
What the fuck?
What?
I know what Timmy punched me in the good?
You fucking jokes?
What?
A baked potato.
Well, he missed a punch line.
Stapho, yes.
I'm gonna get it.
She's just showing.
I'm like, it's not a guess though.
Jesus showered.
He's so cute.
Oh, okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
A bag of ten.
No.
I told you.
It's not the whole joke.
The whole joke.
That was a joke.
Tell it the joke again, pass it over.
Give it up.
Then my neck step higher that he fucking let his нout.
Oh is that his sword.
Check this out.
How apart of him.
What do you call a petafile with no legs?
A creepy crawly.
Oh!
I've got this tiny hole in the gap.
It's like a bug.
Damn it.
Yeah.
A creepy crawly, okay?
How do you give a bogey a compliment?
Telling me, has a nice teeth.
How do you give pada compliment?
No one's got it!
None of you.
Did you have an opportunity to complete the joke?
Just thought Roy would have interrupted.
Roy!
You're way right to finish the joke.
Roy, finish the joke.
Yeah, one job, Roy.
Don't say that.
To finish your joke, say that.
Just like a dog.
Oh, I heard it.
I heard it.
What did you have written to me?
I don't think you had anything written.
You know what I mean?
You guys.
You literally...
What do you mean?
I finished the joke.
You're up for joke to me.
You did it.
Next week on your man's head.
Shut up.
Yeah, yeah.
You did it to me.
Oh, my next thing when it just set up.
It looks like a...
You say what I'm dead, man.
Why you doing knock-knocks and no one answers?
Why did you kick a guy's around?
I'm just kidding.
Oh my god.
I know you've been an Englishman and you've surely walked into a bar.
What did you want me to say?
I don't know, just something funny.
Oh my god.
You got a cat.
You'll finish whatever joke you write.
I don't know if he's going to keep up with his phone again.
Oh, no, no.
Tell me then.
No, I'm not going to use that.
No, there's a couple.
Oh, shit.
It's a couple.
So Mickey Mouse gets a call from his lawyer.
That tells him, Mickey, I'm sorry, you can't divorce Minnie just because she's funny.
Mickey then says, I didn't say she was funny.
I said she was fucking goofy.
No!
Does that have to laugh at that boy?
What?
I love that boy.
Get him off.
Oh, Tim.
I wasn't going to use this.
No, I said, no.
No, I didn't say this.
I told you.
I'll let them drink their drinks.
Oh, my god.
Oh, dear.
Oh, thanks, good.
Love you, Tim.
Oh, my god.
Oh, again.
Hey.
Hi.
What's going on?
Hey.
Tell me a joke.
So I bought a new car.
I bought a Hyundai accent.
Do you like to go with an accent?
It's the wrong car.
That's okay.
That's a great joke.
Why are there no pharmacies in Africa?
Oh, no.
Oh, dear.
It's going where exactly where you think it's going.
Oh, okay.
Why?
You basically can't take meds on an empty stomach.
Oh.
Yeah.
Couching on a dirty couch.
I do love people like that.
That's me.
I'll just make it back to you.
I'll make it back to you.
I'm going to say something.
Yeah.
Oh, my god.
Oh, that's not going to be true.
What was that?
That's not going to be true.