Um, 40 mouth disease.
Yeah.
More like 40 mouth, yes please.
LAUGHTER
I don't know what I'm doing.
Are we hugging? Are we hugging?
You're lying, you're already?
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh my god, how are you feeling?
I am feeling nervous.
I'm feeling nervous.
You feeling nervous?
I am.
I should actually hurt you feeling.
Yeah, that's how communication kind of goes.
LAUGHTER
But yes, no, I'm nervous too.
That's good.
That's going to be great. All right, we...
In his AI.
Oh, yeah, there you are.
I'm also holding the camera at the same time.
LAUGHTER
Um, can you show me your little sister's pepper off?
Let's show her sister's pepper off.
OK, ready? Yeah.
OK.
This is paper off.
Oh.
Let's do it this chemistry.
Seems like Ian's going to be the one that Foxpaten.
LAUGHTER
That's the nicest thing someone ever said to me.
OK, so you want, do you want to go...
I'll go first. OK.
Yeah. Like that.
So I've been writing dad jokes.
I've been writing dad jokes.
I wrote a lot of dad jokes that actually wrote a book.
Yeah, it's a...
It's a thousand and one dad jokes by Ian Luther.
Do you want to have a look through it?
That's OK.
LAUGHTER
Just a stud jokes.
That's fine.
Like, you've got to go.
Oh!
This is the title of this work, though.
This guy came in cross, man.
This is true.
Now, it's fully...
Yeah, it's dead set.
Oh, what?
Heaps, if you guys don't have it.
That's the one I'm here.
Get me in the steps.
Yeah, tough, yeah.
I laughed as well, so I'm going to drink.
The craziest thing is, that's the first book,
Paten's Ever Red.
I did read the hungry caterpillar once.
OK?
LAUGHTER
Oh, jeez.
She is sorry.
Mmm.
Oh, are you having a drink?
Oh, my god, that's...
What do you call a rooster that's not good at maths?
A disappointment?
A math and a chicken.
Does that count as a laugh?
Oh.
You're like, yeah, fuck that.
It's just relieving his childhood.
I am.
A disappointment.
You're laughing?
Yeah, I've got a cool chicken a lot.
Oh.
Does that count as...
LAUGHTER
You're not a chicken.
I'm not. Thank you.
You are.
That's the second nicest thing someone said to me today.
Of course I go.
Oh, I'm really going to keep this.
This is exactly what I call that.
It's an easy read.
LAUGHTER
You're a vlogger.
So I was watching these two minds have sex the other day.
Yeah, they were doing unspeakable things to each other.
LAUGHTER
That was good.
I like that.
Thank you.
I love her.
This is about to be the most awesome episode.
Yeah.
It's like I'm bored.
He'd say the N word.
LAUGHTER
Never kill you.
Do I have your permission?
I can't do this.
Your permission.
I'll pay you a visit.
I was going to pay you really.
Can we just beep and pretend I said that.
Relaxing.
Ah!
Now I can't read my phone.
You can pick it up.
Letting you do it's things.
These go what?
These.
Ah.
So you said a disease.
I was like, oh.
I got that.
What do you get when you see a pair of heribals?
What?
And if you never want to see that reaction again,
let me introduce you to the man-scaped groin and go bundle.
Perfect for your little guy.
And no, I'm not talking about staff.
I'm talking about down there.
The bundle comes with the lawnmower 5.0 Ultra,
which is perfect for when you want a trim
without having to worry about nicks or cuts.
You're telling me I don't have to worry about nicks or cuts?
Mm-hmm.
And the bundle also comes with the handyman face shaver,
which get this is waterproof.
So clean up is a breeze.
And how cool is this magnetic blade cover?
It's so compact.
You can just throw it in your bag,
hit the road and use it whenever you need.
But wait, there's more.
With three different comb options,
one fixed length and two adjustable,
you have complete control over your hair length.
And did I mention it's wireless?
That means this wise.
None at all.
Plus, it's equipped with a dual LED spotlight
so you can groom with precision,
even in the darkest of corners.
For a grooming bundle that's smooth and simple,
head to manscape.com and use the promo code
YeahMad for 20% off your first order.
Plus, free international shipping.
So there you have it, legends.
The manscaped groin and go bundle featuring
the lawnmower 5.0 Ultra and the handyman face shaver.
You'll always be ready to show off your balls.
Try manscape today!
What's the difference between
yoghurt and Americans?
What?
Yogurt grows a culture if you leave it alone for 200 years.
Oh!
I'm going to buzz twice as sure as I'm on.
Have you heard the phrase Jesus take the will?
Yeah.
So I think only Christians can use
their really ugly God to say that.
Because if you say Muhammad take the will,
you're just talking to your Uber driver?
No!
Five stars with a joke in there.
Muhammad take the will!
Three stars.
I don't know why.
I thought it was going to turn into like a hijacked shirt.
Yeah, I love it.
Mm-hmm.
Oh!
Hi!
Hold it in.
That was...
Yuck.
It turned into like a fart.
How do you sign a rave in Ethiopia?
You nail a piece of toast to the ceiling.
I don't know about you being...
Oh my god.
Was that a laugh?
I didn't laugh at that.
Yeah.
That's the whole way I was going to laugh.
I only wish I thought of it.
Piece of toast.
Oh my god.
What should I not get hate for that though?
She's got a lot of factant on today.
It's a very true.
That melanin's looking strong.
So I um...
I took a date to the fish market.
Yeah, but she only sashimi as a friend.
LAUGHTER
Good, good.
I just see Mexico...
I know.
If this was an orange joke off,
I think I would have wanted to hear it out.
You would have wanted to.
No, that was good, guys.
Um...
I'm thinking of selling fragrance to introverts.
I'll need that.
Yeah, well it's called Leave Me The Fault, Collode.
LAUGHTER
That was good.
That's right.
LAUGHTER
Sorry.
You're not going to get up there.
You're going to be a fool.
Sorry.
You might make up today.
LAUGHTER
You want?
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, I'm going to get up.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
LAUGHTER
I have to do this thing where I have to just swallow it.
A little bit by little bit.
Very sexy.
Yes, yes.
A little bit.
LAUGHTER
That was more.
So the darling Alma got kicked out of the bar.
Yeah.
Yeah, they asked him to leave, but he said, nah, mustay.
LAUGHTER
What did Damon's brush their teeth with?
Helsinki.
That's clean.
LAUGHTER
I don't even think I get that myself.
I don't get it.
I don't know why I like it.
I think I've seen where he's going.
Like, that's sink.
Yeah, I get it.
Yeah, but I don't really get it.
We're the Damon's brush their teeth.
Helsinki.
OK.
Should I do another one?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm thankful that one, but...
LAUGHTER
We love you, Peyton.
We believe in you.
Fucking you.
Yeah, fuck me.
LAUGHTER
Oh my God.
Really?
LAUGHTER
Yeah, I'm gonna do it.
She needs it to fucking...
LAUGHTER
Where is he coming from?
It's an alcohol.
I feel like an Elmo right now.
An Elmo?
Like, tickle me Elmo.
Like red.
Oh, you're red, OK.
Asian Flash.
Oh, yeah.
Am I red?
No.
OK.
Mozilla.
LAUGHTER
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
It's getting on me.
You're gonna know, I think you...
LAUGHTER
It's the two guys first day.
It's the first day.
It started so fucking hoarse.
Yeah.
OK, what's the difference between raw ray and a bucket of shit?
The bucket.
LAUGHTER
I'm getting out of here, Joyce.
The very slow.
The slow.
That's not the average.
I'm canceling your only only fan subscription.
Don't lose so much money.
That $3 is coming back to me.
LAUGHTER
Oh!
Yeah.
A strip club opened near the school.
Right, and people were completely, right, completely, completely...
Are you getting nervous around me?
Oh, yeah.
So again, so again, so again.
That's a job, though.
OK.
So again, we really knew we loved you.
Yes.
Fuck, I'm quite angry with you.
You got a team here.
Team, team, team.
All right, so a strip club opened up near the school,
and people are complaining, right?
Because those kids are ruining our strip club experience.
LAUGHTER
No, it's damn kids.
The school's on the way there.
So the kids are in the strip club, so...
That's what Pat's always there.
LAUGHTER
Always running to Pat.
What do you think we're doing again?
The Irish is...
He's got damn sexy kids.
LAUGHTER
What did Trump say when Joe dropped out of the presidential race?
What did he say?
Bye, Dan!
LAUGHTER
Just like that.
Can you deal with Trump's accent?
He was gay.
Bye, he's gay.
He's old and he's gay.
LAUGHTER
Topical, Pat, and Topical.
Thank you.
LAUGHTER
Patents like, yeah, that was a pretty tropical joke.
I guess that was pretty tropical.
LAUGHTER
So that's...
Oh my god.
So you're cheers?
The tropics.
Um, 40-mouth disease.
Yeah.
More like 40-mouth, yes, please.
LAUGHTER
Please?
Hey, you crooks off.
Just walk forward and activate it.
LAUGHTER
Patents are really good.
That's really good.
That's a boost.
Oh my god.
Um...
How does a manipulator change light bulb?
How?
They don't. They use gas lighting.
How does a...
LAUGHTER
Sorry, sorry.
Patents being black-pum.
LAUGHTER
They normally go ahead and change lights on.
They're like, I'm gonna fix that and I just really didn't...
I don't know.
We love you.
I just want to be like you, Seth.
LAUGHTER
Oh my god.
Wow!
Do you know what it's called to practice tickling?
Mm-hmm.
A test tickle.
LAUGHTER
That's good.
I think it's the way it works.
I'm the army.
That's a test tickle.
Patents' balls.
I don't have balls!
Get out!
I've heard that hairie.
That's in shoes, the toilet coat.
Yeah, but...
What does a guy with a two-inch dick have for breakfast?
What do you have for breakfast, Pat?
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
Oh yeah, I mean, Ian had toast this morning.
How did you know? I actually did have toast this morning.
I had to rain if I was trying to...
LAUGHTER
Yeah!
That's it!
That's all that.
Let's drink it up.
We haven't got the answer, by the way.
Roaring interrupted, believe it or not.
LAUGHTER
That's a crazy brain repair.
So make me do a patting question.
OK.
Where are those kids?
Oh, I already need.
I broke up with a girl who wanted to go to the gym together.
I just couldn't see us working out.
LAUGHTER
What's cute?
Is cute that I broke up with the girl?
No, I don't know.
Yeah.
LAUGHTER
That's cute that you can work out together.
But you don't want to do that.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Um...
No, I didn't mean to do that.
I was just...
Thanks for a great guy.
Did you hear the one about the Chinese godfather?
He made them an offer they couldn't understand.
LAUGHTER
I understood it.
You understood it?
No, I understood it.
Not me.
You got the my daughter, Wendy!
LAUGHTER
That's a great...
I'm so glad I've got an origin about it.
It's a Mandarin.
LAUGHTER
That was a good joke, Kaded.
Thank you so much.
Thanks.
It's fun.
What do you call an Indian and a skip in?
What?
Ravagy.
Yeah!
That's a funny joke.
I didn't write that joke. I got TSC.
Yes, I did.
Ravagy.
We couldn't decide if we wanted to bury or cremate my grandpa.
So we just let him live.
LAUGHTER
That's good.
That could be it.
You did so good.
No, you did better.
No, I was so good.
Yeah!
This is actually like so priceless.
This is such a waste of paper.
Exactly.
It's the same to trees.
Oh man.
It is like...