To Targill's.
Alright, I think you're gonna want to go.
No!
Hello.
Guten Tag, Freyline!
Ha ha ha ha!
Yes.
You do be looking like a beautiful smettling.
You're gonna have a face.
You look great, man.
Cheese cobbler.
Oh, I don't think she's gentlemen now.
You see this baby rocked to go first?
Yeah, sure, why not?
See, this is a baby rock.
Yeah, wait, you go.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
What do...
What does peanut butter and strippers have in common?
They both spread for bread.
It's a good start.
Thank you.
Maybe guys.
Why can't you never get any painkillers in the jungle?
Why?
Because parrots eat a ball.
Ha ha!
Bring a spoon.
What type of a bird gives the best head?
A swallow.
Fuck.
mangoes.
You're a bottle-eak.
We didn't count me in the form of a cake with the racnitz.
That was really a bottle-up.
Form a cake with the racnitz.
I didn't.
Doesn't count.
I accidentally took my cats meds yesterday.
They're not us me out.
Go.
No, I did it! I did it!
She is to your face.
She is.
You as an Andrews pretty face.
All right.
What's the best thing about having sex with 28-year-olds?
Tell me.
There's 20 of them.
Cool.
There was a lot of my projects and things.
What's French and love's blood jobs?
What?
I know. I know.
That's what I'm doing.
You're me.
Oh.
What's up?
I'm talking to that not being a criminal.
I thought I was going to win this one for sure.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
The Darren Pooh.
The yoga bugger.
It's good.
What did you think I was?
I thought we were just f***ing us.
Well, but what did you think I was dressed as?
Me, apparently.
That is so funny.
That's how it is.
You ran. That's good.
She's the devos.
She is the devos.
She's the one.
She's really dressed down.
She is the sun.
She's so funny.
Oh my god.
No, no, no.
No, not on.
No, she's the one.
Why did the chicken cross the road?
To get to the idiot's house.
Knock, knock.
Knock.
Who's there?
The chicken!
You're an idiot.
You're a dead-set idiot.
This is so bad.
I loved it.
Are you going to this one?
Yeah, I'll try that one because that's like...
Really hitting it back with her today.
This is the cinnamon.
This one's got the cinnamon.
Oh my god.
Okay, that's a very full shot.
It's fine.
We just get cheese every time.
Look at that cheese every time.
I'm sitting too close to the staff and I was about to take something.
Really pervert.
What are you doing?
Smell like curry.
No, it's going to say...
Sam's legs look fucking fantastic.
You doing it?
Rub it on my hand.
Yeah.
You do that look great.
Pervert Abby is back.
You can't see them.
It's not funny.
Okay, go.
That was great.
Thank you.
You got this.
You're welcome.
This is going to ruin all the jokes coming up.
So let's get stuck into those, eh?
What would a Japanese foot have for dinner?
What?
Shushi.
It's good.
You don't like sushi?
No, likes sushi.
Shushi.
Yeah, sushi.
What do you call a guy with a small dick?
Please help.
Please be a killer.
Fuck.
Go back.
I said the same thing.
That was so funny.
Because it's not your turn Abby.
Do you want the punch?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's all right.
Just in.
Good?
Yeah.
Did I laugh?
Yeah, we both laughed.
And everyone laughed.
And there was a Joyce occasion.
Everyone had a great time.
You just filled the game out, then.
Who's it?
Yeah.
How does a frog fill when he breaks his foot?
I'm not happy.
We've got to get some fillers in there.
That's good.
Thank you.
All right.
There we go.
What would you do if you came across a tiger in the jungle?
Scream.
Apologize and rub it off.
If Matt came across a tiger in the jungle.
Yeah.
You're a tiger.
Tiger.
Tiger in the jungle.
Well structured.
The actual workers make sense.
If it came across a tiger.
If it came across a tiger, you know.
I can't hear a joke on me racist.
I don't get it.
I was there.
I got into a museum throughout New Hampshire.
I got into a museum.
To the table.
All right.
I think you're going to have to go.
Yeah.
It's really really exciting.
Nothing around here.
No.
Yeah.
What's the rush?
I don't know.
I don't want to do the short that we probably shouldn't just done.
How do you circumcise a hillbilly?
Oh.
You know.
Maybe.
Kiki's sister, the male.
I've heard it as well.
I was just out of the sound.
We did it.
I was holding it out.
We're editing that.
We've done it.
I'm fucking Saturday there.
Saturday there.
Did I do that joke?
No.
I did that joke.
But I laughed at that joke.
I can't go on.
Shut up the fuck up lady Gaga.
Shut up.
Lady Gaga.
All right.
Okay.
What Sam's least favourite Italian dessert?
Like me?
You.
Sam.
What is your least favourite Italian dessert?
I hate all pasta.
I don't know.
Oh, it's...
Are in Cheney?
I don't like that either.
Let me say that.
Let me say the joke one more time for Samantha.
Okay?
We're going to really dive into this one.
Samantha.
What is your least favourite Italian dessert?
Can I say wine?
You're going to get close to it.
You can't fare enough for her.
Like the lemon joke.
Yeah, anyway.
We're going to switch the joke up.
Sam's least favourite Italian dessert is...
...Tur-Tur-Tur-Machoux.
Tur-Tur-Machoux.
She doesn't like the word, she doesn't like it.
I'm looking...
Come on man!
I just sat there for fucking weeks!
Coming up with this joke takes you guys two days!
That's the best of God!
Like a tear in the shoe.
Yeah, yeah.
It's half-hage for that one.
Because you're laughing and not...
I'm spitting into your mouth.
You do it.
What?
It's my son.
You want to feed him?
I want to feed him.
You're telling me to feed him.
You better help me.
No, they're not.
I have a suit of milk.
We're going to be doing this next half completely blind.
You're going to have to feed him.
I'm going to have to feed him.
You guys see him?
Now I'm good, I'm good, I'm good.
I'm going to have to feed him.
You've got to feed him.
Go on, I'm gonna feed him.
I'm going to have to feed him.
Go on, follow me.
All right, follow me.
I have to feed him.
This is great content guys.
Keep it up, keep it up.
We're going great.
Where are we at this one?
Okay, we're good.
We're good.
Yeah, I'm the boy.
What did the American foot send the terrorist foot?
Bissletoe.
Oh, terrorist foot.
It actually showed up.
It's so dark.
The Americans are the terrorists.
It's a terror to me.
Let me sort of talk.
Terrorist foot.
What are you good people?
It locked us where I keep a dune.
I don't care.
I don't care anymore.
Who cares?
We got one.
We're going through all these jokes.
Now we don't give them off.
What happened?
What do you call a nurse with dirty knees?
Go.
The head nurse.
What are you rushing me?
Oh, the fucking nurse.
We're good.
What's that up?
We're doing this area.
It was a very funny one.
Head nurse.
Because she gave him head and she's a nurse.
Getting him knees.
Rusted up.
Suck in some f***ing.
That's great.
Put in some catheters and f***ing suck it them off.
I love it.
What else we got?
Anyway, we're going back to this.
All right.
It's a man for?
I can't take you seriously.
You can't take me seriously because we're being serious.
I hear that people with a foot fetish have a highly active socks life.
How's your socks life going, Sammy?
I'm actually about to...
No, I don't know.
Surely it's terrific.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's get on with it.
I need to defeat you.
These socks.
You wearing shoes today?
Why?
Okay, go.
That socked.
That's way better.
That was good, Matt. That was great.
Thank you, Seth. I love you.
Did you eat laughing at any of that?
No.
Did you eat laughing at that?
You really toe-dazzled that one.
Oh, jeez to you.
I can go, go, go, go, go.
Okay.
What do you get when you jingle a man's balls?
When you jingle a man's balls?
Fuck.
A white Christmas.
Jingle bell, jingle bell, jingle bell.
Jingle bell ring, jingle bell.
Come on.
I'm laughing.
In the frosty air.
Um.
I'm going to, can I do one that, that,
can I do one that wasn't allowed,
like that hasn't been shown in a previous one?
Yeah.
Okay, but it's the first time you've
hit it or a,
hit it.
Who's that being beaten?
Matt Scott, Matt Scott, the brain capacity of a middle schooler.
You guys, I'm not a middle schooler.
I need a schooler.
No.
Why, I'm just going to take these.
I took mine.
Oh, sick.
Why does the Norwegian Navy put barcodes on their ships?
It's been done.
I'm never.
The Norwegian Army has been done.
I never been to say that in the whole time we've been to.
Why you do that, buddy?
Yeah, I do.
But like, you just said on me.
Yeah, but there's also been so many different ones being read on them.
That's the only one you've ever tried on the whole time.
What does a burnt pizza, a pregnant woman,
and a frozen beer having common?
I'm waiting.
Are you meant to say what?
Oh, um.
What?
Someone forgot to pull it out in time.
Go.
Oh, I got you.
One, two, three, four, five, six, six, six, six, six, six, six, six.
I can't imitate it.
You won't hear it.
God bless America.
That's a long now.
Awesome.
Oh, no.
Good job.
I got political at the end.
Yeah.
That's a wrong.
Oh, shit.