I don't answer this question if you don't want to matter.
But I have...
I don't know why you brought this up, but I did hear you discuss...
that you had an extraordinary disagreement with your wife about yourself.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
By myself, you mean...
Yes.
Oh.
Listen, I've...
Oh, this story. I do not know this...
Listen with interest.
Well...
One night, as you do, we were talking about stuff.
I don't...
And I just had no interest in...
and of course, being circumcised, I said...
They were chatting. They're married.
They're married. They're allowed.
And she said...
She said...
You're not circumcised?
I said, what do you mean?
You've only known me a few...
All my life, I remember my mother telling me why,
because it was fashionable at the time.
She said, you're not circumcised.
I said, that's ridiculous.
I should know if I'm circumcised.
Of course I am.
End of conversation.
But the next day, I happened to be seeing my doctor...
Are you okay?
I was seeing my doctor for my annual physical, of course.
So...
Well, he was down there.
I said, it's getting dark, by the way,
of...
Um...
That my wife and I had a little disagreement.
I am circumcised, I'm not, because she says I'm not.
And he goes...
Not...
He said, no, no, no, it's not possible.
So he looked down again and he said, hey, I'm Jewish.
I know the difference.
That is a bizarre story.
That is...
You're not Jewish.
That is a bizarre story.
Oh, God.
I have grandchildren.
You're gonna have to change your Facebook status, no?
Yes.
No more beef stew.
Well, there's more beef stew.
Oh!
Oh.
You born in a way?
I was born in Hawaii.
You lived there.
It's a school, but I did a lot of my growing up there.
So, yeah, so it was a...
I don't know. I don't think, no.
I did.
No, I told you.
I told you.
I told you for years, I've always said I was...
But when we were there, you gave me a big speech like,
this is my land, I started.
I thought, I thought, I thought, I thought, I thought,
I thought, I thought, I thought, I thought, yeah.
I'm sure that was that.
Now, I'm a sudden stand-fran.
I was stand-fran, then I transferred.
When we were there, you gave me a very...
Like, spiritual speech about how it all started.
I get my...
I held you over, it's clear.
I didn't think so, man.
It's clear, it's clear.
This is a clip where I was born and my mother didn't mean it.
This is the problem.
Yes.
You're trying to be respectful.
Hawaii was beautiful.
Beautiful.
You know, mountainside and lushness
and we shot in this beautiful place called Kuloh Ranch
where a drastic park, the original dress park
was shot and the ones after that as well.
And it was just amazing.
But you didn't like it, Kevin?
He hated it.
No, this is the problem.
I didn't like it at all.
I mean, outside of the spiritual grounds
that you took me to, and I swore,
you even sung a song.
You were like...
Yeah, I'm not just saying that.
I remember.
I said, we'll talk about it later.
We'll talk about it later.
This song, you were like,
you were like,
Kuloh Matana.
That's how the thing was.
The original.
So, did you bring your medals with you?
No.
We did.
All of them might be wearing them.
Oh, no, they're just casually in the back pockets.
Do they go up there?
No, these are proper, proper, a little bit medals.
Wow.
Married if you've seen an Olympic medal.
I actually did.
It was a French people's victory.
Or was it a French people's victory?
Oh, the French got gold.
Oh, I'm going to go.
I'm going to have to go.
Toad, I'm going to go.
Is there anyone in Ireland who hasn't seen those medals?
They look like they've been around the block, those medals.
Yeah.
They're fairly casual, yeah.
And of course, Michael, down in Kulohani,
word must have reached you off the Adoniver.
Oh, for sure.
I mean, I wasn't in Kulohani at the time,
but everybody knew about it.
That's for sure, yeah.
And Marion, watching that clip
and that could you understand the accents?
Nothing, not a word.
I understood since.
Oh.
That's what I was saying.
I was like, I want to move myself with Michael.
It is take carry accent.
LAUGHTER
So, listen.
It is.
Because people love the interviews you did during the Olympics.
But you guys knew you were being funny while you were doing the interviews.
I don't know.
No, I think it was funny because it would be in themselves.
Yeah.
Well, to be fair, we weren't trying to do interviews.
We weren't trying to do interviews, like, but...
You just...
It's trying to happen now, we're like...
You did seem very happy to be in Rio.
Oh, it's quite serious about the whole situation,
all right? Every time we talk, it's the truth, like.
Yeah.
LAUGHTER
And then I don't understand, like, people ask us these questions
all the time after races that just so happened,
they put a camera in front of us in Rio.
I don't know.
You want to silver medals, or something, everyone will be there.
But the great thing is, Ireland doesn't ever want any medal in rowing before.
Have they?
No, it's all in the Olympics.
No, they have a few World Championship titles.
All right, but it's the first Olympic medal, yeah.
Woo-hoo!
APPLAUSE
Very good.
And the interview where you talked about your approach to the race.
The phrase that you used in that, so explain to the people what you said in that.
Do you know what I'm going to say?
About going A to B fast, you can.
Yeah.
It's a fairly simple sport, like.
LAUGHTER
Does it start like a finish line?
You're going to complicate it, you're going to complicate it.
People do complicate it, like.
Your men says go out to start and there's a hooter at the finish, and you go to the...
Go out to the hooter, and...
Go what you should like.
LAUGHTER
Traveling, this is based on your life.
I mean, this is things...
Yeah.
I mean...
LAUGHTER
Looosely, Crayham.
No, but things like, isn't the washing machine that happened to you?
What?
The washing.
You were very hungover.
Oh.
Yeah.
LAUGHTER
No, tell Tony Foster, that story.
All that stories are really cool, though, Grail.
When I was teaching, which is what this show is based on, I went home one weekend,
and I was in my 30s.
I was probably 33 years of age.
I went home to see my mother, and then I went back.
And while I was at home, my mother did my washing for me, because I was only 33.
LAUGHTER
And I went back.
And on the Sunday night, I got really drunk, and then I went for a curry.
And then the next day I went into school.
LAUGHTER
I'm going to.
I went into school, and it was a school in Slau, and it was quite a rough school,
but they had a really brilliant hearing impaired department, so they were hearing impaired kids who,
you know, struggled.
They were really looked after in the school.
Anyway, I was really hungover.
I went there, and at that break time, I felt really uncomfortable.
I thought something's not right, you know?
So I went to the toilet, and I pulled my trousers down, and some of my mother's knickers had got...
LAUGHTER
..I got mixed up in the wash, you know.
And I was wearing my mother's underwear.
LAUGHTER
And I went, oh, god, no!
Oh, I remember going, oh, you loser.
This is such a low point, you fucking loser.
LAUGHTER
And then...
The curry and the booze...
The curry and the booze kicked in from the night before.
LAUGHTER
So I...
I did like a fecal Jackson Pollock.
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
And I started...
I started going, oh, god, not this!
Not this as well!
Oh, Jesus!
So I cleaned myself up, and I pulled my mother's pants back there.
And I went back into the classroom,
and I saw one of the hearing impaired kids just looking at me like this.
And that's when I remembered that I had a microphone directly.
LAUGHTER
I can't see.
There you go.
Here we go.
LAUGHTER
A lot of youngsters, they, you know, they revere you, so they look to you.
But the other thing you inspire is impressions, people doing impressions.
Now, when people do impressions of you, is it like sort of nails on a chalkboard
or do you kind of enjoy it?
No, I kind of enjoy it, especially if they do it well.
LAUGHTER
So, no, it's great.
I love it.
I only ask!
LAUGHTER
No, because...
Because any hiddlestoners watching will know.
Tom Hiddleston does impressions.
You do a lot of impressions, so who is in your canon?
It's an expression of admiration, just to be clear.
So I do impressions of people that I admire, and I sort of listen to them.
I get the first time I did an impression that anyone was aware of.
I was just telling a story about Midnight in Paris, the Woody Allen film I was in.
And how I never had the whole script, and I thought it was set in the 20s.
And I turned up and I bumped into Owen Wilson.
He didn't look like he was in the 20s at all.
And I said to him, I said,
so wait, how on, who are you playing?
Because I'm playing F-Scope Fitzgerald, and I know Corey Stolz playing on his hamming way,
and we're all playing figures of history, and he went,
oh, no, no, no, no.
I'm from now. I go back in Paris.
There's a time machine, you know?
It's kind of cool, and it's kind of wooding,
and you just kind of... it's kind of awesome.
LAUGHTER
Great job!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
I've done... I've done... I mean...
I've done... I've been made to the impressors of my fellow Avengers.
I think everyone does an impression of Christopher Walken,
because he's such an easy kind of...
You know, I feel like what this show needs is more cowbell...
depends on what you like me to say.
Basically, there's no punctuation.
And anything that comes out of my mouth...
LAUGHTER AND APPLAUSE
And I go...
APPLAUSE
I know whole pages of heat.
You surprised me.
LAUGHTER
So, there's a scene in the middle of the film, which you'll be familiar with.
You were there.
LAUGHTER
The one person you don't need to explain is you.
So, look, there's...
LAUGHTER
He remembers.
You're very good in this film.
Did you see it in the middle of the film, which is...
Because Al Pacino and Robert are in the middle.
LAUGHTER
Sorry about that.
They're separated, like a great thriller.
They're separated from... for the entire film, and they meet twice
once at the end of once in the middle.
And it takes place at a restaurant, L.A.
It's a great scene. It's one of the great pieces of screen acting.
You can hope to watch. There it is. It's a picture of it.
It's like a... It's a mutual recognition of each other.
Anyway, so there's a bit where they...
They sit and have coffee and have tea and talk about stuff.
I'm going on, I apologize.
Anyway, so Al Pacino, at one point...
Al Pacino says this. He goes...
So...
LAUGHTER
We're sitting here, like a couple of regular fellas.
I mean...
You do what you do.
I do what I got to do...
If I'm there...
And I got to put you away.
I won't like it.
But if it's between you and some poor bastard
who his wife is going to turn into a widow,
brother, you are going down.
LAUGHTER
And then...
And then Michael Mancott's back to the esteemed gentleman
at the end of the sofa.
LAUGHTER
What if you do got me boxed in?
I'm not going to put you down.
I'm even face to face.
Yeah.
But I will not hesitate.
Not for a second.
That's my...
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
This is so...
This is so meta.
I feel like I've gone into a parallel universe where...
You were playing Gullisport. Yes, I played that.
No, that's great.
I do that present of Ken Brown.
That's my favourite scene. Was he your favourite scene?
Yeah. It's a good...
LAUGHTER
No, no, but my favourite scene that was written before,
not because of...
I'm doing it, but I'm just my favourite scene written and the film.
You know, that's...
It's a great piece of writing.
It feels like it plays in two singles, in a way.
Like, just...
Yeah.
And it's like the most beautiful game of tennis.
Did you do lots of takes?
I forget how many takes we did.
I don't think we did more than...
5 to 8 or 9 at the moment.
Maybe, maybe, or less.
You talk about your dreams and your life.
LAUGHTER
It's so great. It's so great.
There's another bit where you go.
LAUGHTER
You say, he says...
He says, Puccino says,
So you never wanted a regular type of life.
And...
Bob, may I call you Bob?
Yeah.
Bob says, what's that?
Bob accused of ball games?
Yeah.
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
And then, Kylia, obviously your mother loves you
because you heard her daughter.
Yeah.
But she is actually a fan as well.
You know, we don't quite know.
It's...
I know she is...
Oh, goodness, right.
So, my...
One day my mum came to set on the Star Wars set.
And I was getting this thing called Cyber-Scanned,
which is where you stand in this kind of loads of cameras
and they kind of take your form
and put you into a computer and make a toy
or some sort of merchandise or your face on a cushion.
LAUGHTER
And so...
I go off and do this and I come back and mums
like I've made a great friend.
I'm really in this lovely, excellent.
And she likes the merchandise, you know,
director of all of Star Wars or something.
And I'm like, well, I'll say, you're very impressive.
And then, before I know it, what comes in the post,
he's loads of cushions.
LAUGHTER
My face on it.
So...
My own mum, I guess, she gets a seared a fair amount, you know.
But apparently, it's not enough, so...
LAUGHTER
I was kind of blown away at how much merchandise there is.
Yes, it's all...
And it's just the beginning.
It was like the pre-murchin' dyes.
Not even the real stuff is out yet.
And my mum has all of it.
And it doesn't have that the doll yet, so...
Look, this is so weird.
Is this in your flat or her house?
Yes, for sure.
Okay, so basically, she'll be really funny
if I came home and it was everywhere in my...
OK, so this is...
This is...
Is this Amelia's actual bedroom?
Well...
LAUGHTER
I love you, girl!
I was like a joke, and then...
And then...
Oh, and then...
Oh, my goodness.
We found the photo, but it's not like that now.
That's what I'm saying.
There was another reason why I'm saying...
You took a first date back to that.
Yeah.
Come on in.
I just think this little thing won't it?
I don't have a CV.
I just have a bedroom.
But this is cool, though.
So your mother, a big fan, but...
Yeah.
Brad Pitt, also a great big fan.
That was the best night of my life.
Yes.
I'm happy.
Tell the story quickly.
We've got a feeling of doing...
Yeah, there's a duvet.
We're only here.
She's...
I'm not a slipper.
No, yeah.
It was this auction thing that happened, and I...
They called me and said, do you want to...
Do you want to auction something off, like maybe sort of an experience
watching the show with you or something?
And I was like, OK, it's lovely.
It's great for charity.
Yeah.
It'll be for some...
You know, something.
Yeah.
And it'll be fine.
Anyway, so I get there.
It's a good thing.
It'll be a good thing.
I get there, and it's basically like this...
It's the Oscars.
There's so many celebrities in this room,
and suddenly remember that I said that I would auction something off,
and so the fear grows.
So I was petrified, absolute petrified.
And then the person who's a table I was on is a friend,
and he was being very kind and kind of put the paddle up,
and I was like, thanks very much.
That's very sweet.
That'll be that.
And then someone else's paddle up, went up across the other side of the room,
and I didn't really know, and then suddenly it was sort of becoming a bit of money,
and I was kind of thinking, oh, this is absolutely mental,
and someone went, it's Brad Pitt, and I was like, oh...
I'm like, you're free.
Yeah, exactly.
And I look over to the room, and he's got his paddle up.
Brad's paddle.
Oh, did he experience?
No, not quite.
Well, it didn't work out, because the person who's friend who's my friend,
I think it was probably all set up.
The person who was my friend ended up doing the highest bid.
Boo!
My friend.
But yeah, I just kind of looked over with just the most insane,
emoji heart eyes being like, this is just the greatest moment of my life.