What's the difference between Iron Man and Iron Woman?
One's a superhero, one's a command.
Oh, thanks, guys.
Oh, no.
OK.
Hi.
Hello.
OK, Karen.
Come in there.
It's a star.
That's not it.
Yeah, no? You're good.
They don't pay attention. We're fine.
And I think we've started.
One whole.
One whole. OK.
Um, says paper rock or do you have a preference?
Says paper rock.
OK.
All right. You're up and asking.
I'm fair.
Don't lie, probably.
Fist me.
OK.
I'm so good. Glucinators.
It's not going to go well with it.
That's good. That's good. Keep that energy up.
No.
Um, what do anniversaries, the toilet bowl,
and the clitoris all have in common?
What?
Men usually miss them all.
Oh, you can't look at me.
Can't look at me as if you said.
Now, getting you so you don't look at me.
Shall I be in your...
You're laughing.
No.
See me in the back.
All right.
Good start.
Yeah.
One chicken.
It cannot pause it either.
Stop laughing at me.
Are you a virgin?
Shut up.
Jeez.
Yep.
Did you hear about the guy who dipped his nuts?
Oh, no.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, had me in nuts.
I don't know whether to try the turkey again or just leave it.
I try to get it.
OK, because I already fucked it.
That's what he was right.
Right.
OK, get it.
OK.
Did you hear about the guy who dipped his balls in glitter?
Pretty nuts, eh?
It's not even good.
This is a pretty...
Yeah.
This is a pretty nuts.
Never looked at anyone.
Oh, pretty.
Hmm.
Ah.
What do both men and public toilets have in common?
What?
They're both either busy or full of shit.
I hope this is your humour, because I really kind of tailor it.
This is all of these...
Men hating men.
Does that work?
Like, men hating men kind of things?
Fuck off.
Give me the crack, anyway.
We have literally one minute in.
And...
Oh, this is...
Oh, fuck.
It's bad.
Cheers.
What's the difference between my dad and my dog?
I'm like a dad now.
I don't know.
My dog returned home after going for a walk.
Oh.
It's good.
No, I made it in me.
He said that I was gay.
Did that story?
Fuck.
I don't know what dad is going to stop talking.
No, he genuinely did.
My dad met, and was like,
So what's your sexuality?
What even did this?
And Matt was like, I'm a big old question mark.
Yeah, I'll say that, yeah.
It's like...
We're going to come in now.
These backstories are funny even in the job.
We'll get through one joke soon.
I think I need to like, like, ask my big son, is there a cannot...
Hey, what do you call a man with half a brain?
Matt?
A gifted man.
Matt.
I also said not.
Oh.
Did I laugh at that too?
I don't know.
No, you definitely did.
Yeah, you kept the gathering on.
Yeah.
You get to it?
I don't get it.
The man with half a brain is like quite intelligent for a man.
Just like that.
Oh, gosh.
I'm not sure.
Right.
Do you know why birds fly south in the winter?
Because it's too cold to walk.
I'm doing genuine real dad jokes this time.
Apparently that's not the vibe.
You should think funny one.
Thanks.
Sorry, I don't have a prison sentence to use for humour.
Um...
What's it?
You know what I'd say that and then slink back in the chair
and put the studies on a bit out of your ears?
Well, what's the difference between Iron Man and Iron Woman?
One's a superhero, one's a command.
I really like that one.
That's great.
I really find cocaine jokes funny.
But occasionally a one-liner does make me snort.
It's good one, I really like that one.
I really like that one.
Fuck off!
Oh, Jesus.
What's the score on this one, me?
It's just five.
It's five.
That's losing.
No, I think I'm losing.
No, no.
What do you call an Aussie gaslighting woman?
What?
Abby, you never said toy.
And you backed her up.
You were a gaslighter bitch as well.
You could've used gaslighter and Aussie bitches.
No, no.
No, okay, but...
I questioned it and I was like, did I say toy?
Because I wasn't sure.
And then she said I did.
Or her too.
You never said it.
I think they edited it out.
I'm really sorry.
You were right.
No, I want to see the raw footage.
I want to see the raw and edited footage.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I was at my boss's funeral, kneeling next to the coffin,
when I got removed from the funeral.
Apparently, whispering,
who's thinking outside the box now, Gary,
isn't funeral appropriate.
Why women's baseball game is dangerous?
Why?
Because pictures be crazy.
I like them.
That's good.
Yeah.
I have been looking for my exes killer for years.
Been old to it.
I didn't get that one.
Still thinking about the pictures be crazy.
Can you do it again for me, please?
I've been looking for my exes killer for years.
But...
What's you?
No?
I'm not listening.
It's the understanding.
Yeah.
Oh, he did.
Yeah, I did.
Why is it so hard to argue with a woman that's not wearing a bra?
It's already made two really good points.
We just did him to make him say.
I meant to discline him.
I don't even likeupbeat picture.
I wasn't trying to journal with that contract.
That was big thing, devil.
I forget about that.
I forgot about that.
It was interesting.
And now I will tell you an interesting story.
Bucket gardening?"
I haven't known this story for a long time,
Ah.
Did you hear about the surgeon who was five the other day?
No.
Uh, turns out the weight or man's heart is not through his stomach.
Does it go on?
Thanks.
What are the four words which are sure?
Sorry.
That was a cough.
That was a cough. That was a cough.
It was a cough.
Ah.
Fuck that. Jesus.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Very sorry.
Okay, where are we at?
You're probably...
Yeah.
One of four words which are sure,
fire away to demolish your man's ego.
Not your dick, small?
I'm cute.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Is it in yet?
Hmm. Same point.
No.
Oh, why do you know a fan's head of bars and bars?
Tell the joke, yeah, I got it.
His mat's barred from all bars.
That's not actually the punchline.
I don't know why I think that's...
It's mean.
Oh, I'm going to say the game.
I'll have the shocks at last.
It's mean.
Mean widget.
Back.
Ready.
Why do you never find them in bars?
Just wait for the chorus.
The peanut gallery room.
Hmm.
Yeah, say the joke again for him.
I want to hear the end of that.
Why do you never find petafiles and bars?
Oh, yeah.
Terrible place to pick up a date.
Hmm.
One big difference between men and women is that when women say
smell this, it usually smells nice.
Smell it.
It's a smell.
I'm so sorry.
Did you just say smell my finger?
Yeah. It's pour my finger.
The joke was about smelly.
Yeah, I know. But why would I smell your finger?
It's not a bad one.
You're not a bad one.
Yeah, you're not a bad one.
Yeah, it's not a bad one.
What's this call?
10.
Oh, so we've already finished.
Okay.
Just finish the bottle while you're out of it.
Six again, big boy.
Let's get.
Big boy.
You're so sorry.
I'm sorry.
So you're not like you were joking up here.
That one is not like you were just me joking up.
No, I'm not.
I'm not.
They'll tell you what, Andrew.
When we get to rent, we'll have a little joke off.
joke off?
Can't be.
I'm down.
Yeah.
Joke off?
I'm going to be black.
You're not already black?
I am.
What is 6.9?
Going.
A good thing, ruined by a period.
Mm-hmm.
Damn it!
The paint on the gallery makes it very difficult.
Mm-hmm.
I guess that's the point.
We have none.
Tee.
So sorry. Is your official name a killer of the girl?
No.
Is the most I've loved in any episode ever.
Mm.
What's the difference between an apple and an orphan?
You've done this one and an apple gets picked.
That is correct.
You've done it before yourself, man.
Yeah, it was really your joke.
You did it with Sambia, even a remembering.
I see.
Is that dark?
We...
Okay, what I got, what I got, what I got.
You just...
Okay.
What's the difference?
Oh my.
I just need a joke and three...
You did this already.
I can't!
You can't take a joke.
I can't.
But you take three cups.
You're not gonna do that.
I can't do that.
Abbie, what?
No!
Alright, trust me out.
Thanks.
I did the couch, the day from first shot.
Look at that.
Dude, we have to use the bottle of wine.
Love you.
I don't think I've ever laughed up much in one of these.
Yeah.