What's a gal's favorite number?
You tell me.
16.
Because she gets 8 twice.
Hey!
I got her.
Friend.
I've won!
Alright, south before they start.
I've got Matt.
I bet you a bottle of Patron.
Matt wins.
You're an idiot.
I'm Go Cat.
Yeah!
That's good.
Alright.
Have you watched yet, Matt?
Don't f*** this up, Matt.
There's a bottle on the line.
So you haven't watched my past performances?
Poor remembered them.
Because I don't know.
Um, scissors paper rock.
Alright, yes.
It's that time again.
Okay, scissors paper rock.
That was the quickest one.
What do you want to give us?
I'll go first.
What is Mickey Mouse's favorite sport?
What?
Mini golf.
Cute.
Yes.
That was a warm up.
OK?
I'll do warm up when it's about fun.
Alright.
Alright, what's the difference between me and your eight-n-a-dew?
Who?
What?
I came home from camp.
F***!
This dude, what the f***?
Yeah, heavy head.
Catherine!
I've got faith in you, Matt.
I've got faith.
Hey, Kat.
Hey.
Did you hear about the German domestic violence victim?
I did not.
He Hitler.
A bit of a strong laugh, though.
That's fine.
Alright, let's lean into the Hitler jokes.
Um.
Mmm.
That's favorite.
Where did Sally go during the bombing?
F***!
Sally's dead, bro.
Well, it's done a rough job.
Oh, sh**, it's done a rough job.
It was just a...
Come, come, come, come.
Oh, OK, OK.
Do the joke, do the joke.
Alright.
I'm going to the next one.
How do you do that?
Oh, sorry.
I'm going to get in the office.
Come, come, come.
Oh, okay.
Do the joke, do the joke.
All right.
Where did Celeco join the boving?
Everywhere.
Oh.
That only can't says one.
It does.
I called it, I called it early.
But not the punchline.
Just that shit.
No, just the dead part.
Dead part.
Dead, dead, dead, dead.
Yeah, yes, that's right.
Yeah.
Poois, Celeco.
What do the LGBT people and scoliosis have in common?
None of them are straight.
Yeah.
I like that one.
Correct.
Why does an Ethiopian baby cry?
We wouldn't be crying.
What?
It's having a midlife crisis.
So?
What is it, so many?
Oh my god.
It's so many.
It's so many!
I don't know if that was a laugh.
It doesn't.
When you cross those a laugh, that was a laugh.
No.
That was a laugh.
Laugh.
What is a shark and a computer happen common?
I don't know.
Megabytes.
Yeah, nice.
And if you wanted to download some megabytes safely and secretively, then Surfshark VPN,
the sponsor of today's video is for you.
Surfshark VPN will allow you access to the internet across the globe for any website
that you curious catfishes desire.
Whether it's your fave shows, gaming, or getting access to the internet, you can't get
in your country by switching your IP address to one of the 3200 plus servers in 100 countries.
Surfshark VPN basically hides you from being monitored.
Surfshark will allow you to connect to as many devices as you want under the one account.
So dive into Surfshark today.
Will you get 30 days money back guarantee?
And full custom support.
And don't forget to use the promo code YeahBadToCheckout.
Also get yourself four months for free.
So click the link in the description down below.
Or you can use the QR code, swimming just here.
Surfshark VPN baby!
Yee!
This is...
...hopeful...well.
Oh, hey!
Cat.
So.
Julian Assange had two children with his loyal while in exile.
I realized this gave new meaning to the words pro bono.
Yeah.
I like that.
Thank you.
Because it was a bono.
It was a bono.
I love bono stuff.
Um, why didn't Anne Frank finish her diary?
Dead.
Concentration problems.
Oh, that's...
Oh, my God.
That's so good.
That was a...
...
She did it.
Well, I can smell this fireball and it's so yucky.
I am...
...
That was a good one.
Oh, what was a good one?
Except for my fingering.
I'm...
...
Oh!
Click!
Oh no!
That's messed up.
That doesn't ask me.
You'll go?
Yep.
Cool.
So I got kicked out of the hospital one time.
Apparently, the sign for Stroke patients here
meant something totally different.
Hi, that was a good one.
To get that one, she's jerking them off.
Yeah, I get it.
Never done it, but I get it.
The...
Hahahaha!
Anel sex is a lot like Brussels sprouts.
If you had it as a child, you weren't like it as an adult.
Hahahaha!
Oh my god!
I don't know, I'm getting older.
I think Anel's pretty good.
Your job?
Yeah, I like Brussels sprouts.
Hahahaha!
Okay, okay, okay.
Um, what do you do when you finish a magazine at school?
Yeah.
You reload.
Oh!
Hahahaha!
Yes!
I think that one might get caught!
Hahahaha!
It's alright, we'll try it.
Hopefully...
I'm fast off there.
Hahahaha!
I don't know what I'm doing.
I wouldn't say that you had a school zoned!
Hey, I think you might have to get a school zoned!
That was a huge shit.
How much lube does it take to have Anel sex?
A butt load.
Hahahaha!
That's a good one.
Yeah, that one.
So that is...
Yeah.
What do you call Anel sex on an airplane?
High as fuck!
Hahahaha!
I'm sorry!
You okay?
I'm really sorry a bit.
They were all just Anel jokes from...
I'm sorry!
They were all just Anel jokes!
Do not apologize.
It's alright Matt, I was hoping that you would come from behind.
I'm here!
It is...
It's a hard child.
Oh yeah, did it.
Um, why is it so hard to argue as a woman who's not wearing a bra?
Why?
She's already made two great points.
Hmm.
Oh, what's that?
That was the one I didn't know I did that.
I don't know!
Bro!
It's not funny!
You did slow!
I said his most...
His most deepest darkest thoughts.
Just some...
As soon as you don't know that, go see Protector Pay.
You're the only one I've ever seen.
I keep down all I did to those crazy...
I don't know why I did that.
Oh, actually I got some other ones I don't...
I can't mix it up.
Did you hear about the constipated cast?
There you go.
He just couldn't budge it!
Where was it?
What was that?
Bro, he's having such a great life now.
Sad against that again.
How did you hear about the constipated accountant?
I don't know why that's funny.
He just couldn't budge it.
Let's use the steaming organic.
Clush, Clush.
There I go.
Oh, fuck you, man!
So there's only B word that you should call women as beautiful?
This bitch is love when you call them beautiful.
Go ahead and sing.
She's a bit bitch.
That's a bit of a basketball.
That's good.
I went bird watching with this chick.
And there's just something about the way she was counting the birds.
She was like,
Hawk 1.
Hawk 2!
Yes!
I wrote that.
Prove it.
The spellings wrong in this joke.
No one knew.
No one knew how to spell it.
The best one is he wrote another one.
And it was Hawk 3.
I got you one ready.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, because a lot.
It's supposed to not laugh, man.
What's the difference between a female farmer and Hitler's girlfriend?
One bails her hay and the other hails her bag.
Thank you.
What do you call a large group of men who recently found out they've been cheated on?
I don't know.
A fluster cuck.
Yeah.
Yeah, I love them.
Like a clusterfuck?
No, I get it.
Yeah, it's like...
He's crying.
I'm fine.
I'm really trying.
Hold it in, baby.
Or we'll just get better than we try to explain the matter.
No.
Okay, what?
How do you embarrass not?
You're what we're how?
We are.
We're what we're where.
You.
Who is going on?
This is the worst fag I've ever met.
Hey, Kate.
Kate.
Wait, do you think it's fair to say that?
There's no way, but it is.
There's no way.
He doesn't know who he's versus.
Hey, Patrick.
Poor him.
A version of poor him.
Poor him, right?
This one's for my gaming friends out there in the world.
Hopefully this lands.
My gamers.
Why can't you have sex after playing Assassin's Creed?
Oh, why?
Because you be soft.
Oh, I don't get it.
No one's going to fuck you because you're playing Assassin's Creed.
No.
You're so important today.
Do you know why you shouldn't go for a cheap circumcision?
What?
You see, nothing but a rip-off.
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
What is an alternative?
What is an alternative term for anal bleaching?
A changing your ring term?
What's the score?
Two in the score!
Fuck!
See, I got one, but it's not enough!
Alright.
Now it's next five.
What do you get if you stuffed your hand up a gypsy's
where she is on her period?
What?
Your palm is red.
Oh my god!
Why is he f**king excited to join us?
That'll be my favourite joke, tell her what else is.
That wins!
Wow!
Yeah!
Yeah, Kat!
That was such a good joke!
Yeah, that last joke is definitely worth more than one point.
That deserves a win at the end.
Is that an Indian exit?
It's what he was missing!
Yeah, I got Kat!
He could say I'm a IOU bottle.