The big thing fans are of course is fan art and Sarah Pasco I know you have had that accolade of people sending you fan art.
I mean get one piece and I think fan art is a strong word.
We've got to pick it should we see it first?
Yes, okay, so it's me.
Actually, it's worth saying that it's all of you.
It's all of me.
It is what this is the fan art of Sarah Pasco.
Now the reason I think fan art is a very loose term is I was given this as a gig in lieu of payment.
I just want to brag about my career.
Yeah.
Well.
But that's because the guy who ran the gig had spent too much at the bar to pay me.
So he painted that, yes.
After being at the bar.
Of me.
What are those bits?
I just think they're just free biscuits.
I'm not so something.
You've been sent pictures of people who tattooed your face on their body.
Oh, no, I'm not there yet.
You got one day.
Yeah.
I get them in my Twitter feed all the time.
It's guys with a whole cab, the cash or a picture of jewels on their chest or Nick Fury.
You know people love, and now Tom Edelston, you have fan art but such specific fan art.
There's a lot.
And does it all come with this one scene?
It was at the first Thor movie with the spear?
Right, right.
Yes.
There's a scene in a first Thor film where I'm trying to attack Thor, Chris Hemsworth, as Thor with the spear.
And I jump in the air and he dodges out the way and I bring the spear down and wedges itself into the floor.
And then I use it to spin myself around and kick him in the chest, which has been interpreted by fans as a demonstration of my hidden talent at pole dancing.
Pole dancing.
Yeah, no, no.
No, no, no.
There's so much of this.
This is just one example of Loki really going for it on the pole.
Oh, my God.
Is that Japanese French?
That's what you wear in the movie.
I've not seen it.
Yeah, that's Loki's outfit.
Yeah, I've not seen that one.
Oh, really?
I will print it out.
You can take it in.
Wow.
Very quickly.
It is Oscar's weekend, this weekend.
And Ian, would you mind telling us the story about when you were nominated for Dandalf?
Yeah, Dandalf.
Oh, yeah.
And you had the beads.
Yeah.
Well, there were beads in New Zealand where we filmed Lord the Rings.
If you're lucky, when you leave, you're given a piece of green stone carved and you wear it often enough and your chances are you'll get back to New Zealand.
That's the idea.
And it will bring you a bit of luck.
So when those films were nominated for something like 20 Oscars on that night, everybody from New Zealand was wearing the green stone, the Poonami, they're called.
And when we're on the red carpet going into the ceremony, Maggie Smith, you know, what are you here for?
I said, well, Lord of the Rings, oh, yeah.
She said, what's that round?
Your neck?
I said, it's my Poonami, Maggie.
I only have Poonami.
What's that fight?
Well, if I wear it, it'll bring me luck.
I don't know.
Very nice.
And we went to our separate ways.
And you know it lasts for three and a half or four hours.
You know, don't you?
Oh, God.
You sit there and sit there.
And at the end, of course, everyone else wins the Oscar apart from you.
And a bit dejected, you're coming out looking forward to a drink and you're bumping to Maggie Smith and she points out and you're just saying, didn't work.
So, you make Carol Thatcher.
And now, how much preparation goes into, well, obviously, you put a nose on.
I did have a nose on.
But what else goes on preparing for Carol Thatcher?
I should make up some shit for them.
I watched, I'm a celebrity, get me out of here.
But when you're playing it at something I could attempt, if you do, like for a broad church, did you do preparation?
Sorry.
David did.
And I could ask him questions.
It seems silly doubling up.
So, to defend my actions, I don't think my character spoke in the same sort of rhythms as detectives.
So I thought it'd be better if I didn't have that influence.
Good answer.
Do you doubt a lot though?
Yes, thank you for saving me.
I do.
In that.
Well, Nick Frost is the lead guy.
And he, as a child, I'm his sister.
That's it.
I'm his sister.
I remember.
And as children, he was salsa champion and endless cups and awards and things.
And we used to go off and do competitions and I was his dance partner.
And then something happened.
And his life changed.
And salsa wasn't for him after that moment.
And then, cut to Nick Frost present day.
Or whatever his character's called.
And Bruce.
He's called Bruce.
That's it.
I'm really good.
I got many people who are applauding you rememberingультат of people in your own film.
It was anètement bad.
We know this feeling.
You filmed something.
Nelson Mandela.
You know you're not in big, you're not in big preparation, but you must have had some dancers.
I was forced to because I had to dance on screen.
So I had to practice.
Do you look good though?
Well, there is, as you know, there are people who actually condense.
Yeah.
Because I can only spend three times before I vomit.
We never picture of you in rehearsals where it doesn't look like it's going that well.
That's the best thing I've ever seen.
I also love that you're wearing like a full sweatsuit and heels.
What did you perform?
You performed at a seafood festival?
I mean, which shit show you want to know about?
That town don't know.
It was only, I think they wanted, was it crap?
I had a crab fest.
Crab fest.
What is that?
And at the beginning of the stand-up comedy, you're not performing in luxury venues.
Wherever they feel that they can build the stage and make money is where you're going.
So there was a crab fest.
We're going to book some talent.
A comedian talent.
That was like, oh, you know, I'm available.
I don't know if you guys have ever tried to tell a joke while people cracking crabs.
That's the best environment.
Literally, the frustration that comes from not being able to open a crab is stupid.
But you're not funny at the same time.
I'm not for you here.
I remember hearing a woman, older lady, who was like, she was cracking crabs.
Because this is how you crack crab.
Now I'm here, she's like cracking a crab.
Now tell a joke and a joke doesn't work.
Now remember this lady just going, oh no.
I don't think I would much rather be booed.
This is a point.
From her voice.
She said, baby, it was like, oh no, baby.
And then I made a mistake with my choice of life.
I'm not going wrong.
You know, look, the hardship that I went through has helped build me into the person I am today right.
I can take so much.
But I've been through it all.
I was hitting the face with a buffalo wing.
I performed at a cat's house.
I'm going to show you now.
There's no food.
It was actually a male strip club that they shut down for comedy for the first half.
It was a bunch of ladies in there.
And you know, it was just supposed to be us performing for these women that were riled up.
First thing, I got on stage when they introduced me and his lady was like, pull it out.
I said, hey, hey.
Hey, that's not me.
I'm not here.
I'm here to entertain.
He's a joke.
I know who's got kids.
I started trying to emerge into kid material.
And one dude from the back, I didn't remember his dude from the back.
He was like, that's enough.
And he just threw a buffalo wing at me.
And the man who hit me, hit me in the cheek,
a little bit of sauce, got like, right here.
Buffalo sauce is hot.
So I started.
I assumed it was a woman with a deep voice.
So I was like, who threw it?
Who threw it?
Because at the end of the day, I'm a man.
I'm a man first.
Don't just respect me.
He stood up.
He was like, I did it.
And I contemplated just taking my clothes off.
I was like, I said, I'm the only way to do that.