What do you call it when you fart on another person?
Oh.
Hey!
That's a really good one.
Hello!
Oh!
That's too funny.
You're doing some dad jokes.
Are you ready?
Yeah, I think so.
You think so?
Possibly.
I'm a little bit of a glasses to take them off.
OK.
All right, you're ready to see this paper rock?
Yeah.
OK.
See this paper rock.
Oh!
OK.
So go first.
Now, why shouldn't you play poker with a plumber?
Ooh.
Because a good flush beat a full house every time.
Oh, yeah.
Oh!
Got him!
It's got to be real.
These games, is it?
Well, the thing is games.
Is that true, Tim?
Don't know.
No.
Flush doesn't do the full house.
OK.
What is another use for a woman?
Oh, my fucking god.
OK.
A finger puppet.
Timmy, what the fuck?
Incorrect.
What the fuck?
Oh my god.
OK.
It's so bad of a poker, please.
No.
It's one of those games.
It's a good job.
Great job.
Yeah.
OK.
What do you call a group of disabled people?
A garden.
No, you get it.
A bunch of fucking vegetables, man.
Oh!
I can get a car.
That's pretty good.
What do you call a sunbatte girl with the yeast infection?
Grill cheese.
Honestly, that ain't even man.
No.
No, it's just healthy.
I'm really laughing.
No, it was just the idea I was trying not to throw up.
Yeah.
I'm on the coaches.
I do a proof.
OK.
What is the only organ in women that stays warm once dead?
Your dick.
No!
Thank you.
Or warm up.
Swarm up.
It's just not cold.
What's easier to lift the heavier gets?
A woman.
What?
Is that a rental letting get it?
It's bad joke.
She's easy on her to get it.
Easy to lift.
That's what it says.
You wrote it.
No.
You thought it was fucking great.
What's that?
Pick up.
Maybe pick up?
Oh, pick up.
Oh, yeah.
That's a great joke.
But I was just kidding.
Don't do it to me, but do it to me.
You get to get it wrong.
That's stupid.
If you get to wrong this time, I'm going to say it.
No, no, no, no.
Give it to that.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to see you.
Okay.
What's got a big beard and balls?
To me's mom.
Introducing Manscave's beard and balls bundle.
Featuring the Loma 5.0 Ultra and the beard hedgehog.
The perfect duo for your face and below the waist.
Let's remember things we're starting off with the goat of the shaving world.
The Loma 5.0 Ultra.
This legendary shaver features two interchangeable skin-safe blade heads.
A precision trimmer.
Because I know how to say this word.
A precision trimmer and an updated foil trimmer blade that glides gently over your skin.
Capturing the finest of hairs, giving you some seriously silky smooth hairs.
It also comes with three different comb links and even an LED jewel spotlight.
So you can groom with the precision even in the dark.
Moving on with the beard and balls bundle, we have the beard hedgehog.
A titanium coated stainless steel tea blade and 20 different length options.
And guess what?
It's waterproof too.
So what are you waiting for?
Head to Manscave.com to get yourself the Manscave beard and balls bundle.
And get 20% off plus free international shipping when you use the promo code Yeah Mad.
Wow!
That's right.
20% off and free international shipping when you use the promo code Yeah Mad.
Hela, redneck children, taught to wear their underwear.
Yellow in the front, brown in the back.
Oh, that's gross.
Oh, it's so heavy.
I hate that I laughed at that.
I thought it was great.
Oh, I envy you, dude.
I love these two actually.
This is such a shit combo.
No, no.
What do you call a disabled gang member?
A crib.
Good.
Yeah, nice.
What's the worst thing that you could do to a blind person?
Leave a plunger in a toilet.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah.
He doesn't remember the ones that he was on the couch all the way.
Okay, we haven't done this one.
Okay, right.
Kimmy, just say like this.
Kimmy, by watching how.
I'm ready, man.
That's a good one, Seth.
That's a good one, Jimmy.
Jimmy.
No, I'm going to go to one.
Just say like this.
Jimmy, just say this.
You're a man.
I can't do it.
I just told you it's 10 words.
Just say it.
You're about nine to many words.
What's the worst thing that you can do to your blind best friend?
High five.
That's good.
That's a good one.
I was really hoping that you'd put your hand up.
But if you did it, you'd put up the joke with none of it.
It's been worked for me for a memory of you.
Honestly, to me, you did so.
To be honest, he rifted.
He was like, blind best friend.
I was like, we did not.
Manchin, the best friend in this.
I said, what's the worst thing you can do to a blind best friend?
High five.
What's better than winning gold at the Paralympics?
Not being disabled.
I know.
I thought that would have gotten him.
What's the best part of having a twin?
Spear parts.
Oh!
Shout out to the best friend.
That was great.
That's what he tells the most fucked up jokes.
He's like, hey, what's the best thing about the worst thing ever?
Like, do I have a problem?
Say it with me now.
Only game parts.
Now let's say it's finished.
Uno, step past.
I'm just wondering which one was meant to be Spear parts.
Bosh.
What?
One of them has to be an accident, okay?
Oh, that's true. That is true.
It's true. You're not expecting two.
Show that cat system.
They're not an accident.
Correct.
What time does an ISIS member go to bed?
Usually crashes around to 9-11.
That's...
Play cat.
That is unru-cat.
That's unru-cat.
On that topic.
Going.
Can I just...
I'm just gonna help.
You can do it.
Go. You can try.
No, no.
What's the best way to fade your twins?
Here comes your appointment!
Ah.
Tell me when.
That's not...
You have a sneak, they're like...
That's not you.
No, no, no.
She comes to the twins.
Just feel the classic.
That's good. That's good.
Tough to add.
No, no.
What do you call a disabled supermodel?
Hot Wheels.
Ha-ha-ha.
No, no, no.
Oh, yeah.
I saw in the words about that butter.
Those two close to the chair.
Oh, yeah.
What?
Do you call it when you fart on another person's butt?
A fart plant strain.
I cooked it!
Thank you.
It's a fart plant strain.
Fart plant strain.
Fart strain!
Swing in.
Say that three times faster.
Fart plant strain.
That's a great joke.
That's a good joke.
I thought it was great. You said fart.
Cheers. Cheers. I was a good owner like that.
Who?
Don't.
Now with it.
Oh.
Now the shot.
All right.
What do you call a fire ant with severe learning disabilities?
A fire.
A dent.
Oh.
Yeah.
I didn't want to do it.
What's worse than a lobster on your piano?
You're getting a lot worse.
Crabbs on your organ.
That's a great.
He got it.
Oh my god. He's telling me.
Oh, yes. He's an egg.
Oh, he's me.
The biggest Stephen time in the universe.
He's almost there.
He had me.
Lobsters on your piano.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh my god.
I've never been more proud.
Lobsters on your piano.
Did you know that every star sign has its own hairstyle?
Except for cancer.
That's the right thing.
And what the fuck's Timmy's is?
Timmy's on stage too.
All right.
No, no, no. I meant drink.
Yeah, Timmy loved.
Yeah, I loved it.
Boy, you were.
You see left.
Shout out to me, said dresser.
When a deaf girl jacks you off.
It's technically oral.
Ah.
Just absolutely.
That's the smartest thing you've ever seen.
It is.
Did you hear about the f*** it?
He came out of the cupboard.
Oh, I got one.
I got one.
That's f***ing good.
You got one.
Say, do it.
Say, do it again.
You can say, just say, do it again.
Did you hear about the half a gay?
Say, what?
Say, did you hear about the half a gay?
He came out of the cupboard.
Guys, it's really good.
You're a f***ing f***ing.
A plightful aprice and children is crashing to earth.
One says, what about the children?
The other says, f*** the children.
The third one says, do we have time?
I think you lost me at one.
I lost me at one.
There's two priests on the whole.
There's so many planes for a priest.
If the planes full of priests, where are the kids?
10.
If there's no sense that there's any resistance.
Where the f*** are the kids?
Where are the kids?
All right, I'll write it in.
All right, time for the draw.
Time for the priests and where are the children?
I'm okay.
We gotta keep going.
What is the first thing that you would do if you woke up as a girl?
The dishes.
That's the most easy thing you were.
I was like this man.
I would like that.
To be laughed for sure.
That?
No good.
Actually, no good.
To be has no idea what it was doing.
So I asked the Toistor manager where the Arnold Schwarzenegger door was.
And he said to me, I'll be back.
Back.
I thought you were going to say the end word.
I'll be back.
I didn't get it.
I said, man, got caught fucking a pig.
Okay.
So they killed the pig.
Where were?
I got one of the drugs.
I'm dead fucked a pig.
So they killed the pig.
I didn't even skip over that.
We're taking the same decision.
What do I mean?
I'm just...
What?
I'm just talking.
What did he say?
Did he do it?
I didn't do it.
I did it!
Dude, what's next week?
Next week he only has prime signs, no setups.
Next week he's like, and the donkey did it.
What does that...
At the two strings left, like he's supposed to.