When we have a big star like you what we like to do is if there are fans of traveled
to give me the opportunity to ask some questions now
Who have I got first? I've got a looking for Victoria Campbell
There's Victoria Campbell excuse I okay and I stand up for Victoria
So you're Victoria and where you from Bristol Bristol that's brilliant news isn't it?
Here's probably
He's quite close he's still quite far away back back
What would you what would you like to ask him?
Well, being your friend Lance Armstrong is back in Tour de France. Yes. Is that anything you're considered yourself doing me writing the Tour de France?
Wait a minute. That's your quet. That's a one question
One of these going to enter the Tour de France all these psychic hosts. I'm guessing no
The favorite out of super heavyweight category. Yeah, that'd be great
Oh no, I ride bikes. I ride for like the father's ever been is 80 miles and a lot of French riders were going you pussy get out of here. Don't go
Andrew gosh Andrew go hello Andrew look at you now. Where are you from?
It's where and what's your question? Hi Robin that I just wanted to ask
I'm Graham North. I'm here every week
This week's specialty
Robin in the past you've made a documentary about one of your passions dolphin. Is this going anywhere?
And I just wanted to know whether you are planning to make any films about any of your other interests
Thank you
I am awake. He is I am
There'll be a on sale in adult movie store
One of them is called Goodwill Humping
But thank you
Have you really been interested? Have you really made a film about dolphins?
I did a documentary about dolphins. I got to swim with them in the open sea, which was pretty great
And there was I actually got bitten by a dolphin, which is hard to do
And the guy accused me of putting my finger in his blowhole. I went I
Know that's not good. That's not going up to someone on the street going man if I put my finger in your
Hello nice to meet you
Where's Olga? Oh, she's right here. All right. All this here up against Olga. Hello, and where you from Olga? Hello Graham
London she loved just general London. I think Olga has a surprise for us
I'm a funny feeling it won't be a surprise
Robin you and Mrs. Doubtfire were a tour de force of cross-dressing
Inspiration to us tranny is everywhere. Thank you. Thank you Olga
Robin who is your inspiration in stagecraft?
Studio just got a text
You
I would say RuPaul to me is God's gift. I think if those of you don't know who RuPaul is imagine Kobe Bryant with tits
But I think that for me and a day medna for oh, yeah, pure pure comedy. Yes
I'm going to marry that's right. It's there in New Zealand. Yes
And they got a bit off they got whisked off on a little oh
Service
Can we say whisked on BBC one I think you can't say whisked off. Oh that
It's like pissed off though. Oh
Yes
Minute in good night
Did you drive yourself here tonight? No
No, no, no, got my driving license. No, I'm still on driving me. Would you get in the car with them?
You're coming in your car when the black mariner
No
But now my husband is officially allowed to drive yes, I would get in a car with him
Only 61 years but I mean the terms of teaching you didn't know what before I was too pissed to drive
Okay, fair enough. Oh, no, we can go for my test and I'll go that's seeming I'll go
No, Mr. Osborne come back another day
I'm not even getting in the car
Walking on the test ended with a bottle of oak in my pocket in the car
Did you learn in a manual or an automatic? I can drive anything one of that a few trees
Anything you can use yet
Channel should move is there anything that can go on BBC one. Yeah, you just have a promotion. It's all DVD extras
You you're maize me you do you do you like a sort of Gordon Ramsay figure in my world. Thanks
You are so I don't know if you do you feel busy you seem incredibly busy
I pack a lot into the day. I suppose that is true. Yes
You do dramas travel documentaries books time consuming stuff. Yes, I'm
People seem surprised by but I think it is only because I'm hungry for it
If you are if you're anxious and keen to do things you do it when people say they're on to no fows in the day. It's never true
Yeah
You have you have you have one of those brains that just absorbs things quite easily and retains
Tell you though
They're all kinds of things that everybody in this room knows that I'm completely ignorant this happened to me on
By the journalist the other day they said so what do you think about Katie Price?
When he said Jordan I did know I did know there was a woman called Jordan I'd heard of her
I didn't know I don't know who she is
That's the sort of ignorance that makes you seem even clever
But as a calu as a calu you've yourself yeah, and famously you were quite wild and in school and got expelled
Yes, and but you'd expect me a bill you're a bit of a swat
I was yes for many years. I was a swat you were good at everything. Yeah, I've found it quite easy
It came quite easily now. It's a affinity for languages and studying and I just didn't really take it seriously
And you'd quite a kind of juvenile obsession with drugs and things that could get you high
Yeah, well, that's right. There was always this myth that if you smoked nutmeg, you know
Get some sort of trip some hallucinous
So I got all the nutmeg out of the spice rack
Sort of put it into cigarette papers
I just got a rather sweet breath
And the other thing was dried bananas skin. Yes, there was this sort of this
It was a ludicrous there is nothing on this earth like I got now called in between us
You know that sort of age person when they solemnly go apparently
You can lean forward to get apparently and I had this one I heard apparently if you take the wax from a dog's ear
And you put it on like an argolid or an iron and you warm it up and you breathe in the fumes
It's like the most amazing high
Apparently, apparently you do
5% here is this true worth maybe more now 270 million dollars. I'm kind of been you know go up
Don't very well. That's more money than I make in a year
200 and sent how did you take that?
I
So long water no seriously. It's water. He's a water millionaire. You want to yeah, yeah
First you with those people
Put your name on water
I invested in vitamin water a company sold a Coca-Cola
Did pretty well, but you made was at a hundred million. They're pretty good
That's
That's incredible is it and it's a true now that you're gonna bring out your own range of condoms
I was exploring the idea
Then miss that that was the greatest moment of the show
You said look I was exploring the concept and idea of developing a new fresher
Safe sex program, you know, like your condoms the wrap it up
Is getting a little old and I think it's uneffective so I have an idea for the condoms
You know you can get condoms that I'll give you this you can get condoms that are ribbed for her pleasure
Yeah, so why do you turn them inside out please myself?
Now I have to say Dr. Who fans yes, obviously they they're gonna be very torn this week because obviously they love you
So though I want to watch the show because you're on it
But I'm hosting it and they hate me
I just strode the episode of Dr. Who not my fault
There was a big cliff hanger it was a big cliff hanger and then just I didn't see it but just as he was back
What was he killing someone are going to be killed
In the monologue to end the episode and then and then a little animated trailer because I do a show that comes on after Dr
Little animated trailer of me going
Dancing across the screen with up next over the rainbow
They've had I think nearly six thousand complaints. Oh
They don't like me
I mean it's not
Yeah, you know I think do it again
Yeah, we're doing funny if you next week they do exactly
You began you didn't tell your parents you were doing come no, I did not tell my parents
I was doing comedy for like a few months and they came in they thought I was selling drugs and
They bust the door open one night. We know what you're doing it no one
I'm telling jokes
Why didn't you just say so
You've seen a lot of your childhood and everybody hates Chris in the sitcom because you relate to your mother
I mean she's out forced to be reckoned with yes, and that the mother's pretty accurate
Not really an exaggerate my mother is a ghetto snob
So you can be from the ghetto and still be a snob at the same time so my mother my mother would do things like
Send me to get ribs, right?
But give me a different bag because she didn't want anybody to see the rib bag coming back
We don't want people to know we read
I
Like because you think a lot of parents we you know encourage their their children's kind of high aspirations. Yes, but I you told your mom you
I was a kid
Before I want to be a comedian my dream was to be the president of the United States
The only real job I ever wanted okay
Only time I wanted an office. I wanted to be the president of the United States. I told my mother. She's like you better not you'll get shot
Well, I'm then on I'd never tried to be good in school at all
I can't be president. What's the point?
Emma did Leo bomber's mother did not say that
She had a different message
Age sucks if you got a face
But it is it is because America is really so youth obsessed. I mean how and in the film you show you know kind of that
It is hard for a woman of your age to get the jobs. It's beyond difficult the only jobs really left now for women
Unless they get friendly with people to do films
The only jobs that are really commercials. I just thank God
My I made my yearly nut this year on a practical girlie which is for driver China and it's
Well, anyone knows the heartbreak of driver China
I was perfect for it
Cavals follow me home
Three Jewish men are trying to rent my uterus instead of going to Miami
But and this
God for these commercials there's one called and Zestra is that coming in yet
It's like women's Viagra has that happened yet. It's women's Viagra and they have a big discussion with me
Should they make it in pill form? This is honest to God truth
It was a new favorite pill form or cream because they didn't know which would do better and they find a side of these idiots
We'll do it in cream because if it's in pill form in a bar a man can drop it in a woman's drink and she won't know it
But if you're in a bar and a guy goes so where you from?
So I'm I'm not put I love that commercial
Tom how did you end up in the Fresh Prince Biller? They asked me to go on there
But they were enough before that they they were sort of
Talking about me because
Carl's was a Tom Jones fan. Yeah. I will used to make fun of that
No, no, no, no, no, but I mean you know you can't I was like you know cool and slick and and Carlton was trying to do my moves and all of a sudden
And then at the end there you are
Wow both of you unchanged
At the end of the show the last episode of the series and
So Carlton's looking through Will's records and that he has a record of mine. Yeah, so that was it that was a payoff
And it's incredible given you have this phenomenal film career that fresh prince doesn't go away
Every country in the world that is the thing that I am most known for no matter how big the movies get it's
Fresh Prince everywhere
I'm a book you or is it listen man long as they scream and will I'm cool
But it's funny because Alfonso Rivera who plays Carlton we were when we first started the show
We were trying to come up with names for the characters and we're going through and we're talking about it
Now Fonzo pulled me aside. He said man, let me tell you something
He said whatever your character's name is people are gonna call you that for the rest of your life
He said make your character's name will Smith
You know and he was so right and you know when we go out together people are like will will Carlton
Carlton's better than a fun sir
I