It's with all the yelling.
Leonard disproved my element.
Now all the attention is going to go away.
Oh, that's great, you must be thrilled.
That's it.
I'm down to seven friends.
I was counting habits and superheroes, right?
When I saw that the element was real, I didn't want it.
But now that Leonard made it not exist,
I want it more than anything in the world.
The element never existed.
I didn't take it away.
Science took it away.
Be mad at science.
Don't you dare.
You science against me.
Science is my best friend.
Oh, good.
I'm back up to eight.
Will you tell him he's out of his mind?
Actually, I get what he's saying.
Yes, nine.
Welcome back, buddy.
It's like if you're dating someone, you're not that into,
and then they break up with you, and then you
want them more than ever.
I have no idea what she's talking about.
We're getting up on you, so I agree.
OK, Shogun, what do you want me to do?
Highly the information.
If I don't publish it, it's just a matter of time
before someone else does.
But no, no.
Of course you have to publish.
That your responsibility is a scientist.
Doing otherwise would be unethical.
You have no choice.
Fine, I'll publish.
Can you believe this guy?
This is fun.
I'm going to feel like such a vixen wearing jewelry
that doesn't have a list of medications I'm allergic to.
Benny, how's it going over there?
Good.
I'm just having a little trouble with the glue.
How do you not know how to use glue?
Did you ditch preschool?
Yeah, only because I was dating a second grader.
Hello, everyone.
OK, let me have it.
Let's hear all the rages of girl jokes.
No, Bernard, that's only, does it nice?
And I'm not allowed.
Thank you.
So I won't be making fun of you or the things you like
or the fact that you just want to have fun.
Howdy, stop.
Come on, look at what I'm eating.
It's actually pretty nice.
I'm making a bracelet.
Yeah, I'm just making a mess.
You know, instead of beads and glue,
you guys can use my soldering iron.
You'd be able to make much cooler stuff.
Well, I think we're doing just fine.
Thank you.
Actually, I'd kind of like to try that.
I can't do it.
You'd be right back.
When did I have pistachios?
Isn't that Professor Proton?
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
Look at him.
He's standing in line like he wasn't
moderately famous 30 years ago.
Let's go say hello.
Oh, maybe we shouldn't bother him.
I'm not going to bother him.
I'm going to talk to him.
He thinks there's a difference.
Arthur.
Arthur, it's me, Sheldon Cooper.
But you may not remember because of your advanced age.
Trust me, I remember.
But this is my girlfriend, Amy.
This is television legend Arthur Jeffries.
His science show inspired millions of children.
Hold on.
You have a girlfriend.
Yes, and I've heard so much about you.
Hey, look, we're wearing the same worth of pedic shoes.
Can't believe I dressed like a celebrity.
Oh, OK, I got it now.
Dr. Jeffries, hello again, lettered hostetter.
Oh, all right.
I remember you're girlfriend.
Is she here?
No, she's not.
So what prescription are you getting filled?
That's Sheldon.
You know, I want to guess.
Don't tell me.
I wasn't going to tell you.
Sheldon, come on.
No, no, no, I'm really good at this.
Give me a hint.
Does it involve difficulty initiating
a stream of anything?
Well, given my age, that's more than just a lucky guess.
Hey, Sheldon, let's go mock the people
buying homeopathic medicine.
You love that.
But I'm hanging out with my friend.
We're having fun.
Look how happy he is.
Arthur doesn't have those kind of resources.
No, and that's why he had air and pace, rewire.
How do you even gotten to my scene yet?
I know, but you're going to be a TV star,
and you haven't left me yet.
That takes guts.
I don't know about you, but I'm very uncomfortable with all this.
Why?
I've never seen this show before.
And now I'm starting with episode 246.
It's unnatural.
Just think of the first 245 as the prequel.
All right.
Let me show you guys this is it.
I guess it's you and me, too.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to make peace.
We're good.
Good.
Are you kidding me?
What's wrong?
Well, the diner scene.
Where's my diner scene?
But don't ask me until I see the prequel I'm lost.
No, there's supposed to be a big scene with me and Mark
Harman, but it's gone.
What happened?
They must have cut it.
Oh, Penny.
I'm sorry.
That's stash.
Sure you agreed?
This doesn't make any sense to me.
I thought I did a really good job.
But excuse me.
I've been studying how to make people laugh.
LAUGHTER
They say that comedy is tragedy plus time.
Let's take some ribs.
No.
I think if we want to predict the height of the wave,
we need to use elasticity theory and model the lattice
as one continuous flexible piece.
This is fun.
Playing with popsicle sticks, exploring ways
to store kinetic energy.
It's like preschool all over again.
Except now if I eat pasted, it's because I want to.
Not because Craig Schultz is making me.
Hey, can I ask you a question?
Is it where was the teacher?
She was in the bathroom smoking.
That's where.
It wasn't, but I'm glad to see you've moved on.
I was going to ask if being married felt any different.
Oh.
Not really.
Sorry, that probably wasn't the answer you were looking for.
No, actually it is.
I mean, Sheldon and I are in a really great place right now,
and I just don't want anything to mess that up.
You do remember you're here because he kicked you out
of your apartment.
Yes.
His work is important to him.
It's one of the things I find the sexiest about him.
Well, that and...
LAUGHTER
His butt.
He has a little snack.
Are you sure you don't want your spy to do it?
What are you talking about?
You really don't trust me.
You had to have Amy stop by?
I trust you.
Yeah.
You were a terrible waitress, and we still
ask you to get us a snack.
LAUGHTER
Excuse me, why go take care of your baby
that I'll bring you your snack, and you can insult me some more.
I don't know about you, but I am not eating whatever she brings us.
We have only the K-A-T-Penny's here.
Shh.
Let's get you changed.
Your mommy and daddy say they trust me,
but they're full of the same stuff your diaper is.
LAUGHTER
No, I feel bad.
Well, you never really liked me.
It's kind of nice you hate you now, too.
But I'm here for you, and I would never let anything happen to you
because your anti-penny loves you so much.
Mama.
LAUGHTER
Was that her first word?
Mama.
Oh, no, no, baby, I'm not your mama.
Your mama's a nice lady.
We're going to go see right now so I can rub this in her face.
Do you hear that sucker?
She called me Mama.
What's going on?
What if there was something I wanted to do?
But I was worried other people would think less of me.
Is that other person me, and does it happen in the bedroom,
in which case I think I'm cool with it?
LAUGHTER
No.
It's about working with Bert on, you know what?
I'm not even going to say it.
I am just going to say the letter it starts with, and,
Olaji.
G. Oh, no, no, it's not going to work.
LAUGHTER
Geology?
Yes.
But we parted ways because I was worried about my reputation.
Sheldon, you've never cared what people thought,
even when you really, really should.
You okay?
No, I'm very nervous.
LAUGHTER
Oh, oh.
Oh.
LAUGHTER
Where are you going?
Give shop.
There is no give shops, you know.
LAUGHTER
This was your idea.
It's always having sex, and look where that got us.
This isn't a big deal. Stop lying to me.
When you were in labor and I said that, you kicked me.
LAUGHTER
Howard Wallace?
I'll make it with you?
No, I'll be fine.
Yeah, we got this.
Sit down.
LAUGHTER
Wish me luck.
Other way, Buster.
LAUGHTER
Okay, this is a bit awkward.
It says here that I need to check the area for redness and swelling.
You know what, it hurt so much, go ahead.
They're going to start making Professor Proton's science show again.
They thought he passed away.
He did. It was cremated and his remains were put in the baking soda volcano.
Don't make jokes. He meant a lot to Sheldon.
Me too. I grew up watching his show.
He's one of the reasons I became a scientist.
I thought you did it just to get girls.
Jokes on you, it worked.
You know, they found anyone to replace him?
No, not yet. And it won't be easy.
Arthur Jeffries was an accomplished scientist.
You know who'd make a great Professor Proton?
Merrill Streep.
She's not a scientist.
Then explain to me why she has chemistry with literally everyone.
LAUGHTER
It would be nice if they cast a woman.
You've already got Dr. Who in the Ghostbusters.
Leave us something.
Well, this party's a disaster.
Don't blame the party.
How many favors I'd do calling with my bounce house guy to get Wonder Woman?
Is that Wonder Woman?
Technically, it's a Chinese knockoff called Happy Strong Simpsuit Lady.
Then I take it back. It's a great party.
No, you can sit here and suck if you want.
I'm going to celebrate Halley's first birthday,
which I planned with no help from you.
What are you doing?
It's a bounce house. I'm going to go bounce in it.
You're supposed to take your shoes off before you go in there.
You know what?
I'm stressed about my daughter's birthday party.
I don't need your attitude.
Well, I will do the hard on this, and you haven't even said thank you.
Oh, I'm sorry, thank you.
Thank you for blaming me for everything that's wrong in your life.
Thank you for walking out on our friendship.
You are welcome.
And thank you for mocking me for all of these years.
And for making it so easy.
Why are you being such a jerk?
Because you're my best friend, and you hurt my feelings.
Well, you're my best friend, you hurt my feelings.
I can't believe you shut me.
But it was kind of fun, wasn't it?
It was. Do it again.
Gladly.
Oh, yeah, now the same time.
Oh, it's awesome.
Yeah, okay, this time, knees, then feet.
One, two, three.
Sorry if it's weird, Cheldon made me best man instead of you.
It's okay. I was best man for two whole days.
No one can take that away from me.
Tipford, Cheldon, when he did.
Although if you want to be a part of the wedding party,
I suppose you could be the flower girl.
Sold.
But I thought Hallie was going to be the flower girl.
Oh, that's much better. Sorry, Stuart, you're out.
Hey, so it's Bernadette, okay, with me being made of honor.
Actually, I haven't had the courage to tell her.
I guess I should do that.
Oh, yeah.
Although as made of honor, your job is to make my life easier.
Damn it.
Hey, Stuart, you still want in on this wedding?
Not that much.
Fine, I'll do it.
But do me a favor and unlock the liquor cabinet first.
Scratch paper, check. Whiteboard, check.
Check, mix, check.
And here we go.
Dang it.
Hello, mother.
Hi there, Shelley.
You will never believe who I ran into at the barbecue festival.
I am right in the middle of some very important work.
I don't have time for this right now.
Then why did you answer the phone?
Because you raised me to be polite.
Now stop bothering me.
Either anybody
or somebody else than her.
Hello again.
Who did you see at the barbecue festival?
Mr. Watkins.
Really? You called me and interrupted my work to tell me
that you ran into somebody you could plausibly run into.
I'm sorry, mother. I really need to focus here.
I will speak to you next week.
Okay, sweetheart. I'll talk to you then.
I thought Mr. Watkins moved to Florida.
He did. He was back visiting his son.
Oh, gosh darn it. That is interesting.
Was it Tommy or Joe? I bet it was Joe,
because he and Tommy had a falling out of that time share.
Okay. I'm really uncomfortable with him back in that room.
Why? Has it made a people day?
You don't get it all the years that we lived together.
He drove me crazy the whole time.
And now he's not.
Exactly.
Look at me like that. It means he did it on purpose.
It was a choice.
That's like fighting out Godzilla could have had Arbise instead of Tokyo.
I don't think they have Arbise in Japan.
Not my point.
Sheldon.
Sorry, am I being too loud?
No, you're being perfect and you know it.
Would you like me to be a less considerate tenant?
No. Yes. Stop messing with me.
Hey, I was wrong. There's an Arbise in Okinawa.
No Marisa. How did you guys meet?
Oh, it's a pretty funny story. We met in a bookstore.
That is funny.
Yeah, I was just there using the bathroom.
But this one had a stack of books like this doll.
Oh, I see you really like to read.
Oh no, I work there.
Yeah, she is super smart.
Seriously, you name like any book?
She'll tell you if she's heard of it.
Go on, try her.
Oh, uh, uh, uh, catch her on the ride.
Nope.
Look at that, Penny. I guess we both like nerds.
So, uh, can I take this thing out?
No, it's a little choppy tonight.
Yeah, that's okay. This is nice sitting under the stars.
It's actually kind of peaceful.
Well, it's a beautiful boat.
Thanks, man. We love it.
Although he's so tall, he bends his head almost every time he goes downstairs.
After the first couple, you don't even feel it.
Where are our manners?
Zach, let's get our guests something to drink.
Got it, babe.
You can't believe that guy's rich.
What's your head?
That was a close one.
Are you jealous?
I know, I know. I shouldn't be. He's super sweet.
I should be happy for them.
What's driving me crazy, too?
Really?
Yeah, so I was trying to pretend like it wasn't,
so you wouldn't think that was petty.
What? It turns out we're both petty.
I love you so much.
Oh, it's freezing out here.
Do you like me to eat things up?
No, I want to get into hot tub before I lose a toe.
Oh, petty's bright.
Yeah, a new neighbor put in floodlights.
So, shall we?
I know what I take my robe off under a spotlight.
This is a candle body.
County neighbors, we haven't met yet. I'm Andy.
Oh, hello. Nice to meet you.
You know, your new balcony kind of looks right over our fence.
You might want to put up some trees.
We can see everything.
You can, but it's okay if you don't.
So, can you turn your lights off?
Sorry, they're motion censored.
Go off in a minute. Just try to stay still.
What are we going to do about this?
I say we wait until his lights go off,
and then I make hot, motionless love to you.
Don't move. It's go time.
Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
And I'm Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler.
And this is Dr. Sheldon Cooper and Dr. Amy Farrah Fowler present
Dr. Sheldon Cooper's fun with flags.
I'd like to start this episode by apologizing on behalf of Dr. Farrah Fowler.
He made the wild claim last week that there was no national tri-colored flag
with a purple stripe.
When, in fact, the Estonian governor at Inside the Russian Empire
had a purple stripe on their flag from 1721 to 1917.
See? Right there in the middle.
And I'd like to apologize on behalf of Dr. Cooper
for having his zipper down for the entire segment on the flags of East Africa.
Sorry, Tanzania, you deserve better.
Okay, that's my dad.
Remember, do you not bring up any baby stuff, right?
Not me not one in one, not you having one with Zach?
Got it.
And if he brings up, change your subject to literally anything else.
I got it.
But not the corn huskers. Do not discuss the corn huskers.
Is that a sports team?
Never mind, you're good.
Bye!
Hey, why it?
Hey, it's a hell of a handshake.
Oh, well, I haven't been taking vitamins.
Dad, come on in, sit down.
Gonna give you something to drink? Maybe a beer?
Sure, if you're having one.
Why wouldn't you, since you're not pregnant?
Um, Leonard wants to have a baby with my ex-boyfriend Zach.
How about those corn huskers?
Amy is the one constant I can count on, and now she's changing.
It's just a haircut and some clothes.
No, it's a last straw. I can't take any more.
You and Belira, they finally fixed the elevator.
This is a nightmare.
What's with him?
He want to know Belle Pryzen, his wife looks amazing.
Oh, yeah, got it.
How did you get down here?
Elevator, it's really fast.
I need to be alone right now. Don't try to follow me.
All right, you need a ride?
That'd be great, thank you.
Where's Raj?
He's working with Bert.
They're probably cutting their stupid meteorite open with their stupid diamonds up.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm numb just a little rundown. It might be a head cold.
Pyrr-L.
Can I top anybody off?
Why don't you go to bed, I'll run out and get you some medicine.
It's okay, Stuart gave me someone else at the comic book store.
Really, you're taking medicine from Stuart?
Doesn't need like all of it.
He's got plenty, his pillcats, he's like this big.
All right, why don't you go to bed, I'll sleep out of here on the couch.
No, no, no, you take the bed, I'll stay out here.
Even better, sweet dreams, not bag.
Go away, Raj.
What are you doing?
I'm winning you bag love, actually, Stiles.
I don't know what that means.
Really? You've never seen love, actually?
If you want to watch it right now, I'll just wait.
I have nothing to say to you.
Look, we both made mistakes.
I am so sorry that I spied on you, I didn't mean to, but I know it's not okay.
Now, do you want to apologize to me?
You also said you don't trust me and that you barely know me.
I really thought this would be more of a back and forth thing.
Okay.
Amy?
Yeah.
There's something out here.
Just trap it under a cup and I'll be there in a minute.
I'll try, but it's Leonard.
I know it all feels overwhelming right now, but I promise you things will settle down.
There's no oral grade, you filthy liar.
Hey, Spenny Hill?
No, why?
I wanted to show him my latest creation.
I give you...
Dr. Amy Farah Fowler.
Wow.
Amy, you look amazing.
Thank you.
Sheldon, what do you think?
I like you better the way you were.
But she looks beautiful.
Classic lines, colors that compliment her skin tone,
and hair that goes from office to on the town in minutes.
I don't care, put it back.
I like the way I look.
Well, I don't.
My fault, I was out of her own gray.
I'm new a giant metal door.
I check the door for traps.
There are no traps.
I use my wizard eye to see what's on the other side of the door.
Hey, that's sort of like how you used a doorbell camera to spy on your fiance.
It's nothing like that.
Your wizard eye reveals a monster.
Is it alone and unloved?
I guess I open the door and say, hey, Raj!
Why don't you just call her?
I'm sure you guys can work this out.
I don't want to talk about it.
Let's just play.
Okay, the sideclaps tells you that the enchantress you seek is staying at the end of the dwarven lords.
I'd really un-in.
All I knew was a concierge at a hotel.
That's a little insensitive, don't you think?
I had to notice that before you mentioned it.
You were now that I've mentioned it. How do you feel?
Bad.
Shame on you.
Zach wanted you to donate your genetic material for his baby.
Yeah.
So I'd be helping out a couple who really want a baby and they were going to pay us and Penny freaked out about it.
That doesn't make any sense.
They wanted you?
Yes, children.
They wanted me.
I'm smart, I'm nice.
And I can eat cheese without clearing out a room.
Are you upset he didn't ask you?
Of course not. I just think it's interesting that of all the people he knows he thinks you're the best choice.
Well, he does.
I don't see why Penny is so against this.
Perhaps Penny is worried that you haven't considered the emotional toll of knowing there's a child out there who is biologically yours but not actually yours.
Oh, that's really insightful.
Yeah, I'm taller than you and I don't have asthma.
People are crazy.
I can't believe they're going to cut that with this punk ass diamond saw.
And then what are you doing?
Showing you that this is the better way.
Oh, what ever's inside there is dangerous.
Oh, and pretty.
What is that?
Ah!
Are you okay?
Ah, yeah, I'm fine.
I'm just feeling a little...
Hungry.
No!
Stop eating butt!
Keep eating butt!
Leonard, Leonard!
What? What?
You're having a bad dream.
Oh, thank God.
I was eating my friends. Well, one friend and one acquaintance.
That's either what birds are okay, two friends.
Let me see if you're running in a fever.
Oh, yeah, you're burning up.
Are you okay?
It depends.
What will look?
Color in my eyes.
I don't know. Brown? No, green.
No wait, brown.
Oh, good, I'm awake.
Oh, good, you're here. Are you still fighting?
If you get divorced, do I get two chrispuses?
We're not getting divorced.
Listen, we realized that we're facing some new challenges as a married couple.
Yeah, and there are a few things we need to stay on top of.
So we thought it would be useful.
I can't believe I am about to say this.
Would you please help us make a relationship agreement?
But one that's tailored to us, okay, we don't need a bathroom schedule.
Although a rule about him texting me from in there might help with the romance.
What do you say?
I get to write a contract.
I say let's get this party of the first part started.
You really think that's funny?
It's an R agreement I have to laugh.
Oh, that's a nice one.
Was it yours when you were little?
My dad built it for me.
Wow, it's so cute.
This was the husband, this was the wife.
They'd go out on adventures together.
Cruises, skiing, horseback riding.
That was really me just duct-taping them to our dog.
And did they have kids?
He did.
But the mommy and daddy didn't like them, so they shipped them off to an orphanage I made out of a shoebox.
Yeah, that's not worrisome at all.
Every girl dreams about being a mom.
Sometimes you think you're never going to have kids.
And one day you wake up and you're pregnant.
And it doesn't matter that your career's going great right now.
And they're doing your husband never even got to go anywhere.
I don't even care to a dog.
I skipped spin class for this.
It's going to be a while.
Well, first deliverers can be slow.
I'm trying to rethink the flash onesie I bought this kid.
I found it but it's empty.
Well, it doesn't matter. We're not going to the hospital now.
Are you sure I'd really like to?
Well, should we, uh, head back up?
Well, guys, we're all awake. Why don't we go to a diner or something?
Oh, uh, I don't know.
Sheldon, you don't want to do that, do you?
Doesn't matter what I want. It's your birthday. You decide.
Oh, my God, it's your birthday. What's just something fun?
Uh, we go to a bar? Well.
Okay, I can breathe again. Maybe they want to have sex.
Oh, of course. The annual birthday booty spectacular.
That's a bit childish, isn't it?
I'm sorry, and what flavor is your bubblegum cigar?
Great. I find it the most mild.
All right, will you two go have fun?
If we find my backup in hailer, maybe we can get frisky.
Oh, you sexy, weezy little man.
Would you look at that?
The image we gave it was 45% white noise, and it's still managed to reconstruct it.
I've never seen results like this before.
No, we need to stop from magnets on the way home. This is going right on the fridge.
Aren't you glad you participated in this?
Well, I am. And you realize what the next step is.
Set up a second culture and try to replicate our results.
Uh, no. We lock that door, lower our underpants a little and make a baby.
Make a baby? What are you talking about?
Clearly the combination of our DNA is exceptional.
But our child could be the next step in the evolution of mankind.
We'll be able to get in any free school we want.
She's shelled and I'm not ready to have a baby.
Oh, yes you are. I track your cycle.
For the next 36 hours, you're as fertile as a manure-covered wheat field.
Wow, I can actually feel the egg crawling its way back up.
Hello.
I'm looking for Howard Woolowitz.
Howard Woolowitz?
I have the right address, don't I?
Address?
Is he here?
Uh, no.
Do you know where I can find him?
Me, I ask what this is about.
No, you may not.
I'll get you out.
Have him call me.
Okay.
Raj, who's at the door?
That's not him.
I wonder if this is what it feels like to be Bunnett's baby.
I don't know. Bernard's baby doesn't have a jacuzzi jet hitting just the right spot.
Those jets are for my secret spot, not his.
What are you doing here?
It's called relaxing and that's all you need to know.
Well, it's getting late.
Maybe we should head home.
Yeah.
Probably right.
You coming?
Yeah, just give me a minute.
Why?
You know how you're wearing a bathing suit?
Yeah?
I kind of went the other way.
You jacuzzi fire some hot tub!
You make God sad today, Mom.
Sheldon, they haven't done anything wrong. I think it's nice they're hitting it off.
What's the other reason to rush in to anything?
Look at us. We shut things remarkably slow.
We didn't even hold hands for two years.
It's a lot hotter than it sounds.
You're a patient young lady.
Hey, she's mine. Take a cold shower, Grandpa.
There's a lot of traffic. Are we going to be okay?
You'll be at the airport an hour before your flight.
Good. Thank you.
Plenty of time for you to meet another Jerry Attrick boy toy.
Hey, I will not have you be disrespectful to me.
Yes, ma'am.
Sheldon, your mother's an attractive woman.
You need to get used to the fact that men are going to be interested in her.
And you need to drive the car and mind your business.
I will not have you be disrespectful to me.
Well, you're not my mother.
Don't you be disrespectful to her?
Yes, ma'am.
You'll get there. You just gotta put some zing on it.
I'll make you a deal. 30 years from now, if you're still single and things don't work out with me and Bernadette,
you and I can give it a go.
I appreciate your offer, but if things don't work out with you too, I'm swooping in on her like a vulture.
Too late, still recalled dibs.
But theoretically, if you and I were in a gay relationship, how would we tell people?
Like, bring up announcements?
I don't know. What difference does it make?
Well, I want to make sure we get invited to all the parades.
That was still a fun.
Yeah, well, if you want to march in a fishnet crop top, you better lay off that dip.
You don't want me to eat it, why'd you put it out?
Just for the girls, they broke up with me. I don't care if they get fat.
I'm not gonna get fat.
You want a bet? You never exercise.
Fine. Look, I'll exercise right now.
What?
These are crunches, by the way.
Very mature. Keep eating like that. You're gonna have a heart attack.
Okay. How about if I eat like this?
Mmm.
You're such a child.
Hey, is that any way to talk to your future husband?
Hey, I was being hypothetical, okay? I would never marry you.
Please, when you see the ring I pick out, you're gonna melt.
Yeah, right.
Wait, is it Rose Gold? Actually, don't tell me I want to be surprised.
I'm only living together, kills the romance.
Okay, you guys had sex one whole time. Nothing can put out a fire like that.
But what happens when we each get a peek behind the curtain?
She's never even seen me unshaving.
Just shaved yesterday, you're good for three months.
Sheldon, I understand your apprehension, but let me appeal to the scientist in you.
Given the five-week end date, isn't it the perfect opportunity to consider this an experiment
and collect data on our compatibility?
Don't try luring me in with sexy talk.
Okay.
Start, check the original series. The Enterprise was on a five-year mission to explore new worlds.
Think of this as your personal five-week mission to do the same.
If you want to luring me in with sexy talk, that's how you do it.
Don't be proud of that.
Welcome.
What is this?
Oh, well, you said you didn't have time to go out for dinner, so I thought we could have one right here.
All right, Jason.
Come on, we're at the tennis court room. It'll be like dining under the stars.
You see this double zero? When it says zero-one, that means it's twinkling.
Sometimes it takes a while.
This is so sweet, but you know I'm working.
That's why I already cleaned up in here and all the other rooms in the hall.
Well, I suppose that gives me a little time.
Oh, this is it.
I tried to cook you a meal from your homeland.
Oh, really? You made Cuban food?
That depends. Do they have Mexican food in Cuba?
We'll get the curb out. You can take it for a test drive.
I'm telling you. This mayhem is gonna be...
Oh, is it your bar?
Yeah. Oh. Anyway, let's just get in and see if the GPS can take us to the nearest emergency room.
What was I thinking?
Well, all the witches are not a lifting people. We tip the lifting people.
Do we really have to sit for hours in the emergency room?
They're just gonna give you ice and Advil like last time.
You're gonna feel terrible when I'm in a wheelchair.
Which by the way, was bit easily in the back of this award-winning minivan.
Fine, we'll go to the ER. Just stop selling me on the van.
You're right. It sells itself.
You have to admit it's a pretty smooth ride.
I was hoping it'd be quieter.
You childbirth is half this bad. You are so screwed!
Hey, so we've been talking and if you need a place to stay, we'd be happy to fix up the garage for you.
That would be amazing!
I was literally just looking at my moving boxes trying to pick one to live in.
I know it's not ideal, but you'd have plenty of space for your furniture.
And there's this cool button that makes an entire wall go up and down.
I cannot thank you enough.
It is our pleasure.
Hey, can you hold on one sec?
Hello?
Hey buddy, are you still looking for a place to live?
Yeah, why'd you ask?
You know, we have the extra bedroom and if you needed it's doors.
Oh my god, that's so generous!
At least we can do.
Bye, I really appreciate it. Can you hold on one second?
It's a Howard. What's the bathroom situation gonna be?
Well, there's a sink out there that takes care of half your problems.
But I can use the downstairs bathroom, right?
Yeah, we barely use it, so it'll be like it's yours.
Cool, cool. Yeah, hold on one second.
What?
Hey, what's it like sharing a bathroom with Benny?
Is the hair everywhere? Does she use your loofah?
I don't have a loofah.
Okay, well if I move in you can't use mine.
Hold on a second.
Hey Howard, how's the Wi-Fi in the garage?
I don't know, why are you asking all these questions?
Well, to be honest, Dennis is on the other line and he offered me this bedroom.
Great, go live there.
But you made the garage sound so fun.
I just didn't want you to feel bad about it.
Unless Leonard's apartment also has a raccoon that chooses to weigh in on cold night, go there!
One second.
Okay, I think we're close.
How do you feel about a mini fridge in my room?
Hey pal, you want to live here or not?
Hi, Benny, yes please.
Hey, what do you think we should open a show with?
The foreign doctor Jones or let's get astrophysical.
I think we should start with something that gets them up on their feet.
Maybe Sherlock around the clock.
Great, yeah, let's give it a try.
How is nothing keeping down?
Right, sorry.
It's cool, we don't need volume to rock.
Instead of blowing the roof of this place, we can gently lift it off and set it quietly down in the backyard.
Okay, on the...
On set to bottom, on bank street.
Come on, doctor.
Time to move the feet.
Sing it with us.
Sherlock Sherlock Sherlock, Sherlock around the clock.
We can't hear you Sherlock Sherlock Sherlock around the clock.
Nice going.
Sorry, sorry, I'll get her.
One second.
You bought diapers, right?
Be right back.
Rock, I'm wrong.
They're remaking your show and they cast Will Wheaton as Professor Proton.
And the worst part is, he's not even a scientist.
No, the worst part is, I'm sitting on a moist log.
We have to stop this and protect your legacy.
What legacy?
My last two seasons, I was on Sunday morning at 5.30.
We would be by Davy and Goliath.
I can't believe you don't care.
Believe it.
Well, I care a lot and Will Wheaton grew the day he ever met me.
I think that's true of most people.
Sometimes Amy doesn't do things because she's worried about how I'll react.
First of all, it's not sometimes it's always.
Second, it's not Amy, it's everybody.
Third, it's not news, it's well established.
Yeah, like just now I wanted to get a croissant but I didn't want to hear you say Ula-la.
So you're saying everyone walks on eggshells to spare my feelings?
No, of course not because we don't want to hear you complain about how much you hate the sound of crunching eggshells.
Why don't my relationship with Amy to be like that?
Sheldon, Amy knew what she was getting into.
You think?
Yes, we warned her.
Well, regardless, I can change.
Yeah, of course you do.
Yeah, everybody thinks I'm so predictable.
Well, tomorrow, I'm going to show up at work and do something no one will expect.
We're a baseball cap backwards to prove your point.
Yes, but which hat?
Riffindle.
We know that you guess and I'm not going to do it.
Yeah, you will.
Yeah.
I just talked to Sheldon, he apologized about the tests and asked me to be his best man.
Great, after all you've done for him, he should have asked you.
And Amy's your best friend, I'm sure she'll come to her senses and pick you.
Okay, she's not my best friend, we're not 12.
She wants Bernadette to be her maid of honor, I really don't care.
Sounds like you care.
No, I mean, it's just annoying.
You know, we talk every day, we see each other all the time, she's always there for me, and basically, oh my god, Amy's my best friend.
You okay?
No, my best friend didn't ask me to be her maid of honor, I'm pissed!
So, bottom line, what you did was wrong and cruel, which the mother of my children finds oddly appealing.
So, she still wants to be my maid of honor?
Made of honor, hit woman, whatever you need, make the call.
Look, I know this is your wedding and you can do whatever you want, but if you think anyone but me is going to be your maid of honor, then you're an idiot, because you are my best friend.
Too late, Bernadette.
Bestie!