And can you look at a cartoon and come up with a voice?
Well, like with happy feet, I got to be, like,
I played two different characters.
Initially three, but then there were that
the one voice sounded too familiar.
But when I got to play in Argentina and Penguin,
I was to play the little machismo penguin,
you know, the guys, the Argentinian guys were going,
what do you know you want it?
What do you look at it? Do you know you want it?
Look at it. Don't be afraid of the flippers.
I know.
I brought you some pebbles.
There's some bling, baby. You want some bling.
You know you're doing...
yet you're hard and you know I got a beak
that'll make you feel so good.
LAUGHTER
And then you had like, oh, the crazy ones, you know?
APPLAUSE
Listen, talking about a machin, we got people
on our audience to draw cartoons of themselves.
Oh, no.
I'm sensing, I'm sensing self-esteem issues.
Where?
Let's see.
Now, oh, no.
Now, God forbid, when I ask to see this woman in the audience,
she looks like this.
You better not put that up on a candle.
It's like the best found the state.
I will be on you like, shit on Velcro.
LAUGHTER
Yeah.
Oh, fingers crossed.
Fingers crossed.
OK, show the picture.
This is the lady.
LAUGHTER
That her name is Jane Hayes.
Jane Hayes?
Now let's have a look at Jane in the flesh.
Jane.
Jane, you're beautiful, Jane.
Jane, you're not a gay black basketball player.
LAUGHTER
It's very thought for Sally Jenkins and I think her husband.
But it's Sally.
LAUGHTER
Where's Sally?
Sally suffers from paperclip kits.
Oh!
Sally, you look quite box-um.
With your funny little terrier ears.
Oh, and for some reason you've drawn a penis on your own face.
LAUGHTER
Why she's done that?
She's done a penis with two tiny balls.
And what are those those that, well, I don't know,
there's two upside-down bells.
Oh, my God.
Is that your husband, Jane?
That's you.
Yeah.
And you're naked as well.
What's that strange line?
Yeah, but more importantly, what's peeking out here?
Are those your two balls going, I'm down here.
And why did you have an accordion for a night?
Oh, yes.
You watched them with the nails.
She was drunk.
I don't know. We were drunk.
You're a chef.
Yeah.
Who else, my God?
Actually, I quite have seen this woman.
Stephanie Jack.
Where's Stephanie Jack?
Hello, Stephanie Jack.
There's Stephanie Jack in the flesh and here she's in the cartoon.
LAUGHTER
It's my brother.
Do you see a great Japanese anime character?
He's a teacher lot to come to your house.
See how the big eyes come to your house with a larger breast,
open the door with her nipple.
Look at those.
Ham and ham and ham and ham.
This bouncing breast.
Follow the bouncing breast.
Wow.
That's kind of what... Can I have this one?
Yes, you can.
It's been on the road for a while.
Why were you having the...
Was it a deep tissue massage you were having?
Where are you going with this, Green?
When are you having a Turkish massage or something?
I don't know what it has to do with what we're talking about.
It's a funny story, tell it.
I had an awful experience having a Turkish massage
where this guy's idea of massage
was to take my one leg and the other arm and try and connect it
behind my back.
And I was kind of like... You know, like that.
And then I... Well, his belly went in my mouth.
Oh, he did.
It was like a little brat.
You know what?
And you know when you get something weird in your mouth
and you're like, if you're eating something, you go like you send your brain
send your tongue to figure out what it is.
I don't know.
It's not a conscious thought. It's just like, is that a bone? Figure that out.
The tongue goes in to figure it out.
My tongue was like, what is that?
It's a hairy belly.
Sounds like you're heading off a newspapers.
Now, Amelia Clark, did you get to chat with everyone backstage?
Yeah, kind of.
Amelia Clark loves Matt.
Love, love, love.
Hi.
I was blushing.
Yeah, we just think you're wicked.
Oh.
It's a game of two halves.
I'll be coming next weekend.
Oh, yeah.
You returning the favour, do you watch Game of Thrones, Matt?
I watch it the first season and then I kind of fell out of it
and I tried to watch it this season.
That's okay, that's okay.
And I don't know what's going on.
There's lots of stuff going on.
It's so much going on.
There is.
It's okay.
I could lie, but I don't want to lie.
No, no, no, no.
You've seen the good bits.
You've seen the fast season.
It's all down here.
What is it? It's season six now.
It's season six.
And it's bigger than ever.
Who's lost?
That seriously sounds like a chicken.
I could have won that.
It's been really a while.
It's a studio.
It's a comedy.
I eat them as good as stop because I thought there was a mechanical fault
with something.
But that's a human being.
Oh, is that man there?
Oh, well, I'm glad you're having a nice time.
Yeah, get up.
I was once that song was...
No, no, I know.
I do have one request for me, though.
What's that?
So, would you be able to ask me how I'm doing?
Oh, bestie.
You can say no.
Everyone will hate you, but you can say no.
No, yes.
Well, since I haven't been up to speed on the show, I will say...
Yes, thank you.
How you doing?
I caught that.
It was.
There are some scenes where they will play music maybe a bit of it.
If it's a wide shot and it's not like...
So, it's the closest we get to sort of kind of sort of just sort of going forward in one piece.
And they'll play music or something.
And my temptation is always just to try to make the cuttle-off.
So, sometimes I'll do things like when there's a moment where I'm meant to, you know, orgasm,
I'll be like, do-do-do-do-do.
People do that.
Wait.
Which one of the way, if they don't, they should.
It's like a Ryan Air flight when a Ryan Air flight lands.
Like, give it a little.
Oh, no, no, no.
Well, people travel.
You know, they collect things, postcards, dolls and national dress.
But you collect, like animals, like living animals.
Well, no, I don't collect them. I rescue them.
Oh, okay.
So, did you rescue anything when you were in Sicily and Tuscany?
Not in that one, but in the movie I did right after in Bulgaria, I did.
Okay.
And I had promised my husband I was going to stop because at the time I had ten dogs, five parrots,
I had alpacas, horses, cats.
And by the way, one without a tail, the other one without a leg, you know.
And they always, they find me.
They come to me, these animals, which he doesn't really me, but they do.
And I promise him no more, okay?
We were up to thirty animals.
I swore no more.
And I was there, and a little puppy who was abandoned and was going to die.
I won't tell you the sad story because it's a comedic show and Alstagg, right?
He came to me and I couldn't help it and I picked him up.
And his name is Ochoa after the goalie of the soccer team in Mexico, it was a walk-up.
And I took him and then I was terrified, how am I going to explain this to my husband, I promised, I promised.
And so I came up with this brilliant idea to pretend that I was having an affair.
And then, no, with somebody to make him think I was having an affair, and at the end I would say,
it's not an affair, I picked up a dog and then he would feel better.
I picked up a dog.
This is clever, it's not an affair.
So I left him a message, you must call me at this time, we need to talk.
It's very important.
And I never do that and this time it's okay, what happened, what happened?
And I said, listen, I feel so terrible.
I don't know how to say this to you.
And I know this is not going to go down well and I'm really nervous.
And please have mercy on me, you have patience, be understanding, it's just, it's been so stressful and I'm so tired.
And I was so lonely here for so many days and you know you do crazy things when you're in this state.
And he said to me, oh please don't tell me you picked up another dog.
What I'm afraid of is you can conjure up people's fears.
Yes.
So you're afraid of basic things.
I'm afraid of like most things, like anything high risk I'm terrified of.
But those irrational things.
Okay, irrational is the expiders because they actually, I become paralyzed when I have a spider in my room.
Really? Yeah, I wish I were tougher than that but I'm not.
Okay, now, small gruffloat, we use serious when you told us what your fear is.
I mean it's a good fear.
I think it's a founded fear.
It is.
Tell us what it is.
I have a phobia of being chased around with poop on a stick.
That's fair.
I wouldn't say we've all got that fear.
There's another one that goes, not a lot for that.
It started when I was a kid.
It was just weird parenting.
For some reason, kids thought it was funny to stick a stick and dog poop and chase each other around with it.
But that scared the crap out of me.
Because of the cleanliness problem of it?
No, because of the poop.
It's just dogs poop.
It's just a prank of sticks.
Now, Jeremy Ranado, yours is brilliantly specific and I think without knowing it,
I think we probably all share it.
We may.
I don't know.
I didn't have the fear when I was younger because we all go through this but it's when a little child,
and I'm the oldest of seven kids and I got a lot of little rug rests running around.
And these little roaches start losing their teeth.
And they get a little wiggly and they like to show me like this little dagger flipping it in and out of their mouth.
And like, look out there, Jeremy, I want to pull this thing out.
I'm like, I can get out of here.
You're freaking me out.
But don't you think that is really freaky?
I mean, it's like...
It's like her thumb.
I just read it.
It's just again.
No.
It's just really kind of gross to me.
I have the cutest little thing on the planet.
It starts to do the creepiest thing on the planet.
And I'm like, get out of here.
I'm like, you're tied to string to my thing to the door knob.
I'm like, get out of here. Creep.
You got to be an animal?
I'm gonna be an animal for the year of the stage.
That's now.
No!
The other one's running around flipping their little teeth on out.
Look, we all have this...
You know, you have the dreams, you're teeth full out.
I don't know what it means.
Does anybody want a means?
We get bigger than ones.
No, you have bad dreams.
Am I the only one that has bad dreams?
No, we're your dreams.
I've written a line just had that dream too.
Just a brandy of words.
Yeah, not me.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
This is strange.
I'm sure of money, I think.
I think that's what the two call it.
Who does fear of money?
Where is the other freedom you think?
Maybe I'm just afraid of my teeth fucking falling out.
Guys, that's just what you're up to.
What are you afraid of?
Well, I was gonna go with flying,
but I think I'll go with...
Girls over 12?
You're fucking me.
I'm fucking me.
Come on, give up that blow.
Give up.
Give up that blow.
You're a terrible...
I don't know what came over me.
I'm not gonna lie to you.
The last minute of my life, I wouldn't have predicted that.
How was it, Mark Ruffalo?
You're not gonna believe what he said to me.
But he was bang on the money.
He's a very perceptive man.
It was the Dara poem.
Don't try and justify it.
Do you know what?
I've always hated the Hulk. He's shit.
You're making me angry.
Yeah, you would let me one of angry Ruffalo.
My son stood up to me the other day when he was mad at me.
What do you all like him?
I always hated the Hulk. I think he's shit.
What is the hold that the spice girls have over you?
Is this real?
I just feel like I've been talking more about the spice girls on this press tour than I have about the movie.
You went to Australia.
I did. I know. I wept.
Did you really wept?
I really did.
But now which one was talking to you?
Melby.
What she really told you was a message.
No, it was a video message on an iPad.
And that made you cry.
Yes!
Were you jet lagged?
But I also...
You do understand because we're in the UK.
I was a fiend.
I was obsessed with the spice girls.
And they taught me about girl power.
And I love them.
I think they're fantastic.
And I...
What's the song?
There's so many, Jamie.
There's so many.
That was a good one.
No, I'll set your life.
Every boy and every girl.
I'll set your life.
No!
There's so many.
And they're so fantastic.
And today on the radio, Melcy talked to me over Skype.
Oh, wow!
So it's really very exciting.
Okay, that...
Who would you say is your favorite spice girl?
Emma Bunton, baby spice.
She's your favorite.
She's my favorite.
Who's next?
Oh!
Do you have to do that?
Just a question.
All of the other four.
So Emma Bunton?
Well, Emma Bunton was the one that I had blonde hair and bangs.
And my name, obviously, is...
Now Emma.
My name was Emily, but it was taken...
When I became an actor.
And so...
Now it's Emma.
And, yeah, I just...
I love...
So give me this.
So you won't give you a video message and want to talk to you on Skype.
Yes.
But are you telling me you've never met a spice girl?
Are you gonna do something?
Have you never met a spice girl?
Are you gonna do something really?
I'm... wait, hold on.
I have to mention I compare myself.
Have you never met a spice girl?
Not in the flesh.
Okay.
Now, as you know...
Go!
As you know...
As you know, Emma...
It's very rare...
It's very rare for more than one spice girl to appear together...
For any reason at all.
So, they're not here.
Oh!