The man is...
She is a...
Yeah!
Yay!
Oh!
I'm dead.
Amy?
Okay! You got me!
Alright!
Don't twist my arm!
She's a queen!
She's Louise!
I feel something twisted.
Alright, so, Dad jokes?
Hit me with that.
Sizzes, paper, rock.
Oh, okay.
Sorry, I'm not chanted.
Which fist ways?
Oh, rock.
Sizzes, paper, rock.
Oh, here you are!
I'll come first.
That's hurt you always too.
I always do.
I um...
I gave my chicken by Agro.
Alright, now my chicken lays hard boiled eggs.
Hard boiled eggs.
Don't encourage them.
Okay.
Alright, I'll see your chicken joke.
Yay!
Louise!
Alright!
Something's raised, I don't know.
I made a chicken salad the other day.
Yum.
It turns out chicken's hate salad.
I don't know if that was a joke or if she was trying to fuck you.
Oh, that's not what I'd be.
Oh, um...
I feel like I'm already red and I have to touch drinks.
Okay.
That's the happy.
Slap.
Still at all.
Cheers.
Don't want you to drink alone.
That's Louise's every evening.
I ain't no loser.
Yeah.
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Pretty mature ejaculated.
I think Jack.
Louise.
Check his pants.
I'm wearing black, it's okay.
Oh, no.
That's a drink.
Was that the entire joke?
The churro ejaculator who?
No.
No, no.
I already finished that joke.
Everybody drink.
Oh, a little bit.
We need because you...
Oh, that's a sweet one.
Okay, he's trying to black out right now.
I brought my other chocolate blasts too.
So did I.
This is fun.
Is it bad that I start drinking as soon as the kids get to school?
Or does that make me a bad teacher?
Yeah.
Oh.
Everybody drink.
We've nailed it.
Okay, I would...
I would've loved for you to be my teacher.
Yeah.
Cheers.
So, I had sex with one of your food delivery robots.
It dropped off...
It dropped off its load and so did I.
I refuse.
You refuse too.
I refuse to laugh at that.
Oh, fuck it!
Oh, my god.
It's not bad.
Woohoo!
Big money.
So, way more anyone knows that I was expecting a hoose.
Oh, no.
He's fucking the real one.
Okay, I guess...
He's a sport.
He's a little man.
He's a little kidy.
That's why there's a robot in our Airbnb as well.
He had that in a robot.
What's going on?
I can't believe it.
The robot's like, please...
dismantle me, start.
That's dirty talk.
What's that?
Oh, my god.
You know, it's really hard to be an adult star when your electos intolerant.
The cream pie is really messing with my stomach.
Oh, shit, my pants.
I'll shoot my pants too, because I'm lactose.
Okay, mutual pants.
Okay.
Can we try another one?
You want to try another one?
No.
I'm not going to do it.
Can we try another one?
You want to try another one?
What do you call?
That was good.
Did you love?
I'll take it.
Take it up here.
Yeah!
Woo!
I'm not going to stop.
I just laughed again.
We're going to do that.
That's too easy.
I'm going to stop.
I met this Chinese porn star.
Shit.
Oh, the SharePoint.
She...
I met this Chinese porn star.
She gave me a wool hand job.
Oh, my God.
It's over for us.
Woo!
Oh, my God.
Shit.
Everybody.
Yeah.
Let the photo.
We're here now.
We're in it.
Yeah, but...
Let's find out.
Why are you looking for that?
Let me tell you about the Chairman Pro package.
The ultimate grooming experience,
which features the Chairman Pro electric foil shaver.
Featuring a 360 degree,
contouring head, which comes with two interchangeable,
skin-safe blade heads.
You good?
Still need time?
You've got that skin-safe,
full-blade foil for that super-close shave.
And the skin-safe double trimmer.
If you want to keep that landing strip trimmed,
both heads are designed to reduce razorburn.
So you're feeling smooth and comfortable.
The package also includes the power shave gel.
For the ultimate wet shaving experience.
Dan, I'm going to keep going.
The Chairman Pro package is a perfect gift for you
or your step-brothers Christmas balls.
It's got everything you need to keep your face
and anywhere else looking and feeling its best.
Use promo code YearMad for 20% off your order.
Plus free shipping.
That's 20% off.
Plus free international shipping.
With promo code YearMadAtManscape.com.
Danon.
What has one horn and isn't magic?
What? What?
A dead unicorn.
Oh.
You think you got horny of that job here?
I was horny from the start.
Okay, let me try another one.
Here you are.
What?
I laughed, I laughed.
He wants it.
I'm the follow.
I'm the freebie.
This is the game now.
Oh my god.
Do you know what my favourite pawn categories?
Tell me.
It's a Covid just turned 19.
Oh my god.
You said Covid.
You said Covid just turned 19.
Covid.
You said Covid.
No, Covid.
That's my second favourite.
We're in.
Hey.
Where did it put me?
I feel like I need to just cross my legs.
Yeah, just relax your ass.
Hold on.
Don't, I can go back to the hotel.
Just relax.
For some people,
nine months doesn't seem like a long time, right?
But for some, it seems like a maternity.
That's great.
You can come and give it to someone.
You can have it a little.
Yeah.
I feel like right now,
when I take a shot, she takes a shot.
That's fun.
Oh my god.
It's a good thing.
So I come from the land down under,
whereas in your use to people coming on your land down under.
I feel like in.
Hello, you're not used to that.
I come from the land down under.
Oh my god.
Sing it.
Sing it with your chest.
Like Joey Chestnut.
Oh my god.
Sing it loud.
How does it go?
I come from the land down under.
I feel like I do those layers better than those trillion people.
It's a good thing.
Alright.
So, we're going to kind of express the other day,
but it wasn't food.
It was just even falling down the Hollywood hell.
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
That is crazy.
Oh my god.
Holy shit.
That is crazy.
Dana, you're an adult film star.
Sure.
So you're quite thin.
But I couldn't do your diet because it's just nuts.
Oh my god.
And some fake.
Come on.
Get me some credit.
Have you got tips?
Yeah.
You got me.
I'm skinny.
We need more cream pot.
I got this later.
Who cares?
Oh, she's so good.
Did you hear about the guy with a fruit fetish?
He's bucking bananas.
They love that.
A fruit fetish.
That's good.
He loved it.
I feel like we're both agreed that we're just going to like...
Drink every time.
I love this.
So I refuse to believe I'm gay.
You know, don't let it go.
Yeah.
I refuse to believe I'm gay.
I'm in denial.
But I think he pronounces it Daniel.
And he was in me.
You're in denial.
Yeah.
I just found out I had a stepson.
How do we get rid of this all the career?
Oh my god.
Okay, well I guess.
It's part of what we're doing now.
Is that...
Could someone call me a new bird?
Call us a new bird?
Oh god.
Could someone to call me?
Get him out of here!
He instant into a pimfton.
He's absolutely roasting me up here.
I guess someone helped him.
Yeah man, he's...
She's a friend of mine.
Yeah!
That's what we show.
You're on the team.
What did this idol film star have for lunch?
Me?
Five guys.
There's two different girls!
Oh!
Yeah!
Oh my god.
I guess.
It won.
Yeah!
I'm gonna give it a try.
I'm gonna win.
That's not it.
He's on the team.
Yeah!
Oh that's the best.
Oh I love you man.
I have a chance at my mom.
Woo!
Hey, baby!
You guys are so sweet.
Oh my god.
At least you know the thumb man.
Woo!
That was the best.
That was the best episode.
Thank you so much.
You're amazing.