What do you call a blonde that is still in the closet?
I don't know.
Last year's hide and seek champion.
I don't get it.
I don't know.
Hey, exactly!
LAUGHTER
Oh, f***!
Oh, shit!
You see you too. You ready?
Yeah, ready. You excited first time, dad jokes table.
Dad jokes. Never time dad jokes before.
Oh, really?
A lot of memories on this table.
Wait!
Where the f*** did everyone go?
LAUGHTER
Oh, my goodness!
What the f*** are these guys?
LAUGHTER
Hey.
Yeah, who's that? Who's that? Who's here?
Oh, my gosh.
OK, so who?
I saw about that killer stage.
All right.
LAUGHTER
This is fate by rock.
Oh, OK.
I'll go first.
All right.
So I don't know what makes you laugh.
I'm going to...
I'll start off easy.
Yeah.
And then I'll go into the most f***ed up shit you've ever heard.
Yeah, that's true.
OK, so, why should you never take fungus on an aeroplane?
Because it smells?
No, because it takes up too much room.
LAUGHTER
That was really good.
That was really funny.
OK, OK.
No, that was good.
That was good. That was good.
Yeah, yeah.
LAUGHTER
That was off?
Yeah.
Keep the ginseng off.
That was a mistake.
Do you know that Bruce Lee had a brother who was a vegan?
Go on.
His name was Broccoli.
That's good.
Oh, I'm sounding bad!
Oh!
Broccoli!
LAUGHTER
So...
Oh!
I'm only careful when the guys are back.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's my first time.
Any other household?
She drove me.
Yeah, I know it.
Yes, I was down here in Uber.
She's fine with it.
The Uber driver's driving to me over there.
That's all good, but...
I went into the codec store to steal something.
Yeah.
But I couldn't. They were cameras everywhere.
LAUGHTER
That was...
That was a lot.
That was a lot. That was a lot.
Oh, don't...
Oh, fuck.
You're so...
So the first time you got to go with...
Oh!
I make my mom...
I make my mom cry all the time, all right?
Oh!
Oh, man!
That's good.
Oh!
No.
That's in your roasts.
OK.
So, I'm blaming you the staff here, you're the man.
Thanks, Ben.
No, you're the staff here.
No, no, no.
So, my Hawaiian pizza the other day.
I should have used a low-hear temperature.
Oh, come on, I'm just following you.
That was pretty good. That was good. That was good.
Yeah.
It's so awkward.
Talk me sad if you were in the back club.
Any dude you spoke to would have liked me.
Yeah, exactly.
Here's your bag.
I gave an Afghan purse to my daughter.
And she went, thanks for the bag, Dad.
Oh!
That was so good.
I have a doughnut apparently, and that's it.
Fuck bag.
Oh, my God.
You like it?
You finish it?
They're gonna get way worse.
OK.
What's black and always in the back of a cock-cub?
Rose of waxed.
Now start again.
Go again, go again.
Go, go, go.
What's black and always in the back of a cock?
What?
The seat.
Oh, yes, yes.
Oh, it's coming.
It's coming.
What do you call an Indian who does not identify as any gender?
Non binary.
That's good.
Did you get that from the comments?
I swear I read that in the comments before.
You still joke off.
I don't really know.
This lazy fox just got through the comments.
I hear it.
All right.
That's so fucking crazy that South Canary did.
That's so fucking crazy.
What's 12 inches long and hard in the morning?
Wait, don't tell me.
Not South.
What do you call her?
The thing is that.
How do you call me just like that?
That's like a six-meter pot, that thing.
Six?
You can do that.
12 inches is insane.
You had a four-kilo four-skit.
Oh, thank you.
It's four kilos, but it's very small.
It's very small.
What card is an Iranian dictator drive?
A sedan who's saying.
I wrote that.
You wrote that.
I wrote the comments.
I think I saw it in the comments.
That was me, comedy.
South the best.
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Cargo.
Cargo who?
Low-south.
Owls go who?
Cargo.
Bip-bip.
My car goes.
The most polite car.
I'm just polite.
Do I need it?
Yeah, do it.
What do you call an Indian dating site?
Kadek.
Kadek the dots.
Oh my god.
I hit.
And now the racism comes.
Oh fuck.
I'm a lady.
Yeah, same.
Can we just say, Peyton has a name on her phone?
She's like, what's your name?
Peyton.
What?
Oh wait.
Are you alright?
Yeah.
Quickly, quickly, have some vodka.
That's classic stuff.
Classic stuff.
That's like how do you get up?
Is it my turn?
Yeah, alright.
So a man walks into a zoo and he looks around and there's only a dog there.
It was a shitsoo.
Yeah, I got to take that.
I'll take that.
That's good.
Why was six afraid of seven?
I was going to say seven, eight, nine, but that's...
10 scared.
Because he was right in the middle of 9-11.
Oh my god damn.
Oh, oh, oh.
Oh he's back.
I'm back baby.
Oh yeah.
That's a well-written joke.
I don't know.
Peyton's gone down like towel one.
Oh, me too.
Oh my god.
I'm sweaty.
I'm fucking sweaty.
Oh my god.
I'm sweaty.
I'm fucking sweaty.
That's my turn.
Okay.
Why English people bad at chess?
Why?
Because they lost their coin.
Why can't the US play chess?
Why?
Because they lost their towers.
Hey!
Oh man.
That was...
Call back.
Why can't my little brother play chess?
Why?
He's not allowed any bishops.
He's back baby.
Yeah.
That's a pretty good joke.
Can we get some more fun?
No, can we?
No.
I'm Kiera me.
Someone has to drive my car.
Sure gun.
Yeah.
You get it.
I'm not.
Oh fuck.
That's alright.
Get him back.
You're in the bad rating.
I'm not.
Alright, Blondjax.
A few Blondjax.
Oh fuck.
Here we go.
Hey.
He blocked.
What do you call a blonde that is still in the closet?
I don't know.
Last year's hide and seek champion.
I don't get it.
Exactly.
Oh man.
I'm not.
You're like a man up.
Yeah.
Wow.
Alright, you're done.
I got it.
Now I've got the fucked up shit coming.
Oh.
What?
Oh or I feel like I've said my best ones.
But anyways.
Do you know what's clarious?
What?
Catching a boss.
That's what I'm.
I run that one myself.
You run that one.
It's just like, you know it's funny.
Because I never tried it before.
Even if you will money your transport.
You know what, I think it's so funny.
You know what, I think it's so funny
when like poor people catch buses.
LAUGHTER
Oh, sorry guys, I just got to make a quick call.
Hello, is Mr. Wing there?
No. It's Mr. Wong there.
No.
I guess I winged the Wong number.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
That was so funny, man.
That was good.
That was all act out.
That was really good, man.
That was amazing.
Let me do another one.
No, that was a lot.
You loved it.
I loved it because we were so dumb.
I'm sorry.
You were a funny girl.
LAUGHTER
No.
That was cool.
What's the difference between Michael Phelps and Hitler?
Well.
Michael Phelps can finish a race.
Oh, my God.
That's like...
Why are you not even talking to this guy?
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. That's...
At least five laps.
No, I don't love.
That was shaking. You're on it.
Am I?
It's the closest he's been to boy woman in a while.
Yeah, my mom would be so unhappy right now.
Some of the labels is the movie South West.
LAUGHTER
There are eight years against you.
You feel safer, right?
Well, I'm good, but again, I'm really good.
You know what?
Yeah, I signed a consent form before I went in.
Nothing makes a girl feel safer than God.
Hey, you feel safer.
You're like, goody, yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm good.
Yeah, you signed a consent form, so it's like...
Am I really?
I'm really, really...
Oh, my God.
Go, bus, go.
Bus, go.
Um...
Like they said, boss, not boss.
Can't be a boss on it.
Exactly.
You can be a boss on a boss.
Can you?
Yeah.
I call.
Don't worry.
Why couldn't Stephen Hawking play basketball?
No, no, no.
Because he's white.
But...
So, I think it's right.
I can't play.
Rachel.
I touch kids.
Fuck that guy.
That's it.
I'm going to see myself out of here.
You said I touch kids with their own hands.
Okay, you made me laugh, son.
Did I?
Yeah.
I love that.
This is the craziest one.
I don't think I've been on a crazy...
Is that what you're doing?
Yeah, this is great.
Yeah, this is fun.
Okay.
Soak spring the children, but which bird prevents children?
What?
Swallow.
Oh.
That's a boat for swallowing.
What do you call a line of people at a gay bar?
An LGBTQ?
That was great.
No, it's good.
The line of funny, but you like it.
You have one more.
This is really dumb.
So, a Spanish guy, right?
Do you speak Spanish?
See.
See me, man.
Okay, so a Spanish guy goes to Ireland and he walks into a bar.
And he sits down at the bar and the Spanish guy turns to the Irish guy sitting there and goes,
What's your name?
And the Irish guy turns around and he's like, it's Michael O'Brien.
And the Spanish guy goes, What?
He said, Michael O'Brien.
Go to the Spanish, so I don't get it.
But if you're Spanish, you get it.
I'll tell you something.
Hey!
Okay.
All right, well, you still laughed.
I did laugh.
What do you call an Asian guy with a big ***?
A sleep, because that motherfucker's dreaming.
Oh my God.
Fuck it.
Cut the tape.
All right, last one.
Last one.
I'm not even going to show it.
All right, all right.
You made me the whole.
I felt like I was talking about nature.
Oh my God.
Okay.
I said, like, say a joke with an awkward joke, I appreciate it.
What do you call a white man with a big ***?
Michael Jackson.
Hee hee.
I can't believe it.
Oh yeah!
Woo!
Yeah!
Another white woman winning in life.
Fuck yes.
I'm sorry.
What are you fucking you and camera?
Hey!