It might be the end of our friendship, Pamela.
Come on.
It's...
Hey!
Hey! How's it going, mate?
What's with this... the get-up?
I don't understand the reference.
I just thought maybe you'd like to film more at home, you know?
It's... I mean, it's crazy, because I...
I don't even know how you knew that I went to jail.
I barely ever bring it up.
What's up looking at?
Yeah!
Holy moly!
I was jailburdened!
I was jailburdened on it.
I was...
I was jailburdened!
Oh, damn, I got caught. Look at the jailburden again.
No, in Australia, we wear green in prison instead of orange.
Is that why you're in green?
Is this green?
Yeah.
I call it more teal, I don't know.
Anyway, it's a wee thousand jo...
We'd like to go first.
Oh, it says a paper-ocky?
Ah, sure, we can go.
It says it is paper-ock.
Why do you do it quietly?
It's so weird.
It says it is paper-ock.
Get it together!
Why are you making that face?
You're like... not even one.
What face?
Oh, my gosh.
Just... you start.
I can't give up with this, it says paper-ock.
Why are you gated so rude?
Why?
Because they're fucking ourselves.
No, that's my best joke.
All right.
Ah, this is not funny.
I'm not going to do it.
This is not funny.
This is not going to go well.
What kind of jokes make you laugh?
Because I'm going to need your guidance.
If I'm going to get you to laugh at you, please.
Good to be here.
Go ahead.
Why was the parrot in prison?
Oh, we've got jail jokes.
All right.
Why was the parrot in prison? Tell me.
Because it was a jailbird.
You know, you're a type.
I went to a paraplegic strip club the other day.
The place was crawling with pussy.
No.
For...
You're tough, Abbs.
You're a role model.
You're tough.
If they don't crack it, they're my best stuff.
Who never minds being interrupted in the middle of a sentence?
A convict.
I've just got prison jokes.
I'm really sorry.
If this is triggering, you can let me know.
No, that's all right.
I've got mostly jokes about prostitutes.
So we really went for each other's jugular?
Yeah.
Did you hear about the rapper who only battled when she was on it?
No.
Did you hear about the rapper that only battled when she was on her period?
They said she had a mean flow.
I like that one.
I knew I was going to lose this, but I didn't think it would be this comprehensive.
Comprehensive?
It's 3-0, why is it a moment?
Yeah.
Why is a white guy in prison scarier than a black guy in prison?
Tell me.
Because the white guy actually did it?
Oh.
Well, you did actually deal drugs in there?
I did, but they were the good drugs.
And if anyone needs any out there, I'm not allowed to sell them for another year.
Did they actually?
I'm just going to wait.
The bottom of the Yamad merch mailing list, you'll see it.
I'll be extra option.
Take that box.
Have you heard of a reverse exorcism?
It's when the devil tells the priest to get out of the child.
Oh.
Oh, my gosh.
Oh, fuck.
Well, here we are.
Here we are.
Cheers.
What's the difference between a Jula and a prison guard?
A Jula?
Mm-hmm.
One watches cells and one sells watches.
I've got one of those kind of jokes.
Go on then.
What's the difference between an epileptic oyster fisherman?
An epileptic oyster fisherman, yeah.
And a prostitute with diarrhea.
One sharks between here and onefish ducks between here.
Fuck that shit!
One sharks between here and onefish between here.
That's three sharks.
Mhm.
Uh.
One sharks between here and fish her with two.
Yeah, see if you got it!
Yeah!
LAUGHTER
Oh, no!
How's that going?
LAUGHTER
This is the new...
Yeah, Mad, Drinking Shorate...
Shocklasses.
Cheers.
Do you know what Mrs. Doubtfire served time in prison for?
No?
Male fraud.
I thought you were going to do like a robbing movie.
Where he was in prison.
In person, actually.
Hello!
Coming in.
Well, like...
What do you call getting gonorrhea from a handicapped person?
What?
Slow clap.
You know it's bad if Ben makes a...
Oh, no, sir.
It's so bad.
Have you ever slept with a disabled person?
Ah, death go.
Yeah.
How could you tell...
How could I tell you she was death?
No, that's not what I was going to say.
Because she was lip-raining.
Your lips.
You are lip-liquid.
You know what I asked, that's on me.
You had sex in my mate's kitchen and...
She fucked off the dive-dark.
Sell us the store.
She's death, she didn't know how loud she was being.
Are you sure she was like...
It was from pleasure and not like...
How could you tell her she was screaming?
No, no.
That was not an invitation to do an impersonation.
Is it your joke?
It is, it is, yeah.
A man escaped from prison.
What are his initials?
S-K-P.
Mm-hmm.
It's clever.
I tell you know it's a good joke when no one laughs,
you never goes, that's fun.
I like that.
Why did Michael Jackson have an allergic reaction?
Did the impression first?
Do you know why he had an allergic reaction?
I won't, I won't hear it until you did the impression.
He got stung by a bee.
Bee.
Why is that just a blind hand?
She's asking for it.
I'll be working on my 10th, thanks for noticing.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
I wanted to say, if you just need to be resting and be bee on your belly.
Yeah, be good, it's so good.
Yeah.
Are you getting it?
It's so hot in here.
What do you got?
What do you call a drug dealer that shows up on time?
Great and...
I can't.
A cop?
Yeah.
Well that's insulting to the drug dealing community I think.
What's very punctual?
Where are you?
Very punctual.
Service with a smile, punctual.
Service with a smile.
Good drugs, good value, great customer service.
That's how you get ahead.
Are you doing an odd breed right now?
What is this?
And that's what Andrew Hamilton's drug dealing service.
Good a mushrooming dog coke.
What do you call a Serbian prostitute?
What?
Slumber down my cocky bitch.
You heard of Slumber.
Slumber.
Have I heard of what?
Slumber down my cocky bitch.
That's not what you said.
You changed the name halfway through the joke.
No, that's his real name.
He's real name, so it's a male prostitute.
No, the old leader of Serbia was Slumber down my cocky bitch.
And the Serbian prostitute is Slumber down my cocky bitch.
Pretty good.
What's the difference between an escaped prisoner and an orphan?
Only one is wanted.
I think we've had a few of those kind of wanted orphan jokes before.
Oh yeah.
It's a real great subject for us all, considering none of us are orphans.
I know it's just hard.
What's the best part about having a hookah dog?
Don't definitely have to take a shot.
Sorry, I was taking you shot for the laughing.
What's the best part about having a hookah dog on you?
What?
The second hour is free.
You were shaking the table so hard that you could spill it.
That's a real...
South of Lanzadil.
You like that one?
Yeah, nice one.
Why did my dad go to prison?
Your dad went to prison?
Why?
Beats me.
That's pretty good.
He always asks about the bruises on me and I just felt like he deserved an explanation.
Why are non-alcoholic beers like going down on your sister?
Why?
Because they make tastes the same, but it doesn't make it right.
Do you have a sister?
Three.
Do they all taste the same?
None of your business.
Shouldn't be yours, mate.
We're very close in Hamilton family.
How do you maintain your professional network in prison?
Via lockdown.
Oh, it's like LinkedIn.
Lockdown.
It's a lot of puns based on prison.
Where...clever, where'd play?
Yeah, I'd play with them.
What are you called children born in a whole house?
In a whole house or a whole house?
A whole house.
Gotcha.
Brothel sprouts.
That's good.
It is good.
Oh, I go in.
These are shit.
That's the thing.
I'm really going to throw that thing.
Thank you, Shar.
No, I got it and got something.
Thank you, Shar, though, because that was a love apparently.
That was funny.
What's another name for coming inside a woman?
What?
You look worried to say the answer in this.
It might be the end of our friendship, haven't we?
I want to hear the joke again.
What's the joke again?
I've forgotten you've been laughing for so fucking long.
What's the name for coming inside a woman?
I'm a terrible woman.
Yeah.
What?
Loading the dishwasher.
That's not funny.
We run that.
That's terrible.
What's the difference between Disney and porn?
Oh, what is it?
Disney teaches you to hate your stepmother.
I love stepmother porn.
I cannot talk.
Clearly, it's an awesome Disney movie.
It's going up.
Have you heard that hookers don't fart?
No.
They do little prostitutes.
You remember, like, two videos ago when you were like,
they're called sex workers.
This whole thing has been hookers and prostitutes.
I thought...
Just saying.
I thought it'd be funny.
Respect the business, you know?
Oh, I do respect the beers.
What did you just say?
Follow me on Only Fans.
I'll shout about it.
Are you done?
Are you tapping out?
No. You got more?
Yeah, I got more.
I've got...
I've got so many more.
I've been full paid for them.
Brood.
Go on, on, on.
Thanks.
One day, yo. Oh, no, you did win one.
I beat Matt once.
Go off.
Hop off, King.