The other big Hollywood news is your stand-up tour.
In almost like a demovie itself, is now inter-induced with sitcom?
Yeah, I did the stand-up show in America
and some HBO, which is a TV network over there, came up and said,
you know, what do you think about doing it as a sitcom?
And my stand-up show was about my failure to find a wife
and general pathetic life as a loser.
And they thought, yeah, we want this on TV.
And so that's what we're doing.
It's not going to come a huge dilemma, though.
When they say, too, we want to turn this into a, you know,
a six-part, you know, like masses and masses of series,
that if you find a wife in that time, you ruin your career.
Yeah, he'll keep her in a bunker.
It's sort of where he already does keep her.
LAUGHTER
No, it isn't. Yeah, you're right.
I mean, it's not a documentary, so I could theoretically be married
and still be acting the role.
It's going to ruin your jam, though, mate.
It would really, it would really be.
Yeah, yeah.
It's fun, OK.
You're just wishing on me a deep and miserable lonely life.
So the laugh keep coming.
LAUGHTER
Is one of the episodes, is one of the episodes
going to feature that sort of hideous wedding experience you had?
It is. It is. We, uh, yeah, I, I mean,
I thought I'd met this woman of my dreams at this wedding.
I was at a wedding and you know you get stuck sometimes on a table
with people that you don't know.
And there was this girl opposite and she was dynamite
and we hit it off.
But I was stuck next to this couple, Oli and Lisa,
and they had this kid, this toddler, in a high-chair,
just sat there like that, just, eh.
Just bashing this big red stick and stuff.
And, um, and the mother wouldn't recommend
if you just kept going, what's she like?
What's she like?
And she was exhausting and she, she would just dominate the table
with these stories.
You know those people looked just, they're not really stories.
It was, it was all that, it was all for you.
Um, went to the, I went to the, I went up the, um,
the, um, the, no, no, no, no, no, the, um,
supermarket went to the supermarket.
Um, did a big, did a big, um, shop, did a shop.
And then I got back to the checkout
and I'd forgotten the purse and I had to go home for it.
LAUGHTER
That was it. Honestly.
And I was thinking, if, if that story was making its way
out of my brain towards my mouth,
another part of my brain would have stepped in and gone,
eh, where the hell are you going?
LAUGHTER
This is all wedding. I don't know what this is.
This is just some bullshit.
She was wet right now.
And then her husband, who's quite a posh bloke, pips up.
When he goes, um, I recognise you, where do I recognise you from?
And I was trying to impress this girl, so I said,
oh, I did this TV show called the office.
And he went, oh, the office, yeah, I've seen the office, yeah.
Not my cup of tea.
I'll tell you where you're going wrong with the office.
LAUGHTER
And said, not much story.
I'm thinking, yeah, because you know about stories,
because you're married to bloody Charles Dickinson.
LAUGHTER
And it's important.
But that's not the reason I've looked at this girl.
I, so this toddler is sat there the whole time, right?
And we're having some soup.
And for no reason, this kid just took his shoe off,
just lobbed it in the air.
For no reason, it came flying down.
It landed in my suit.
But I swear, just no one else has touched.
I'm covered in it.
And the mother, Lisa, just went,
oh, wassy like.
LAUGHTER
And I said...
He's like a f***ing...
LAUGHTER
APPLAUSE
Do you know you've probably seen it?
Harper's Bazaar.
Harper's Bazaar, posh magazine.
It's a new sage in town.
Yeah, there is a man at the back of it.
What would you like?
Harper's Bazaar to their, the most powerful women.
It's their 2009 list, the most powerful women
in British theatre.
And look at this picture.
How fabulous.
Do you look there?
That was one of the funniest ten-minute photo shoots I've ever had.
That only took ten minutes.
It felt like I literally had ten minutes to run into it.
And we was like...
Stand like...
I don't know, that's me in the meantime.
The wind was blowing, the lights, the everything.
And we had to like...
You and Rosman Pike.
Yes.
She's so beautiful, isn't she?
You both are absolutely gorgeous.
Completely manufactured that.
It's all post-production.
But I photo...
You know, Photoshop.
That's what it is.
I'll get in a stony way back.
LAUGHTER
Go do, sorry about that.
Yeah, I shot the one.
Hang on, they're going to mark a pen.
Coloring in the hair.
Yeah, exactly.
What's the reason?
Because in the research, you know, so they did the research.
The research that you did before I came on, you mean?
Well, that's somebody did.
Yes.
And...
You know, it's got the lists of various things.
And it's got, you know, most powerful women in theatre,
Harper's Bazaar, and then throw it down the list.
And this is like how your life has changed.
Previously on it, Outmagazines list of celebrities
who people would like most like to drink their bath water.
Yes.
I know.
You were quite high up on that list.
I know. I think I was number one.
Number one?
I was number one. Yes.
Oh, no!
What is it that you put in your bath that makes it so tight?
Just me and all my oils oozing all over the place.
LAUGHTER
Who the hell was number two?
And may I shaving?
Oh!
Oh, come on. That's delicious.
I pay a lot of money for that.
And when you do theatre, when you do due to pays,
do you get the kind of the science fictiony people coming?
Yes. Yes.
Which is good as well, because they're exposed to a play
they wouldn't have seen.
That's true, yeah.
I mean, don't put that on.
Yeah, all like that.
It's good for them.
But are you a believer in things like the X-Files?
I don't believe the X-Files existed.
I think it's a massive conspiracy to keep nerds
at their computers.
No, I don't really...
I don't really feel for any of the kind of conspiracy stuff.
I don't believe in any of that.
All that moon landings never happened, kind of conspiracy.
You know, 28% of Americans don't think the moon landings happened.
In fact, you don't think the moon landings happened.
I'm sorry, if you could do that in 1969, yeah.
Like, we can't do anything now, what do you mean?
It's like, I'm just sort of changing Hoover bags
into the Earth and the night.
As soon as we can get to the moon, we'll find all these amazing
devices.
Well, no, we'll be able to make a phone call.
I'm doing that.
When you, as a child, you assumed that things would be better
than that.
We live in the future.
Oh, yeah.
And we always told that at any point, about 30 years from
wherever you're talking, you're going to have jet packs.
Yes.
Monorail of flying cars.
Where are they tomorrow's worlds?
Where are they?
Yes, sir.
I'm still sat here.
Why isn't Graham having to talk to me out there?
Yeah.
As I float about the place.
And also, Graham, that's an interesting question.
How trapped.
Why do we even have legs still?
Why haven't we evolved?
That's why I think maybe things like that,
those conspiracy things might be true.
I don't know.
Anyway, look, the reason we're talking about this is you can't hang on.
Because your toast is not good enough, people
think go to the moon.
Toasters are getting worse.
They are.
They used to be great when I was a kid.
Now, too many settings.
If you know, it's like the burnt or raw.
But it got raw.
It's so good.
You told me to rip.
What's that?
How many of you said it?
One of the great things about toast is it can be eaten raw.
We know the harmful facts.
It's not the same, though.
Anywho, ran over.
What we did is we asked the audience what sort of presence they got.
And some people, in fairness, they didn't get, well,
they didn't get great presence.
I've got some of them here.
Now, where's Fabian?
Fabian Devo.
Now, this Fabian, oh, hello, what?
No, what?
Fabian Devo.
Somebody gave you that.
That's true.
You gave me this?
My ex.
Your ex gave you this.
Yeah.
Now, do you have a dog?
No.
So, how did he explain it?
Well, he said that at the time in the show,
it was a lovely ball,
and that I think of my cereals in the morning.
LAUGHTER
Is this a weird sex game, Fabian?
We supposed to wear a collar at the same time.
So, how did he react?
You opened a dog bow, what did he do?
Well, you go, oh, I love dog playing.
How did he react?
With your positivity, you slap him in face, I'll tell you.
I'll tell you.
What do you see?
Do you see a dog?
I am not a dog.
I am a man.
I am a man who tries his hair from one side.
LAUGHTER
It's beautiful.
Now, this, this is really pissed,
but this is what you're talking about.
Oh, I love it!
LAUGHTER
Mango and papaya!
Oh, I've often...
Have a time, Joe.
You said it the other night.
He said, so often, mango on its own.
So, I select it.
I see mango, I want you and your name.
I love it!
Is that lovely?
Who bought this?
Oh, you, their lovely lady.
Who gave it to you, first of all?
My husband.
You.
You're still together.
Just.
And why was it a particularly bad gift?
I'm allergic to shower, Joe.
LAUGHTER
Did he know you were allergic?
Yeah, I think you did.
We're being together 21 years.
Do you swell up or something amusing when you show up, Joe?
You're a red and scratch.
That's funny enough. I'll give a shout out.
LAUGHTER
Game for a laugh?
Yeah.
It's lovely.
But presumably...
Better presence now, sir.
Not really, no.
Travel, Noughts and Crossies last year in Toronto.
Travel, Noughts and Crossies.
This is a game that you can create yourself.
That's a secret.
You're in bed.
You've given someone a pad and a pen.
No, you've gone to see a travel north, so cross it.
Oh, it's an electrical.
Oh, save paper, my friend.
That is lovely.
I stand correct.
But you like it?
No.
You've brought it out with you tonight.
I love it.
Just a bit, yes.
Any kind of travel at all?
Are we off, darling?
Let me fetch my travel, Noughts and Crossies.
These lights seem to be taking quite a long time for fans to
play the game of travel.
Oh, no.
You're on Amba.
I win!
Very exciting.
Look, I don't know who got this, but Nick...
Look, I found you a cat.
What's wrong with this?
You think this was yours?
Well, I give that to Nick.
Nick, you hold onto that.
So you've got it when the motorbike arrives.
Okay, there you go, Nick.
Okay, handy trainers.
They'll come off like some quick.
Okay, so you've got a cat.
Who else have I got?
Right now, very quickly, we got an email from someone
with this picture.
And I think it's...
Let's have a look at the picture.
This is the gift.
This is Kelly.
Oh, no.
Now, it's Kelly's here.
There's Kelly.
Hello.
I love Kelly.
Looking at her hands, like...
I love it.
Like you've never seen that picture before in your life.
So your husband...
Your husband bought you that outfit.
Thinking you'd like it.
I think Kelly's face says it all in the picture, really.
Because it's as if, sir, you went into a shop
and said, I'd like something suitable for my wife
to be buried in.
What is it?
Is it supposed to be pajamas?
Yes.
It's like a baby.
Do you think they're going to be sexy?
Not at all.
No.
At least it does say angel on the tith.
So it's like...
It's sort of...
It's harsh of nice.
We were going on a winter holiday, you know.
It was cold.
I don't think anyone's that cold.
Unless you're at six months old.
So did you have to open up for ten to be pleased?
No, I did not pretend to be pleased.
Well, listen, sir, you're obviously not very good at choosing good presents.
So I thought I'd give you some experience of a good present.
Would you help me test a good present, sir?
Sure.
What's your name?
Neil.
Okay.
What it is, somebody sent me this phone, right?
And they make extravagant claims about it.
So nice and on.
Let me just check that it's on.
Yes, it is on.
So if you take this, take this phone.
Okay.
They claim, right?
This phone will operate under extreme thermal conditions.
So it's very cold outside to agree,
something just being there.
Very good.
So if you follow the camera there,
I'll ring you as you're walking,
and then we'll see if it's still working when you're outside in the cold.
All right.
So now, I've got the number for that phone I hope I do.
Six, six, seven, seven.
Okay.
It's calling.
It's ringing.
Hello, Brian.
Oh, hello, Neil.
I'm here.
Okay, bring it.
It's not cold yet.
Oh, yeah.
So, keep walking to you outside.
I am.
They threw a door out into the cold.
There you go.
Now, can you still hear me?
I can still hear you.
Okay, stop around there now.
Now, Neil, that's very good.
So it's a Sonom XB3 and Juro, apparently.
The world's tough as phone.
It's not just thermal conditions.
They say, they make other claims for the phone.
It says here, Neil,
that it's a water and liquid proof.
All right, yeah, okay.
I guess.
Oh!
Oh, no.
Neil.
Yes, Brian.
Can you hear me now?
I can hear you now.
It's not a free barbell, apparently.
It's also dust and micro particle proof.
All right.
Can you hear me now?
I can't see anything like it.
And that last thing, it is that ready-resistant
to shock an impact, Neil.
What?
Can you hear me now?
I'm going to have to go.
Well, that's Neil.
Wow.
Can you enjoy it?