You really were a blue coat, weren't you?
I wasn't blue coat, yeah, at the place you showed.
Which was next door to Heisham Nuclear Power Station.
LAUGHTER
I think it is. I got sent there because I was...
I worked a really good one in Yarmouth, great Yarmouth.
Got sacked, which is another story.
And then sacked and then...
What?
..and sent to... We'll move on to that in a minute.
Sent to this one.
Sent to that one as a sort of punishment.
It was like, you're going to Morkham to do six months.
Because you have just...
You've just done something which...
What had you done?
Well, something that was considered cheeky in the 70s,
but now is illegal.
LAUGHTER
Oh, wow.
No, that's not true.
It was actually an incident where...
It was my first attempt at stand-up comedy.
And what happened was I...
I'd always wanted to do stand-up comedy.
I didn't have the guts to do it.
I got very drunk.
I had to go at doing it as a blue coat.
My mate said to me,
just copy all the other comedians at Ponton's and steal the jokes
and basically talk to the front row.
So you're supposed to say, were you from?
They say Scotland, you say who paid for your holiday,
were you from Wales?
You make a noise like a sheep.
Rubbish jokes, all right?
But I said, that's terrible.
He said, don't worry, you're just padding.
What you're doing is you're looking for comedy gold,
which is, were you from?
They say Kent and you say,
what did you call me?
Right?
Now at Ponton's, this used to take the roof off, right?
LAUGHTER
So I tried it, but I was very drunk.
So I go on stage and I say, were you from?
The splot says Scotland.
I can't remember the joke.
LAUGHTER
I say, hello.
Then I said to the, were you from?
The guy says, Wales, I'd black out and I go,
hi.
Hi, panic.
And then I say, anyone in from Kent?
LAUGHTER
And this splot shout, so me.
And I said...
LAUGHTER
Well, you're a f***er.
APPLAUSE
LAUGHTER
That's so, that's so...
That's so...
LAUGHTER
So I miss it.
I'm such a moron.
LAUGHTER
That's...
Fifty Shades darker.
But actually, this isn't darker.
It's more romantic, I would say.
Yeah, I think that's probably true, yeah.
Yes, but there's probably more sex in it, which...
LAUGHTER
More sex?
It is.
Jamie doesn't speak.
LAUGHTER
I make noises.
I make like...
I'm not very good at accenting noises, though.
No, there's...
You know, there's actually a question, though.
Do they let you do that?
I mean, like, when you're...
When you're doing the scenes, does the directors say...
More vocalization?
I mean, there's often...
There's often so...
Ah!
No, that's not good.
No one comes like that.
LAUGHTER
That's all I do.
That is you.
Like we do, man.
There's some scenes where...
They will play music, maybe, a bit of it.
If it's a wide shot, and it's not like...
So, it's the closest we get to sort of kind of...
Sort of just sort of going forward in one piece,
and they'll play music or something.
And my temptation is always just to try to make the cuttle-off.
So, sometimes, I'll do things like...
When there's a moment where I'm meant to, you know, orgasm,
I'll be like, do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do-do.
LAUGHTER
People do that.
Which, by the way, if they don't, they should.
It's not a Ryan Airflite when a Ryan Airflite lands.
Give it a little...
LAUGHTER
Oh, yeah.
Well...
And was it nice of you this time?
Because last time it was you and sort of everyone else
was a woman, the director, or whatever you...
But this time it's a man directing, that makes a difference.
No, not really, to be honest.
I mean, I think whoever is tasked with directing those kind of scenes,
I mean, you know, these guys know it.
Sex scenes are awkward, anyway.
And it just needs a very...
This wild love, how?
Because he includes me in... Yeah, you know.
These guys know sex scenes are just really hard.
It's like, no, babe.
No, you know what?
Ever done a sex scene?
What?
We've been in so many films.
I know.
I'm from somebody at some point.
No, no, no, no.
Not in Back in the Harvest? No.
I might have been on a couple of people under that habit,
but...
No, no, no, no.
Why is that your decision?
No.
This is based on your life.
I mean, this is things...
Yeah.
Loosely, Graham.
There were things like, isn't the washing machine that happened to you?
What?
The washing.
You were very hungover.
Oh.
Yeah.
Tell Tony Foster, that story.
All less toys are really cool, though, Graham.
When I was teaching, which is what this show is based on,
I went home one weekend, and I was in my 30s.
I was probably 33 years of age.
I went home to see my mother, and then I went back.
And while I was at home, my mother did my washing for me,
because I was only 33.
And then I went back.
On the Sunday night, I got really drunk,
and then I went for a curry.
And then the next day I went into school.
I'm going to.
I went into school, and it was a school in Slau,
and it was quite a rough school,
and I was really brilliant hearing impaired department,
so there were hearing impaired kids who struggled.
They really looked after in the school.
Anyway, I was really hungover.
I went there, and at about break time I felt really uncomfortable.
I thought something's not right, you know?
So I went to the toilet, and I pulled my trousers down,
and some of my mother's necks have got mixed up in the washing.
And I was wearing my mother's underwear.
And I went, oh, God, no!
I remember going, oh, are you loser?
It's such a low point, you fucking loser.
And then the curry and the booze kicked in from the night before.
So I did like a fecal Jackson Pollock.
And I started going, oh, God, not this.
Not this as well.
Oh, Jesus.
So I cleaned myself up, and I pulled my mother's pants back there.
And I went back into the classroom,
and I saw one of the hearing impaired kids just looking at me like this.
And that's when I remembered that I had a microphone directly.
LAUGHTER
I couldn't have seen it.
Here we go.
APPLAUSE
LAUGHTER
So maybe, man, down isn't that far fetched.
John, for you, obviously,
lovely that Emily wants to be in the film.
Absolutely.
But as a director, is it then weird giving your life partner notes?
It was weird, because I was very nervous about, to be honest.
I think we both were.
Before we started shooting, she said, are you nervous?
And I said, I'm terrified.
And she said, oh, good, me too.
I think it's one of those things where people think
because we're both in the same business, we have the same experiences.
But I've actually never been on set with her, seen how she worked.
I'd heard she was a diva, and I just...
LAUGHTER
I can't get Emily out of her trailer, stuff like that.
It's like, oh.
And no, but I think what it was is...
And it sounds really sappy, but it's true.
I think it's the greatest collaboration I've ever had in my career.
I've never seen her work.
And when you are actually in the room when she does what she does,
it, honestly, it changes the air in the room.
Everyone is just completely and totally stunned by what she does.
It's all...
The sneer!
But I can't really hear you off.
I have to say this is what...
This is what I actually learned early on in our relationship.
Was it British people are notoriously terrible at taking compliments?
Which you agree? Just like...
LAUGHTER
I always thought, oh, guys...
Oh, that's actually what she did.
People are saying, it's like, I just want to get out of the way.
I'm a huge fan of yours and...
Oh!
I was like, oh, no!
Later!
You weren't cool at all.
There was none of that.
Actually, I don't know your work.
You were a proper fan of it.
Oh, I'm going.
I was full stock or status.
Yeah.
I was just like, hey, you want to go out and date with me?
No, tell me, but how many times have you seen Devil Wars Prada?
I mean...
Not 75.
Give or take 72.
No, it's one of those things that back in the day,
us elderly people used to channel serve.
And no one does that anymore, but...
What's that?
LAUGHTER
Like I said, a painting tool.
Oh, it's just one of those movies that whatever...
Whenever you're going through the channels, you just stop and you...
I mean, look.
Has anyone seen the film here?
Probably.
Do you know that there's...
There's a sort of montage sequence where Annie Hathaway's got
numerous fabulous outfits that they go through.
And John, one day, I came home and he was watching it.
And he was watching the montage, but then he goes...
And...
That's my favorite outfit.
LAUGHTER
That's not in the meanies.
Oh, I couldn't get Annie in so I'm like...
LAUGHTER
You're talking about that.
You're talking about the new album, Bush.
And a very sexy bit of PR, of course, that the mighty Farell...
He co-wrote...
Do you write all the songs?
He produced the whole album.
Produced the whole album.
Yes, sir.
Wow.
Is it true that Farell, he was the one encouraging you
to be a bit more family-friendly, a bit more mainstream-wise?
Yeah, yeah, he...
Made me change certain words.
I had a song called So Many Holes.
He made it So Many Proves.
LAUGHTER
Well, that certainly toned it down.
On prose, just prostitutes.
No, they're professionals.
Oh, I see.
LAUGHTER
Silly me.
The ladies in the video still look quite like hoes.
LAUGHTER
They're professional.
They're in a video.
And then Farell, is it true that he...
I mean, I'm sure he enjoyed working with you,
but he did have some difficulties working with you as well.
Yeah, and when we were working on a particular song
called California Raw, Stevie Wonder,
he came up to the studio and for real,
he called a second hand contact
from being in the studio with me.
And he kind of froze.
He didn't know how to produce it anymore.
He was stuck. He was like...
Might have to explain what the...
Yes. So Farell was in an environment created by Snoop.
LAUGHTER
Farell was no longer the same Farell.
It's not the same.
Yes.
He was now someone else.
LAUGHTER
He was not the greatest producer in the world.
He was the greatest producer in the world.
He was just a guy in the room.
LAUGHTER
So was Stevie Wonder trying to talk to him?
Stevie Wonder was in the mic booth.
Yeah, you know Stevie can't see.
So Stevie was waiting on some direction.
And Farell was again, you know,
directed for Stevie, which is in there just...
This is weird.
I don't answer this question if you don't want to matter.
But I have...
I don't know why you brought this up,
but I did hear you discuss...
an extraordinary disagreement with your wife about yourself.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
By myself, you mean...
Yes.
Oh.
Listen, have you known this story?
I do not know this question.
Well, as you do, we were talking about stuff.
I've done...
I just have no interest in, and of course,
being circumcised, I said.
LAUGHTER
They were chatting. They're married.
They're allowed.
And she said...
She said,
You're not circumcised?
I said, what do you mean?
You've only known me a few...
All my life, I remember my mother telling me why,
because it was fashionable at the time.
She said, You're not circumcised.
I said, That's ridiculous.
I should know if I'm circumcised.
Of course I am.
End of conversation.
Next day, I happened to be seeing my doctor.
LAUGHTER
Are you okay?
I was seeing my doctor for my annual physical, of course.
So...
Well, he was down there.
LAUGHTER
I said, It's getting dark, by the way.
Erve.
My wife and I are in a little disagreement.
I am circumcised, I'm high,
because she says, I'm not.
And he goes...
LAUGHTER
Not.
It's not possible.
So he looked down again and he said, Hey, I'm Jewish.
I know the difference.
That is a bizarre story.
LAUGHTER
Oh, God.
I have grandchildren.
LAUGHTER
You're going to have to change your Facebook status, isn't it?
Yes. No more beef stew.
Well, there's more beef stew.
Because when you were starting off in wrestling,
you had a persona that, Am I right?
Well, sort of half-man, half-machine.
Yes, that's correct. Yes.
It was prototype. It was awful.
LAUGHTER
So you want to try to find a persona, or here's some more
inside Facebook, where a gimmick,
where it describes you as a character,
so when you walk out, people notice you,
and you can describe your character.
But these are not gimmicks. This is real.
Well, well, I mean, if they work.
Yes.
But you kind of...
It's a trial and error process with a lot of errors.
And my first try was the prototype,
which was half-man and half-machine,
and 100% crap.
LAUGHTER
But given that you're not half a machine,
how did you demonstrate you were a machine?
Well, I used this ability to talk rather monotone,
and would say things authoritative,
and just when I said I would kick your ass at the fairgrounds
on Sunday, I would rewind it and say it again for you.
I would say, I would kick your ass at the fairgrounds.
Did it work?
You know.
Oh, it didn't.
That's a good one.
Yeah, you've worked on one.
I have one.
You found you success as John Cena.
Imagine that.
I figure I need to come up with some sort of name.
Yeah, look, everyone...
Doesn't everyone...
Every wrestler has a name.
Yes, and people think that, like, hey, man,
how'd you make up the name John Cena?
It's like, no, dude, out of made up like Dick Hammerbush
or something cool like that.
No, Dick Hammerbush.
Or something, I don't know.
That's a star.
No, it's moving there.
No one's letting you go out with that, no?
But they actually think that John Cena is a gimmick name,
but no, that's actually...
Through all the presentation that is WWE, I'm stuck with Josh.
Are you wrestling fan, Jamie?
I used to love wrestling when we were much younger,
about the same time as Transformers, back in the day.
We had Big Daddy.
Yeah.
The giant haystack.
No, no.
No, I love it.
I love it.
I thought it was just fantastic.
By the way, I'm John Cena.
That was awesome names.
You know, you're the ultimate drooler or, like, nothing else.
I just like to have signature moves, I think.
Yes.
And one of yours is the...
You can't see me, but that's correct.
Is that true that came out of your family somehow?
Yeah, I was dared to do it.
So I was actually making the music for my own theme song
that you just so heard and finally serenaded me to.
Thank you very much.
And we played it for my brother.
And the first time he heard it, this was the 50 cents crew
had a really popular song called In The Club.
And he heard it the first time, and instead of dancing,
like, he was our litmus test to see what songs were good,
what songs were bad.
He did this.
Oh, my God.
And I'm like, dude, what are you doing?
He's like, no, everybody does this, man.
Everybody does this.
And I guess this was from 50 cents video.
And he's like, you won't do it on TV.
What the hell do I have to lose?
Am I going to fire me?
Of course I'll do it on TV.
But instead of doing this, I did this.
And now for 15 years.
Because of a dare.
I've been doing this.
And I'll do you one better.
People actually think I'm invisible.
There will be people to look at this couch.
And be like, why is there nobody next to McConnell, hey?
You said Joe and Cena would be there, but we can't see him.
So you never know.
You remember Hacksaw Jim Douglas,
and you King Kong Bunny, Skandar, Ack bars,
and Caravan Erics, and Carie the Claw,
I got a kick out of Hershkall.
Let's talk in Texas Wrestling.
I get kicked out of Hershkall, see him in Treyport,
for pelting Skandar Ackbar, the bag of tomatoes, on the Ackbar.
Skandar Ackbar was a man dressed as a sheep
that used to throw fire.
Yes.
And he managed King Kong Bunny,
who was like 484 pounds.
And remember there's Missy Leeds from Parton None,
and then Ah.
And then the Green Face, Spit Green Mr.
They sound really good.
Good stuff.
Yeah, they're entertaining.
Here's something I'm talking about.
And I'm John Cena.
And you've got the King Kong Bunny,
here's the Red Bull.
Hello.
Hi, what's your name?
James. James, lovely James.
And what do you do?
I'm a civil servant.
A civil servant, lovely, in London here?
Yes, in London.
And are you from the London area?
No, I live in London, but I'm originally from Suffolk.
Oh. Oh.
Yeah, mate.
It's a Suffolk Massive.
Yeah.
Isn't mentioned in the song.
Probably, yeah.
What school did you go to?
So, I went to Brandistan.
Oh, sweet, yeah.
I went to the primary school.
Yeah.
Okay.
Did we know each other?
Yeah.
Did we?
I'm not wearing my glasses.
What did you say, James?
I know.
James.
Yes.
Me.
That's the one.
What the fuck?
Do you do this with my best mate growing up?
You're giving him.
And now you're talking to him, me, on a monastery.
I'm not having my specs and he's like, oh my god.
Can we not flip him and just get him out of here?
Yeah, yeah.
Do you have a sorry or do you?
Well, yeah, I did, but it's okay.
Please let it be about edge.
It's about edge.
Okay, tell your story.
Then we'll flip you and then...
I'm a civil servant.
Okay, cool.
So, yeah, as Edward said.
This is so random, mate.
It's what it is.
Yeah, when we were younger, Ed used to come around to my house and yeah, like you're saying,
we used to be quite good mates.
And I remember one time he was coming around for tea and I forgot to tell Mum that he was a vegetarian,
at that point anyway.
And so Mum cooked, I think, the sausages and mashed for tea.
And Ed said, you know, after the meal, these are the best sausages I've ever tasted.
You know, where did you get them from?
Mum had to lie because she had no clue.
And so, yeah.
For 16 years later, I'm pretty sorry.
First time I ever had me.
And also the first time I ever watched a Simpsons episode was around your house as well.
Okay, well done, you've got to flip you now.
We can be reunited backstage.
Okay, okay.
Oh, okay.
There it goes.
It's coming.
I feel like Cilla Black on Surprise, Surprise.
There it is.
Come on.
We just, we just surrender me.
I'm gonna look something like you know.
Have a seat, have a seat, have a seat, dude.
One of the things you can do is you can conjure up people's fears.
Yes.
Okay.
So you, you're afraid of quite basic things.
You yourself.
I'm afraid of like most things.
Like anything high risk I'm terrified of.
But those irrational fears.
Okay, irrational is the spiders, because, but they actually, um,
I become paralyzed when I, when I have a spider in my room.
Really?
Yeah, I like wish I were tougher than that, but I'm not.
Okay.
Now, small rough low, we use serious when you told us what your fear is.
I mean, it is, it's a good fear.
It's, I think it's a founded fear.
I think it's a founded fear.
It is.
Tell us what it is.
I have a phobia of being chased around with poop on a stick.
LAUGHTER
Is that fair?
Yeah, I wouldn't say, I just say we've all got that fear.
There's another one that goes, not up for that.
It started when I was a kid.
It was just weird parenting.
For some reason, kids thought it was funny to stick a stick in dog poop
and chase each other around with it.
But that scared the crap out of me.
Because of the cleanliness problem of it, with spreading germs?
No, because of poop.
It's just dogs poop.
It's just a parade of sticks.
Now, Jeremy Ranado, yours is brilliantly specific,
and I think without knowing it, I think we probably all share it.
We may.
I don't know.
I didn't have the fear when I was younger, because we've all, we all go through this,
but it's when a little child, and I'm the oldest of seven kids,
and I got a lot of little rug rests running around,
and these little roaches start losing their teeth.
And they get a little wiggly, and they like to show me,
like this little dagger flipping in and out of their mouth,
and like, look up to Jeremy when it pulls his thing out.
I'm like, I can get out of here, freaking me out.
But do you think that is really freaky?
It's like her thumb.
It's just weird, it's just again.
No.
It's just really kind of grossed me out.
The cutest little thing on the planet starts to do, like, the creepiest thing on the planet.
And I'm like, get out of here.
I'm like, you're tied to string to my thing, to the door knob.
I'm like, get out of here, creep.
You got to see the animal?
I'm a little bit scared of this touch.
That's now.
No!
No one's running around flipping their little teeth fall on out.
Look, we all have this, you know, when you have the dreams, your teeth fall out.
I don't know what it means.
Anybody want to means?
We get bigger than ones.
No, you're bad dreams.
It's not the only one that is bad dreams.
No, we're your friends.
I've said the one I just had that dream too.
You said you were really, weren't it?
Yeah, not me.
What does that mean?
I don't know.
This is strange.
I'm sure of money, I think.
I think that's what the teeth fall on.
Who has fear of money?
Maybe I'm just afraid of my teeth fucking falling out.
That's right.
Josh, look at you up here.
What are you afraid of?
Well, advertisers are going to go with flying, but I think I'll go with...
Girls over 12?
Stop, stop, stop!
I'm not going to lie.
Come on.
Come back here, my brother.
I feel terrible.
I don't know what came over me.
I'm not going to lie to you.
The last minute of my life, I wouldn't have predicted that.
How was it, Mark Ruffalo?
You're not going to believe what he said to me.
He was bang on the money.
Very perceptive, man.
It was your darapalm.
Don't try and justify it.
Do you know what?
I've always hated the hulk, he's shit.
You're making me angry.
You're making me angry, Ruffalo.
My son stood up to me the other day when he was mad at me.
What do you like him?
I always hated the hulk, I think he's shit.
I think he just told him there was afraid of girls over 12.
For him, that would be okay.
He's a tough guy.
Hi, what's your name?
My name is Sebastian.
Sebastian.
Where are you from?
I'm from Newcastle.
Newcastle?
Do you live there or here?
I live in Newcastle.
I'll figure out where this was, Sebastian.
Many moons ago, I went to school in Newcastle.
There was a disco coming up.
There was a popular girl at school.
She was like a scenario, all the guys after it.
I waited for the last moment, last couple of days.
And as a girl, one of this popular girl had a question.
If she'd like to go with me, she said yes.
This was literally the day before the disco.
Lo and behold, turns out she was actually going to go with somebody else.
And that other person was actually Charlie.
Sebastian Lippiatt.
I didn't know.
I was just a minute.
How could this have happened to two people?
Rachel Gold.
They're very same.
Yeah, she know who it is.
Wow.
You look older than me.
Where does that image?
And did you end up marrying Rachel Gold?
No, not yet.
No.
Still time.
You know, it all happens out of a sword with you, do you?
You could ask revenge if you want to.
Do you want to?
There you go.
All of a year.
Oh, wow.
We thought we'd seen you play everything, but first which?
Mostly bitches.
My first which.
But here you went through a phase you got offered a lot of witches.
When I was 40, when I turned 40, I was offered three witches in one year.
And it was sending me a signal I felt.
Probably didn't know how they felt about people turning 40.
So I felt bad and it made me sort of, I had a little, my back up, you know.
And so, no, I didn't want to play them.
So lots changed in the last five years for you.
Oh, good, mom.
Good.
Oh.
You're right.
That's a nice smile.
That's a good smile.
I was looking for a fear of solving it.
That's seen in episode one.
The doctor's thing.
Yeah.
Did that really happen?
My mum will kill me for telling this because it was my, our family doctors.
And I, he'd been, my family, my doctor since I was a child.
But I went to, as an adult, because I was,
there was something wrong with my bum.
When you said bum, you looked at me directly in the eyes and I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I mean, I'm a rouse, done unnerved and you call me?
There was something, but there was something wrong with my bum.
I could see it was magic.
And I was, I said, there's this thing wrong with my bum and he went,
OK.
And I went, so what did he say?
He goes, well, it'll probably be all right.
And I said, well, I, I, I, I, which really like it.
I'd like you to just, if you could make me feel better about,
if I feel better that it will be all right.
And he went, it, it'll probably clear itself up.
And I said, yeah, but, is there any way I could be sure?
And he went, ah.
Do you want me to put my finger up there, don't you?
I'm sitting on it.
Not if it's not magically necessary.
And, and the other, I think, maybe, maybe there's a reason,
but what is the reason that you film it in the school you used to teach in?
I think it's therapy, probably.
I mean, that's a classroom where I taught,
because I was just to keep the theme going, a real teacher for a long time.
Yeah, but six years in the school that we film it in the classroom that I'm going mad in.
But that's really...
Well, that was my classroom, yeah.
But you did it for such a long time, did you ever enjoy it?
Was there ever a moment when you thought, oh, I like this?
Oh, no.
Okay.
Well, I met some very nice people there.
And the kids were so like, you were nominated for Teacher of the Year, weren't you?
Yes, I was great.
I was.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, yes.
I've told this story many times.
But Teacher of the Year is a very prestigious award,
that's taken very seriously and rightly by the hard-working teaching community.
And my head teacher called me in, and he was wetting himself laughing.
If I couldn't stop laughing for the first ten minutes, he went,
I went, what...
Why have you called me here?
He goes, you've been nominated.
You've been nominated.
I've got this.
I've got a Teacher of the Year award, you've been nominated.
And I went, oh, okay.
And it was by a very sweet girl called Gemma, I've humiliated many times.
And it's a six-page document that people have to fill in
for the reasons why you should be nominated for Teacher of the Year.
It was blank,
aside from one sentence that she'd written on it,
which was of the reasons why you think he should be Teacher of the Year,
and she'd written, he's a well-good laugh,
and he don't make us do no work.
Well, your character's name is Dr. Smolder Brevestone.
Yes.
So, all the characters have strengths.
So, one of your strengths is the Smolder.
An actual Smolder, yes.
It just takes over, and I have no control of it.
And did you know you could Smolder?
Like, did you kind of think, yeah, when you were doing your Reddit,
you got to go, oh, yeah, I'll do my Smolder.
You know?
I take you.
Is that it?
No, it didn't come, yeah.
Oh, okay, okay.
That literally is where it came from.
What you're saying, and this is why he looked at me,
because it's so frustrating.
Just go ahead.
Tell a story about your stupid Smolder.
No.
It's one of those things that, you know,
is we're developing the script and thinking,
well, what could be a fun thing?
Well, what if a fun thing, one of the fun things was he has this ability
to Smolder, and it just takes over him.
He has no control of it.
And it's just one of those things.
Graham, that God delivered, I signed for it.
And then, just do it.
And everywhere, everyone likes it.
And everyone loves it.
Except one individual.
Everyone loves it.
I'm going to tell you what it is, okay.
Now, we are very close.
We have very close his friends.
And, you know, in this position, he's a producer on the film.
So sometimes, I just bit my tongue.
So this idea came up from a producer like mentality.
Oh, you know what it'd be great for this character?
Well, I know I know.
If he's Smolder, not like what?
You know what?
You know, if he did a thing.
And I was like, what the hell are you doing?
Being like in the game.
He's like, it's a thing.
And then he's born and back.
He's like, my mom used to do it to me when I was...
When I was on the mountain.
And that's why we listened to him.
Because he's born and back.
Everything got tied back to Hawaii.
That's how he did it, Graham.
Well, the producer, can we see him?
Oh, I'll be happy to.
Greg, sit back for a second.
Oh, yeah.
Well, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, here we go.
Here we go.
Can we have a little music?
Maybe something that's a little ominous, maybe?
I can't hear you.
Wow.
Yes.
Here we go.
You can do it to me if I want.
I can do it.
Yes.
You're right. Here we go.
Beautiful.
Thank you.
That's a stage smothering.
That's the acid.
It's very impressive, yes.
But that cable...
Yeah, I'm not.
Oh, yeah.
It's pregnant.
No, we're having a baby.
I got revel.
From there.
From that distance.
Yes.
Rebels pebble.
It's good.
Yeah, it's a little rock.
That's good.
That's why you are, bro.
That's why.
You have it.
Obviously, you're not just a stand-up.
You're like a stand-up superstar.
You sell out of me as all over the world.
The best of our time.
Yeah.
I think that's a big deal.
That's a big deal.
But what's nice to know is...
What's nice to know is...
It wasn't always like that.
I don't know.
They're like...
What did you perform at the seafood festival?
I mean, which show you will know about it?
What was it?
At town don't know.
I think they wanted...
Was it crap?
I had a crab fest.
No, I had a crab fest.
A crab fest?
What is that?
And at the beginning of the stand-up comedy,
you're not performing in luxury venues.
Wherever they feel that they can build the stage
and make money is where you're going.
So there was a crab fest.
We're gonna book some talent.
A comedian talent.
That was like, oh, you know, I'm available.
I don't know if you guys have ever tried to tell a joke
while people crack in crab.
That's the best environment.
Literally, the frustration that comes
from not being able to open a crab is stupid.
You're not funny at the same time.
Enough that you hear.
I remember hearing a woman,
older lady who was like, she was cracking crab.
Because this is how you crack crab.
You know what I mean? She's like, crack in a crab.
Now, tell a joke and a joke doesn't work.
Now, remember this lady just going, oh, no.
I don't think I would much rather be booed.
Did this appointment mean it?
From her voice and then she said, baby,
it was like, oh, no, baby.
As if I made a mistake with my choice of life.
Like, I'm not going wrong.
You know, look, the hardship that I went through
has helped build me into the person I am today,
where I can take so much.
But I've been through it all.
I was hitting the face with a buffalo wing.
I performed at a catapult.
Don't perform around food for no reason.
I'm going to be going to show you now.
There's no food.
It was actually a male strip club
that they shut down for comedy for the first half.
It was a bunch of ladies in there.
And, you know, it was just supposed to be a performance
for these women that were riled up first day.
I got on stage when they introduced me.
And this lady was like, pull it out.
I said, hey, hey.
That's not me.
I'm not here today.
I'm here to entertain these dudes.
I know who's got kids.
I started trying to emerge into kid material.
And it went due from the back.
I didn't remember his due from the back.
He was like, that's enough.
And he just threw a buffalo wing at me.
The man hit me, hit me,
hit me in the cheek,
a little bit of sauce, got like, right here.
Buffalo sauce, hot sauce.
I assumed it was a woman with a deep voice.
I was like, who threw it?
Who threw it?
Because at the end of the day, I'm a man.
I'm a man first. Don't just expect me.
He stood up.
He was like, I did it.
And I contemplated just taking my clothes off.
I was like, I did it.
The only way to do that.
I collect, yeah.
Well, I collect stuff from movies.
Some of the movies I've done,
but really mainly Star Trek memorabilia.
Because I love Star Trek.
I'm such a nerd.
Have you ever been in a Star Trek?
No, I've never been in a Star Trek.
But I love the original series.
So I have the Gorn Head from the original series
from the episode Arena where...
I think I know.
I know. I'm just...
That was nothing.
Oh, the Gorn Head.
Oh, I am.
He was the owner.
The Gorn Head, Jack.
I have...
What the...
Is that a Gorn Head?
That's not something you can't even present.
What the Gorn is?
The Gorn from Star Trek?
We're going to give you the Gorn Head.
Oh, wow.
Do you have any of the Boulders?
I don't have any of the light Boulders.
I don't have a paper mache.
No, but I have Spock's ears from...
Oh, they actually...
They are.
Yeah, they're working.
They're working.
Yeah, very good.
But on Brightsmaids,
you did do a lot of proper bum-ding on Brightsmaids.
Did you like party nights and stuff?
We did a pre...
Press a pre.
The My Co-Writer, Annie and I had the idea
to get all the girls together
plus the script supervisor, Wardrobe,
like the women on the film,
to Bought 40.
There were a lot of people.
40 women.
It was pitched to me as research
because initially there was a scene
where we went to a gentleman's entertainment...
Yeah, parlor.
A strip, a guy's strip of...
A guy's strip club.
Yeah, okay.
So we got in a party bus
with a lot of...
A lot of booze, weird poles,
which I was thinking...
Did it have the disco lights in the bus?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, fabulous.
Yeah, and then we went to...
We went to a strip club.
And...
They did watch the show.
They did Vignettes.
It was not a back draft.
Yeah, it wasn't that...
It would all come out and like...
Fire mid stuff and then it was like...
Well, like everything had the same theme
and everything involved.
I seemed like every number had a duster.
They had a long trench coat to the floor.
A lot of equipment.
But they did do...
Do you remember the Matrix one?
The Matrix one, yeah.
Yeah, there was...
Somebody was playing Neo.
Wonderful.
There was a lot of long trenches
and guys and suits
and everybody had these very cheap glasses on.
But I couldn't figure out the...
One guy had a huge, huge thick rope around his waist.
And I was like...
I have not seen the Matrix in a while.
I couldn't figure out...
We were all like...
What's the rope about?
I don't remember a rope in the Matrix.
And they're like...
Do the synchronized dancing.
It's like all this are closes coming off.
We're like...
I mean, on and on.
I'm just like...
I don't get what the rope is about.
And then the big move comes where, you know,
the bullets come and he does the back bend.
Clearly, this professional dancer could not do a back bend.
So the big move was like...
All of a sudden it's like...
And somebody offstage is clearly holding the rope.
And it's clearly...
Now I can say...
He's like...
No!
And that was like...
That was like a stand-up model.
A lot of themes.
And now, Saturday Night Live also was a big bonding thing.
Now, because...
Do you know Leslie and...
Kate...
We met...
I think we met when I hosted...
Oh, no.
And we did a movie together.
And we worked together after that.
Okay, yeah.
Okay.
But now, you guys are still in, like, most people I'm sure know,
but it's a big comedy sketch show in America.
But how long have you worked together for how many years now?
It's been two...
After one.
Right?
It's been three?
Maybe three.
It's been three.
The first year, Leslie...
My name is Kate McKinnon and she...
I know that.
But she came up to me and she said...
After a year of knowing me...
You all right, Kate Middleton?
Oh, my God.
And were you joking?
No, I was not.
And I was like, my kid.
I was like, whoa, who's Middleton then?
She's like a princess bitch?
I was like...
I like her, baby.
I like Kate Middleton.
Oh, her hair is awesome.
And Kate, you did some great characters on Silent Live.
You're Justin Bieber.
You are.
Justin Bieber is spookly accurate.
Thank you so much.
That is incredible.
And did you...
You've done it in front of him, haven't you?
I have not.
We haven't.
I haven't.
I have not breached.
I met him before because he hosted SNL once.
And then that was before I started doing the pression of him.
But I was so struck by how...
This was before he got really beefy for those Calvin Klein ants.
And now he looks like, you know, a big beefcake.
But he was really...
He was very delicate and he very tender, beautiful, just up such a beautiful face.
And such a big, big hat.
Such a big clothes.
And just the most beautiful.
And I am a huge fan of his and I love it.
And now, you have a special way of...
A special way of preparing the face, haven't you?
Yes.
Yes, you want to look as though you've done something wrong, but like...
Yes, you do.
LAUGHTER
That is very good.
How old are you now?
I'm 77.
And I...
I don't...
Don't...
That is...
Oh, that...
I want to be a floc.
Say, you know, they're going to live longer than me.
You have to go, oh...
In New York, they floc.
I mean, it's a new apartment on the market, too.
I hate when people say, like, oh, there's 77 years young.
I met Vanessa...
Vanessa Feltz.
Oh, yeah.
And she said to me, he has, Joan, she's 77 years young.
And I want to say, and he has Vanessa and she's 350 pounds thin.
LAUGHTER
Oh, my God.
She has...
Yeah.
So...
Age...
Age sucks.
And you have to face it.
And you have these...
I've been on this show with some of these older women
that still try to look good.
No name, it's Goldie Han.
LAUGHTER
She's my friend, and she says to me,
would you believe I got a grown-up daughter?
And you go, yes!
LAUGHTER
And the lowest skirt, your nipples are showing.
There goes the Goldie Han booking.
LAUGHTER
No, age sucks, so you got a face.
But is it because America is really so youth obsessed?
I mean, how?
And in the film, you show, you know, kind of...
That it is hard for a woman of your age to get the job.
It's beyond difficult.
The only jobs really left now for women,
unless they get friendly with people to do films.
LAUGHTER
The only jobs that are really commercials.
I just thank God, I made my...
...early not this year on a...
a practical girlie, which is for Driver-Gyna.
And it's...
LAUGHTER
It may be.
Well, anyone knows the heartbreak of Driver-Gyna.
LAUGHTER
I was...
I was perfect for it.
I...
Kattles follow me home.
LAUGHTER
Three Jewish men are trying to rent my uterus
instead of going to Miami.
LAUGHTER
But...
And there's...
Thank God for these commercials.
There's one called...
A Zestra.
Is that coming in yet?
LAUGHTER
It's like women's...
Viagra has done happening yet.
It's women's Viagra.
And they have a big discussion with me.
Should they make it in pill form?
This is honest to God, truth.
They're in pill form or cream.
Because they didn't know which...
And they find a side of these idiots
will do it in cream because if it's in pill form
in a bar, a man can drop it in a woman's drink.
And she won't know it.
But if you're in a bar and a guy goes,
so where you from?
LAUGHTER
So, I'm...
I love...
I love for that.
I can wear a show too.
LAUGHTER
We do another thing.
We loved you as the Dini in a lap.
Oh, that was fun.
So, we thought we might have our very own
Genie on the show tonight.
So, is there anyone in the audience
who fancies a go at being a Genie?
Oh, look at them. They do.
OK, try you.
What...what's your name?
Yewren.
Sorry, what?
This name is Yewren.
Yewren.
Nice to have you here.
No, no worries.
Can I hear you a little too late?
You start frightening.
Oh, no.
Don't piss off Yewren.
OK, so Yewren.
Don't think of a magic word.
Right? Something, you know, it's just you, magic word.
And that camera three is going to do a kind of Zoom crash on you.
So, when I say go, you...
And you'll just do your magic word.
OK, so, Yewren, go.
Hi, Graham.
LAUGHTER
Wow.
How Graham I feel like we're in the middle of a telephone right now.
Yewren has learned to say hi, Graham. Thanks to your dollars.
Please help.
You'll learn another phrase by the end of the show.
Do you...
Should we try another boy?
Oh, actually, you're wearing blue already.
Yeah? OK.
So, into that camera, you're magic word. What's your name?
Nick.
Good Nick. OK.
A fan of Yewren.
OK, Nick.
Number three, and go.
Alicazam.
Wow.
It was almost...it was almost two words.
It was a bit like...
You're very good at that.
Yeah. Alicazam.
Time to dance now.
I'm going to dance with you and...
And, good Nick.
I'm Alicazam.
Jazz hands, jazz hands, jazz at all.
We're going to go, good Nick.
Good Nick, go.
OK, go, go, go. Follow the follow-up.
So, I'm just going to get my jeanie to help me.
OK, hang on.
Oh, yes.
I'm going to go back for creature.
LAMER.
OK, come on, Nick.
Good Nick.
Oh, there he is.
Yes!
OK, Nick.
Ready?
I need...
I need a lovely funky DJ console, please.
Alicazam.
Good luck, man.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Good work. Good work, Nick.
OK, I'll tell you what. Nick, you can come back into the studio.
Come back to the studio and help us in this thing.
Well done.
LAUGHTER
That's fucking losing.
That's that.
That was so great.
Yeah, right, I'm not exploding anymore. Thank you.
OK, we got to get into the DJ booth. Right, here we go.
Here we go. It's the Robin and Graham Road show.
Hello, sir.
All of the clubs.
OK, you go over there and I'm well done.
So, there's a mic there.
Then Nick.
Well, what's the music?
Nick, we're the shoutout right now.
Nick, we're not full of blue people.
Nick, go, keep it real.
Get ready for an Alicazam.
Alicazam.
Yeah!
Very good.
You hear that?
Now, I don't have any jingles on it.
So, it's the Robin and Graham Road show.
Could you do a jingle, a live jingle for it?
Welcome to the Robin and Graham, ready, y'all shall...
Nice to meet you.
Very good.
Let's back with a big shoutout from Nick.
OK, let's sit at Sunset, so-so here. Good evening, Robin.
Good evening, Graham. Welcome back.
Once again, we got some shoutouts.
I got one going out right now to Steven Buck.
He wants a shoutout to Jess, who's a best friend, and he says,
Stop texting him. He's not interested.
Yeah!
You're listening to the Robin and Graham Road show.
Alicazam.
No, you're ticked the jingle.
Welcome to the Robin and Graham, ready, y'all shall...
Where's the whisper shoutout?
The whisper shoutout.
What's the shoutout to Esther, best friend?
That bloke you pulled, don't worry about Toinder Remember's name.
You can do so much better.
Yow!
Whoa!
Where's Martin?
Marlon?
There he is, as Marlon.
Very well going to say, we'd like to shout out to his friend, Greg War.
Don't worry, girls love that you have got a third nipple.
Woo!
Oh!
Three nipples, ABC way to go.
Show it!
Shep's off!
Show the nipple!
Oh!
Greg!
Come on, little Newton boy!
What?
Well!
How many times have you?
You don't have two!
Oh!
Go, little nipple.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Yes.
First of all, I'm not a circus freak.
I'm just kidding.
Secondly, I will get my third nipple out on the condition
that Robin Williams comes and touches it.
Well!
There we go!
Oh!
This better be a real nipple.
All right, ready?
Here we go, ready?
Ready?
Let's see.
Oh, please, please let it be a nipple.
I have a third ball, too.
Ready, ready?
Here we go.
Oh!
I did.
Wow!
Round of on.
Six really did that.
I like that, man.
Just like that, the thumb girl is going,
you've got another one.
Play with my third nipple girl.
You've never had fun till you go third.
Once you've touched a third nipple,
things get crazy.
I get two nipples going, but when the third goes,
mmm!
The third nipple goes and then my fourth penis jumps out.
I'm like, mmm!
There is a gentleman, please, that I guess,
to like the fantastic Mr. Robin Williams.
Oh!
Where does it?
What would you now?
Surrapaptic, sir.
And you don't really use the surrmuch, do you?
Umm...
What should I...
Sorry, should I have been calling you...
No, I shouldn't.
Am I supposed to?
No!
Okay.
But do you...
No.
I take my lead from Sir Ian,
whom we've both shared some time with.
Yes.
And he is...
He is so...
...flegmatic about all of that.
And I just...
You know, it's a great honour,
to help something that I need to press.
When you bump into another sir, when you're writing about...
Do you then...
Do you...
Do you pull...
A few...
Well, you must roll in surr circles.
Okay.
Circles.
Oh, sir.
I just...
Oh, I just...
I just opened it.
Yeah.
For just a minute.
That was my answer.
I heard it.
Can I read the ignorant American in the ass?
So, how do you become a sir?
Well...
A Patrick?
How?
Well, you know, it's a case of...
...a long day.
No, no, no.
I got mine on the Queen's Birthday Honours.
But you have reminded me that I did have a sir encounter.
Only a few weeks ago in Los Angeles.
A rather fancy...
In fact, extremely fancy restaurant.
Tell them what it is, they'll know.
It was the Tower Bar.
Some sort of tower?
No.
No, yeah, guys.
The Queen.
No, no, no.
Sit down.
The Tower Bar.
Oh, man, it's a...
Oh, Europa.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
What?
It's a...
It's a Tower Bar.
Yeah!
Oh, my goodness.
It's a little narrow.
Oh, no!
Keep going.
Okay.
Well, not a Tower Bar, it is a spot.
I got a feeling this isn't going to work out.
It's a spot.
So, we had four of us were seated at a table,
about 15 minutes later, into the restaurant walks Sir Paul McCartney.
Wow.
Now, Paul and I have a very slender relationship,
but it lasted decades.
I first encountered him in 1964.
No.
When his girlfriend, Jane Asher, then, told him that I loved Aston Martin's.
I was driving a battered old Ford,
but Aston Martin's were my dream car.
She told him this.
And one night, we knew he was seeing the show.
There was a knock on my door.
And I said, yeah, come in.
I'm there in my underwear.
As usual.
I was a great people.
I hang around, that just in the hope.
I'm in.
I'm in my pants.
Yes.
I'm ready for you.
Come in.
And the door opened, standing there was Paul McCartney,
who I had never met before.
And this was 1964.
And he said, Jane says that you like Aston Martin's here.
Drive this.
Wow.
And he tossed a bunch of keys off the table.
And it was an ass.
It was his.
He threw.
Anyway, you want to hear the rest of the car?
Keep going.
We're in the fanciest restaurant in LA.
We're now in the Tower Bar.
Tower Bar?
Oh.
Oh my god.
It's a legend.
I am feeling less, less good.
Keep going.
You're in there.
The Paul McCartney's coming.
I'm ready.
He's in the 60s.
And he sees me and comes over andhil I stand up and say hi.
And we have a big hug in the restaurant.
And I'm very much aware that there's all the tables are full on this kind of thing.
And we talk for five or six minutes and he goes and sits down.
Five minutes go by and into the restaurant walks a ringo star.
I swear to you.
I'm not picking this up.
What were they together?
They were.
Oh, they were at the same table.
Well, they were the same.
Yes.
Well, we were at the Tower of Bartholomew.
At Tower of Bartholomew.
I am expecting so many free meals.
And we finish early and I get up to go and Paul stands up to say goodbye and we have a hug.
And this we have a hug.
He says into my ear, do you know a ringo?
I said, yeah, of course.
I've never met him but I'm.
He said, oh, boy, ringo, come on, come over here.
Hang on a minute.
He said, sir, ringo, sir, Patrick, sir, Paul.
Hey, we've got the Knights of the Round Table.
He's right.
He got that.
Yeah, he got that.
Yeah.
He got that.