Do you see all that controversy with Arnold Schwarzenegger?
Because he was saying he'd be willing to use face paint
for his new role as a tribal warrior.
He said the...
I'll be black!
Yeah!
Yo!
Trouble!
Oh, bro!
Thank God.
I'm just...
You only have to do that a little bit.
Yeah.
Oh.
Ah, it happened.
Baby?
Not much?
Yeah.
Do you know?
Do you just fill me up?
Yeah?
Here's to you.
Happy quanza.
Ah.
Sizzes paper rock.
All right.
Yeah, you can go first.
No.
Do you see that little robot from Star Wars got cancelled?
Yeah, he was R2 Meetude.
That was good a lot, that.
That little robot?
Nautiboy.
What do you call the wife of the hippie?
Mississippi.
OK.
I laughed for that a bit.
I laughed for that one like 2am last night.
That was a good one.
Yeah.
OK.
Mark.
Sorry.
I need to do Mark.
Did you hear about that princess that kissed a frog?
No.
Died in a cockroach.
Dirty bag.
Oh no.
My therapist says I should think of mental health like sex.
I always come first.
Can't you?
Pardon.
I'm trying not to.
Yeah.
You know who cares, right?
It's not real.
I really scream so much.
Do you see all that controversy with Arnold Schwarzenegger?
He was saying he'd be willing to use face paint for his new role as a tribal warrior.
He said, I'll be black.
I'll do it.
I'll be black, though.
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
I had to pay three grand for an operation for my dog.
Yeah, it did sound cheap.
That's so dumb.
Yeah, real frank.
I think you can get you go saffles like a hundred percent.
Oh my god.
Two fat eggs really hard to call that fucking five-boy.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know what it is.
Good boy.
That's a boy.
Let's put tit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look guys, this is how I used to trim my peeps.
I just have a fade, thank you.
Even busy or how's the shop been?
I'm a flat out.
Yeah.
But Andrew is here.
Yeah, did he?
Big boss, big boss on I go.
Big boss on that boy.
Yeah, George, watch that.
But now, with the performance package, 5.0 Ultra, everything's changed.
Thanks to this baby, the normal 5.0.
Wow.
They've taken position grooming to a whole new level with their next-gen dual skin safe blade heads.
Now a company by an upgraded Truman blade and an interchangeable 4 blade to enhance performance.
Performance package 5.0 Ultra and 20% off shipping plus international free shipping.
We're giving it all away.
20% off free shipping.
Get free shipping.com.
Get the performance package 5.0 Ultra and 20% off plus international free shipping
when you use the promo code YeahMad at menskate.com.
I'm at the King of England once.
If you count a gang bang in an orgy as a meeting, it's sex with the guy.
Is it a top, top, top, top?
Please be top.
You had to go either.
You were the one who did the wrong.
I thought, far.
Top of the maroon.
We did it.
What's the difference between marijuana and pussy?
If you can smell weed across the room, it's good weed.
Swap.
Ooh.
I think I retracted.
I went to the diarrhea convention the other day.
Boy, did that play stink?
He's so bad.
Is that count? That doesn't count.
That counts?
No.
He had like a little giggle.
But on the scale of me laughing.
That's like, yeah.
Just as for me.
Ooh, up you now.
Oh.
Okay.
I like my women to be like a pair of swim goggles.
So the tight wet and on my face.
I'm sorry.
I go off and jump off.
You're a graduate.
I just drive.
Are you scared of monsters?
Yes.
Because he comes the tickle monster.
I'm so sweaty.
Fuck, I can't.
I can't.
I'm actually a bit scared of that girl.
I wouldn't have a touching.
Oh my god.
I've taken more shots than an American school.
Okay.
Yeah, these cricket tracks are going to fall real hard with this current.
What the vegetarian...
Fuck that.
Why do vegetarians give a good head?
Because they're used to eating nuts.
I didn't laugh either.
We're good off.
Yeah.
No.
He looks like a doing cricket.
I changed it.
It needs to eat now.
Why is China so good at cricket?
Oh, fuck.
They take out every country with one bat.
Oh.
Oh, wow.
What do you call a nun on a bike?
A virgin mobile.
I really like that.
It's giving me a horde house, like in the Seven Ears world.
I was watching a film with my dad.
And I'm like, Dad, is that lady going to die?
He's like, judging by the size of that horse's cock.
Yes.
A painful death.
What the fuck?
That's it.
Pretty much.
What choice have I made last?
My sister is mad at me because of Fakty's girl.
What?
How he had it?
What's that?
My sister is mad because I Fakty's girl.
I wanted on camera.
Take it again, Brian.
What's this?
My sister's boyfriend.
My sister's boyfriend is mad at me.
I'm not this girl.
It's going to suck.
I'm getting it like this.
How the fuck are you?
The asshole hits Matt like...
He goes boom.
And then just...
Oh my god.
Let's keep going.
You lost your option.
Why?
Oh, I did it.
I fucked the joke before.
Oh, how you doing?
I'm training.
I like my women.
Like I like my microwave.
Ready to kill any baby I put inside them.
Reheat.
Good.
That's good.
You can send to your mate David Water.
Why?
Why is Johnny Best so so bad at ironing clothes?
He's always leaving a crease.
You guys don't get it, but the Krigger fans.
David Water, message Southland.
Here's some Krigger truck now.
I got it.
Oh, it's okay.
Everyone's got that.
They're taste.
How does a Muslim close it all?
It slams it.
It slams the door.
That's not good.
It's an accent.
Fucking fuck.
I'm going to come off to me, man.
I'm from via somewhere.
Do you only know Irish accents?
Hey, what do you call a girl standing in the middle of a tennis court?
A net.
Bro.
Fuck you, shout out.
My name is for having sex next door.
So I knocked and I complained.
Can you be a little bit loud?
Can you be a little bit louder, please?
I'm trying to have a wink.
Are you being so slow?
Yeah.
This is fucking dope and off.
Okay, good.
Golf one for you.
Fuck off.
Some people out there like sports.
What does a wanking have in common?
Four-pudding.
I swear you.
You learn on the green and then you try to get the ball full time.
It's very embarrassing.
It's a golf thingy.
The first guy in the art cell we like never leaves.
Fuck you, that's me.
Four-pudding.
I'll tell you about four-pudding.
Well, when I was your age, I used to be the four-pudding master.
I'm at my first sex wife, 32 or four-pudding.
I once had sex with this guy and he had a full latex cover-all-body suit.
And everything fit him except his glove.
OJ Gibson.
All right, what about this?
That Gibson's.
Here's a show over.
Amy!
Yeah, yeah.
What's the difference between a hamburger and a bona?
You're not giving me a hamburger.
Hello.
Good morning.
Yes, that's exactly where my jeans are ripped.
Hey, Matt.
Yes, go ahead.
Did you see that there was that Irish guy who got stuck in a river in the Middle East?
Tell me more.
But he wouldn't admit it to himself.
He was in denial.
Oh.
In denial.
What's the difference between golf and sex?
What?
A bad hole won't get you slap across the face when you play golf.
That's slow, that really badly, probably.
What do you get if someone comes in your eye?
Good, Dom.
A stick magician.
That's good.
Good time.
That's all.
Fucking hell.
You better bottle up five, boy.