Was it a honeymoon couple on a plane?
Yeah, there's a couple on a honeymoon.
And the plane hadn't yet taken off.
And the woman who just got married just
became violently and horribly ill on the plane.
I mean, it was not a pretty little sick bag kind of thing.
It was just like, I'm going to paint with my organs.
Like, it was just crazy.
And people were freaking out all over the plane.
And so they brought a stretcher down,
they put her on the stretcher and they're wheeling her away.
And like, her new husband is just kind of cruising along
with the thing.
And he sees me and he's like, Deadpool!
No way!
High five!
And I'm like, I don't want to do you.
Like, what has she got?
Like, what's happening?
You know, like, he's like, let's touch eyeballs.
No, no.
And by the way, your wife is like half dead.
Half her!
Half her, man!
So it was just a very surreal moment.
I'm sure they're fine.
I'm sure they're on their second anniversary now.
Just kicking it somewhere.
That's such an embarrassing thing I have to be yesterday on the tube.
So I've always said, you know, like,
oh, anyway, right, basically, what happened more?
So I was stood on Oxford Tube platform.
Yeah.
And I've always got, so you know, like, a glass keep cup.
You know, like, rather than going to a coffee shop and getting a new cup,
I carry a glass one that I then wash and we get my latte.
And so I got me empty cup and I just stood up down stuff.
And an elderly gentleman was walking towards me on the platform.
I was just like, oh, God, I just want to get on the tube.
I ain't getting recognised.
And he said what towards me?
But then he had his arm out and his arm came into my space.
And on the tube, on the platform, it's crowded and it's a bit,
I don't know, I just got the can of light.
Oh, what are you doing?
A bit aggressive, unnecessarily.
And actually, what I was doing was he went, oh,
sorry, I thought you wanted money.
And he was trying.
Oh.
He was going to put 10 P in the cake cup.
LAUGHTER
I knew, and I thought, I was like, yeah, oh, God, oh, man.
Oh, I thought it was true when I just sat there.
And I was like, someone make high contacts.
So I can tell this story.
I was like, wait, I'm just someone.
I was like, mm-hmm, no, we got really good story.
Because Dwayne, presumably, you can't hide.
You can't put a hat on.
You can't put a hat on now.
I mean...
But yeah, I've seen you in a gym, like a public gym.
So do you get to get bothered all the time?
All the time.
Yes.
But how do you work out...
The end of the minute he's gone out the window.
But how do you work out in the gym if people are constantly giving me up to you?
Just be nice, say hello, get a moving...
Get a moving.
Lipsome.
LAUGHTER
But fame isn't funny thing, right?
So that story for you will...
That will be like the constant anchoring reminder, right?
Of like how cool fame is, but also never like...
I don't have the stress you have, though, because I think the thing is...
If you are five or six, and you've got a hat on,
and you dress like a...
Most of the time, a teenage boy and a baseball cat.
He's...
Headphones on, head down.
I catch the bus and the...
I catch the bus in the subway every single day, because...
I'm not in anyone's eye line like that, but I imagine...
You...
There is something about...
If...
If you're...
You can't...
You're seven feet tall, though.
So, yeah...
But Kevin's had weird...
You've had weird fans...
Well, what happens if you're three foot two?
Like...
Wait, how do I say it?
How do you...
How do you do that?
I'm talking about...
No, how do you deal with that when you're doing that?
Five, two.
I'm sorry.
I don't think...
Well, first, there's two.
We're skipping around some points here.
First thing...
She's saying she's dressed like a teenage boy.
That...
Somebody had to put money in your cup.
It's got to be a lot worse tonight.
50 hours.
I'm putting in the little song...
Something...
Something with the near parents said,
I need to help this person.
Make sure they eat today.
Something that...
For me, I mean, it's bad.
And because I'm a big deal.
It's...
It's just...
You know, as I followed, was it in a restaurant where you followed you?
Oh, my God.
I had a guy actually following me into the bathroom.
It was a true story.
In the storm, you know, I got to go.
And, you know, a guy while I'm in the bathroom,
it's like, can I get a picture?
And I'm like, you know, because I'm obviously a very big guy.
I stand up for myself for me, and they say,
Hey, not in here.
You wait until I'm done, okay?
You go outside.
I'll take you with you when I get outside.
And I go on the stall, close the door.
And, you know, you would expect whoever that was
to have left.
They're gone.
And I, you know, I do what I got to do.
And there was one of those situations
where I had to be in there for a while.
And I'm in there.
You know, literally, you know, when you get comfortable,
you start to take your time.
And I'm on my phone.
I'm scrolling.
You know, it's a comfortable environment.
That's what you do with the mall.
That's it.
I get done, and I like get out the stall and close the door.
He's right there.
He's like, you're in there for a while.
He's like, can we get the picture?
And I was like, I'm in outside the bathroom, man.
I'm not taking the picture with you in the bathroom.
But the fact that he stood there, like, very nicely,
though, it made me feel obligated.
And I was like, hey, just, just come on, selfie.
I was like, don't tell anybody you saw me in here.
You've been friends with Jason Statham ever since.
Yeah.
But I'm distracted by the makings of a...
Cocktail.
Oh, yeah.
It's a cocktail at Christmas, everyone.
Yeah.
You know, cocktail?
Shall I?
Yes, please. Now, what have you brought us?
OK, well, I like to give Britain a little tip every now and again.
So you need to find yourself a sheath, right?
Now, this is...
Hold on.
I don't know if I want dead drink.
If you go to the really posh cocktail bars,
you get these incredible ice cubes that they hand carve.
Oh, no, no, no.
We go get a water bomb, right?
And we just split it, and we peel it off,
and we get a lovely round bear with me.
This is what they do with the posh places.
Then we're going to make a Christmas negroni.
I know.
I think of myself as a Christmas negroni.
LAUGHTER
Only you could have said that.
I couldn't have gone away with that.
So, in the groany, I want you to think of it as medicine, right?
OK.
If you've got every one of us has someone a bit boring,
a bit sort of dodgy come into the Christmas party.
There's always one.
So then what you do is you take this negroni, aka medicine.
Medicine?
Right.
And it turns people that are a bit problematic and boring
into interesting people.
Whoa!
So, and the groany is 20...
What's Jamie trying to say?
I know.
And he's pouring three drinks.
This is 20 mils of campari, 20 mils of vermouth russos,
which we've sented with a little cinnamon and Christmas fare.
Yes.
And then we have a little gin, a little bit of clementine to get you guys.
Are you ready for this?
I'm like, come on, man.
Now, once you sip this, if you don't become more interesting,
I don't know what's going to happen.
OK.
It's going.
Lovely.
It's like school.
Yeah, go on.
Oh, we have four.
We have four.
No, no, we're...
It's here. It's very Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
And this is very Christmas.
This is a bit like a Christmas carol, and we are scrooge.
Because like, Merry Christmas, everybody.
Merry Christmas.
It's like 600 tiny tins.
Yeah.
OK.
Oh, come on.
Come on.
Oh, that is delicious.
How come the weld's changing?
Oh, no.
Be the judge of whether or not it's delicious.
No, I like that.
It has just enough Christmas in it.
Here's the thing.
No, that's very good.
That's great.
You want to sit?
Hold on.
Oh, wow.
Here we go.
I drank from this side, so you could drink from this side.
You could drink from this side.
You got to do it.
You could see what you think.
Is this like feeding a gremlin after midnight?
That's good.
I'm not mad at you.
Yeah, it's delicious.
It's good, isn't it?
It's nice.
Yeah, that's good.
No, it's delicious.
Try that.
We've got our Christmas cocktail.
Oh, okay.
Oh, that's good.
Yeah.
Christmas to remember.
That was the Christmas O.
The underwater sequence.
Yeah.
That looked hard.
Oh, dear.
That was pretty difficult.
Yeah.
A Christmas to remember.
That was the Christmas O.
Yeah, that was pretty difficult.
It was a really technical, probably about a week at Pinewood,
because we shot the film here in London.
It was all underwater.
It's a sequence where this sphere falls off a cliff.
She and another actor by the name of Justice are stuck inside of the sphere.
And I'm on the outside of the sphere trying to rescue them as it sinks.
And it was.
Water is filling up the gyrosphere.
And at one point, we're completely submerged in water.
Yeah.
We spent, I don't know, eight week or eight days or nine days we spent in water.
And it was, boy, I'll tell you, they put a lot of chlorine in the water
because you've got a crew of 85 people just pissing this pool.
No.
Like, no.
Never got it.
No, no, no, no, no.
People, we didn't have time for people to pee.
So you knew people were peeing?
Oh, I'm certain of them.
They didn't look the most there faces.
Huh?
People would suddenly just...
Oh, I don't know.
I'm sensitive.
That was good pee face.
That's a good...
What am I doing that again?
Thank you for that.
Yeah.
She just made me think a little bit.
Yeah, just make sense.
Yeah, I think I'll do a little bit when you...
Well, I mean...
You're not supposed to pee in the pool, but no one got out.
And I know, because I was...
I had to be underwater with my eyes open, of course,
as if I could see with my eyes open under water.
Chris, did you pee?
I actually shit myself.
I just go back.
Yeah, that's not how I am.
Time is money on a movie like this.
But as you were in the water...
Mm-hmm.
Well, I was trapped in this gyrosphere.
In your defense.
In my defense.
I just felt this freedom as I was working.
You know what I mean?
I just was like really present.
Oh.
You didn't pee.
Claire peed.
Yes, Claire peed.
Claire was panicked.
Lost it.
Oh, God.
Yeah.
She's such a good actor.
You're a pro-life man.
Every time you've said that for the last seven months,
I'm like, what's the crap you?
I'm just going deeply to shame.
Oh.
And that's when we team up
and we sort of become best buds on and off screen.
And we fight these elemental creatures.
But now, feel me together, Jake.
Tom, it sounds like it was quite unsubithetic to you
while you were filming.
What did you get a little peaky in?
Oh, well, yeah.
We were shooting a scene.
Well, we were shooting a scene.
And I got sick.
I was very nauseous throughout the day.
And in the middle of one of the takes,
I threw up in the middle of the take.
And kept going.
But that's how that's what acting is all about.
I was sitting opposite him.
And I was like, how is he doing that?
He is so good.
He looks so tortured and so unwell and so hurt.
And then he basically just had a stomach buck.
And they actually CGIed the vomit out of the shot.
But if you look in the movie,
my mouth is just partially open at one I'm kidding.
I was like, how's he going to get it?
I was right there.
Yeah, I mean, that's the Marvel Universe.
It's painting out the vomit.
It's all the great chunk.
But my eyes were so expressive that they had to keep it in the movies.
It's so good to read you the shot, you know?