Can you believe it's been five years since our first date?
I know.
Do you think I should start watching the Flash TV show?
LAUGHTER
That's what you're thinking about?
Well, one of the things.
Are any of them me?
Yes.
I thought, I can't decide if I should watch the Flash TV show.
I know. I'll ask Amy.
Anyway.
What are you doing?
You're right. You did kind of kill the mood.
I didn't kill anything.
You did talking about your stupid TV show.
Excuse me?
Starting to watch a television show that might run for years
isn't a decision to take lightly.
I'm wrestling with a big commitment issue here.
Really?
That's the commitment issue you're wrestling with.
Sheldon, do you understand the irony of your fixation
on a man with super speed?
Well, after five years, all I can get out of you
is a distracted make-out session on a couch.
Irony's not really my strong suit.
But I have been getting better with sarcasm
if you want to give that a try.
Oh, sure. I'd love to.
Whenever you're ready.
She passed me the man in Sheffitts.
I took one look at this poem and almost
plots on the cougill.
I know.
Is this what I saw naked and talk about in you?
So my mother's OK with this?
Why would your mother have a problem with me and Stewart?
Because they have a weird and appropriate relationship.
Weirder than what you and I did in my dad's corolla?
This is so messed up.
I know. I'm having the best time.
Why would you even come to this?
Didn't you know I'd be here?
It was a long time ago, Howard.
And your only second cousin, Zooka Ears.
So you knew when you brought her anyway?
Oh, so she's good enough for Howard, but not for me?
Yeah.
Yeah, go have weird relationships with your own mother
and cousin.
This is his turf.
Yeah.
OK, I got to ask.
What makes you think that your relationship is so wonderful
in ours is it?
For starters, we enjoy spending time together.
So do we.
And I've seen you guys ignore each other for hours
doing totally different things.
It's called parallel play.
You got toddlers do that.
Not as well as we do.
You believe this guy has to be the best in everything?
So what? Why do you even care?
Oh, listen to them.
Not even married in the honeymoon's over.
Whatever.
You can't even go on a date without checking
your relationship agreement.
If you've got a problem basing a relationship on a contract,
I'd like to tell you about 13 plucky colonies
that entered a relationship agreement called the US
Constitution.
And it may not be cool to say so,
but I think that love affair is still pretty hopped today.
It's a good thing I'm not wearing flag underwear right now
because there's about to be a fire.
Oh, it's beautiful.
The girls really did a nice job.
Oh, I know I wasn't into this before,
but I'm so glad I get to take you to your first prom.
What makes you think I didn't go to my prom?
Oh, my went.
Who would you go with?
I took a little idea.
I like to call loneliness.
No, it's all right.
We ended up having a threesome with her friend Humiliation.
LAUGHTER
Well, if I would have been there and saw you alone,
I would have asked you to dance.
Oh, you wouldn't dance.
Well, they don't know that.
It was before my growth spurt.
What that already happened?
Ah.
Very funny.
Well, you wouldn't have asked me either.
I would have asked you in my head on the way home.
While I was having a good cry.
I've invented a science joke.
Could you like to hear it?
Sure.
How many Edison's does it take to screw in a light bulb?
How many?
Who cares?
He stole the idea and doesn't deserve a zone joke.
Is that really true?
Of course.
That's how you know it's a good joke.
It not only entertains, it informs.
Hey, sorry to interrupt.
Barry, how many Edison's does it take to screw in a light bulb?
Did you know Edison didn't actually invent the white bulb?
LAUGHTER
What do you want, Barry?
Just wanted to walk this office with all.
Thank you for Amy.
What's this for?
Your idea willy helped me out.
My white conquantization paper is online already.
The response has been amazing.
Well, that's fascinating.
I can't wait to read it.
You don't know me as well.
A please email it to sheldonatbezenga.biz.
Why dot biz?
Because I just gave you the business.
And also bezenga.com was taken.
This is an easy one.
You love this guy.
Me.
Come on, he's an underappreciated genius.
Still think it's me.
It's not you.
Now think, there's a car named after him.
Of course there he is.
The mini-cooper, because it's me.
LAUGHTER
How about this?
He's a poor man's sheldon cooper.
Oh, Tesla.
Hi.
How'd it go?
Not fun.
The doctor shoved a camera up into my sinuses.
Yeah, I watched.
He was like the scary boat tunnel in Willy Wonka.
LAUGHTER
Did they figure out what's wrong?
Yeah, it's a deviated septum.
The surgery to crack to the simple.
He's going to do it in that sweet.
Why would you have surgery?
Because I can't breathe.
Well, I snore. I get sinus infections.
Now back off. He's on mine.
But you don't have a life threatening condition.
Why would you take the risk of surgery?
Sheldon, it's a routine procedure.
I've heard you complain about his snoring.
What?
Yeah, that's for the first five or six years,
but I've gotten used to it.
It helps me sleep.
He's like my mucus powered wide noise machine.
LAUGHTER
Sheldon, I'm going to get the surgery.
It's no big deal on the story.
Very well.
Now I'm done talking about it.
Thank you.
I believe it was your turn in the game.
Oh, OK.
Let's see.
Oh, this person is most famous
for never having gotten his nose mutilated
with elective surgery,
and never living the rest of his life in the shadows
as the hideous, disfigured freak.
LAUGHTER
I think you could give a better clue.
I don't.
I'm not even sure if that's a person or a typo.
Do you guys ever fight over money?
Sure, sometimes.
I mean, it could be a little awkward
since I make so much more money than how he...
LAUGHTER
You didn't have to say so much more.
Well, I didn't have to, but for the sake of accuracy,
I felt that I should.
LAUGHTER
I brought a lot of significant assets
into the relationship, too.
Like what?
Your incomplete set of star-check collector plates?
LAUGHTER
For your information, I just bought the last one
I needed on eBay.
LAUGHTER
Without asking?
There were only three minutes left in the auction,
and it was a mint-conditioned Scotty from a smoke-free home.
LAUGHTER
How much, Ali?
Not a lot.
How much?
It's not talk about this in front of our friends.
Was it more or less than falconry schools?
LAUGHTER
For the tenth time that was, A, Groupon.
Would you enjoy my lecture?
No, and neither did our waiter.
LAUGHTER
If you're going to serve Cornish Gamehen,
you should either be familiar with the history of Cornwall
or be prepared to learn it.
LAUGHTER
It's hard to argue with that, and I know,
because I saw a sad man with a pepper mill desperately try and fail.
LAUGHTER
Hey, how was dinner?
Good. I had Cornish Gamehen.
Oh, that poor waiter.
LAUGHTER
Sheldon, how about tomorrow night we see a movie?
You guys are going out two nights in a row?
Yeah, well, I missed a number of date nights
while I was on my train trip,
and I'm contractually obligated to make them up
under the terms of the relationship agreement.
That's so hot.
LAUGHTER
It's better than hot, it's binding.
If you're free tomorrow night, I'd love to have you join us on a double date.
Aw.
You are aware that a double date doesn't count as two dates.
LAUGHTER
Oh.
Well, then come her down, I don't care.
They're not dating. They're just two friends who went out to dinner.
And then went back to the room they share
where they probably fell asleep in the matching pajamas.
She got them because they both just love penguins.
LAUGHTER
Lots of people wear matching pajamas who aren't dating.
Like who? Like you and your dog.
LAUGHTER
They don't rule out the dating.
Fine. It bothers me.
Happy?
You think you've got problems?
The Gibbon is the only member of the ape family
not classified as a great ape.
LAUGHTER
How is this helpful?
All the non-human apes are classified as great apes except one.
That means tax on them has created the entire category
of a lesser ape just to single out the poor Gibbon
as the weird kid on the playground.
LAUGHTER
Now, there's a hairy little fella with a genuine beef.
But the Gibbon doesn't know what it's categorized as.
It doesn't even know it's called a Gibbon.
True.
Sorry, kids, you got it worse than a Gibbon.
But I made a video.
LAUGHTER
I'm Dr. Shelton Cooper.
And I'd like to tell you why I should be chosen to...
Go to Mars!
LAUGHTER
I'm exceedingly smart.
I graduated college at 14.
While my brother was getting an STD, I was getting a PhD.
LAUGHTER
Penicillin can't take this away.
Being in close quarters, cleanliness is important.
LAUGHTER
My hygiene is impeccable.
In fact, animals don't trust me because I smell like nothing.
Yet.
Sigh.
Literally nothing.
LAUGHTER
During the seven-month space flight, I can keep up morale
with my wacky sense of humor.
LAUGHTER
Hey, Leonard.
Is there any peanut brittle left in that can?
You mean this weirdly suspicious one?
Yes.
Open it and check.
LAUGHTER
I don't get it.
There's actually peanut brittle left.
LAUGHTER
Please go to Mars.
But on a more serious note, the most important reason I want to go to Mars
is that I believe as a scientist, it's my duty to push the boundaries of human knowledge forward.
Now, I know that life on Mars will be difficult,
but life here on Earth is no picnic.
Also, picnics are no picnic.
LAUGHTER
Where should we go for lunch? Oh, I know, the ground.
In conclusion, thank you for considering me for this journey of a lifetime.
Tomorrow!
LAUGHTER
That's ridiculous.
You know, I'm going to go talk to the meter, D.
What are you going to say?
I don't know. I'm going to flirt with him.
I don't know if I'm comfortable with that.
I'm still sleeping with you tonight.
So you even get a title by the window.
LAUGHTER
Hi there. What's your name?
Glenn.
Oh, boy, it is crazy in here tonight, huh, Glenn?
Well, you know, Valentine's Day?
Yes. Uh, but your girlfriend is super bummed you had to work tonight.
Anyway, look, we have been waiting a while, and I just...
With all due respect, man, there's nothing I can do.
You don't have to call me man.
OK. I mean, we're basically the same age.
OK.
LAUGHTER
How old are you?
I'm 21. How old are you?
Just shut up, Glenn.
Come on, let's get out of here.
What? Why?
Because I'm young, let's go.
Seems we're at a, uh, stalemate.
Not technically.
In chess, a stalemate refers to a situation in which there are no remaining moves.
Uh, you have plenty of moves available.
You could beat us up and steal the money.
You could kill us.
Really, you're only limited by your imagination.
Well, all these years have been using stalemate when I really mean impasse.
I feel foolish.
LAUGHTER
I don't think it matters if this is a stalemate or an impasse or a Mexican standoff.
What are we going to do here?
Oh, how can it be a Mexican standoff?
Everybody knows you need three sites for that.
Not necessarily.
You know, many argue that essence of a Mexican standoff is that no one can walk away from the conflict without incurring harm.
Hmm, I don't follow.
Let me give you an example.
Earlier today, I decoded the headers on your email, and I know that your name is Kenneth Fitzgerald.
From that, I figured out where you live and where you work.
Now, to make this a Mexican standoff, I would say something like, uh,
well, you give us the helium or I'll turn you into the authorities.
Is that a threat?
Yeah, exactly. See, you're getting it.
What is this?
I don't know. Maybe it says something on the back?
Continue it on milk.
You're tricking me to making my own breakfast.
It didn't work for my mom and it won't work for you.
Are we...
Are...
Seaspoons for more?
What could it be?
We are Groot.
We are the champions.
We are family.
I got all my sisters with me.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Are you positive?
That's a joke, because the pregnancy test says I'm...
It's incredible.
We're gonna be parents?
We're gonna get to board planes first.
We're finally gonna get to see what's in that family bathroom at the mall.
No, it's crazy.
It is crazy.
Oh.
I mean, how do you prepare for something like this?
I'm not even sure I've held a baby before.
It's okay. You figure it out.
How's this all gonna work?
Do we get a nanny?
Can we afford a nanny?
If we can, we can't get a pretty one because we'll wreck our marriage.
We can't get an ugly one because it'll scare the kid.
Are we gonna get schooled this straight with your Catholic?
I'm Jewish. What religion do we raise it?
And if it's a boy, do we get him circumcised?
People say it's barbaric, but if we don't, it looks like a pig in a blanket.
Oh, damn, it's gonna be okay.
How's it gonna be okay?
Look at me. I'm a mess.
That means this baby's gonna be half a mess.
And that's even before we screw it up with our cut rate moderately attractive nanny.
Oh, there's a woman.
I'll make her my girlfriend.
Oh, walking up to a strange woman in a bar, usually doesn't look.
You're forgetting something.
Ladies love jocks.
I'm at least six of the beauty of her three.
Excuse me. I'm recovering from a recent breakup.
And I'm told asking out another woman might make me feel better.
And as Ash Ketchum said to Pikachu, I choose you.
What?
It's a Pokemon reference.
I don't know what that means.
Well, we gave it a shot.
How about you?
I'm married. And I'm a grandmother.
Ah, what might have been?
And you give my regards to Barnum and Bailey.
You're eating? That's a good sign.
You're gonna have to wait one hour until you can go swimming again.
He's pretty cute.
He is.
Do we name him?
His Valentine's Day.
How about Valentino?
Nice.
Classic rabbit name.
Peter Rabbit, Roger Rabbit, Valentino Wallowitz Rabbit.
Oh, look at all that chest hair and over bite, of course, you're a Wallowitz.
Son of a bitch, he bit me.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay. Wild rabbits can have rabies.
Why'd you put your finger in your mouth?
Poor judgment, obviously.
He's so little, I'm sure it's fine.
How can it be fine? I just got attacked by a clearly antisemitic wild animal.
It says rabies and rabbits is highly unlikely.
Terrific.
It's not terrific.
Lots of highly unlikely things happen.
You saw what's under this robe and you still married me?
If you're really worried, we'll take them to the vet and have them tested.
Thank you.
Okay, there is a test.
All they have to do is cut off his head and check his brain.
Oh, cut off his head.
That's where his little noses.
He's not showing any symptoms.
I guess I'll just go to the emergency room to be safe.
Howie, this is just your hypocondria.
When I sat on the mute button and thought I'd gone deaf, that was my hypocondria.
There was a song I couldn't get out of my head.
Eventually I realized the song was about you.
And like that earworm, I can't get you out of my heart.
So what I'm trying to say is, you're my heartworm.
The metaphorical kind, not the poodle killing kind.
What?
If I may, I believe what he's saying in a charming and delightful way is that he loves you and wants you back.
Dave Gibbs, huge fun if you work. Don't mind me.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize you were on a date.
No, it's okay. Keep going.
Amy, if you want to be my girlfriend again, I really want to be your boyfriend.
I really want that too.
Good. Because I love you.
I love you too.
Kiss her, you brilliant fool.
Dear crazy future sheldon.
This is a thermostat.
It controls the temperature of the apartment.
The ideal setting is 72 degrees.
If you find this too cold, then put on a jacket.
A straight jacket, because 72 is the best and you're crazy.
Now, this is your spot.
You're very protective of it.
When anyone else tries to sit here, you berate them relentlessly.
And it sounds mean, but somehow you make it adorable.
People are also delighted by your love of pranks.
For example, Leonard has no idea what I did to his coffee.
It wasn't replaced with Folters, Crystals.
I'll tell you that much.
Hey, can we please get back to work?
This is Leonard.
He's your best friend in the world.
Just stop. This is ridiculous.
Sometimes he gets cranky.
But you can trust him with your life.
And he does more things for you than I can even begin to list.
Thank you.
Don't know he's drinking it.
Come on, Leonard's doing bachelor's stuff.
Are you sure we can't take you to a strip club?
If I want to see a naked, dancing man,
I just flush the toilet while Leonard's in the shower.
Hi.
Hey.
I know we're not making a fuss, but in the spirit of bachelor at parties,
I made cookies in the shape of male genitals.
Really didn't have to...
Whoa!
That is anatomic.
Thank you. The veins are gummy worms.
Oh, look.
She was shunned, Gentile.
I had extra dough.
Oh, that's Leonard. He said they're about to cross the border.
I hope the boys don't get too crazy in Mexico.
Oh, right. You'll lock up your daughters or Sheldon might lecture them
about the North American free trade agreement.
Boy, that was a long night for me.
What do you think?
I think it's very cute.
Cute? It's not cute.
Cute as children dressed as vegetables.
Okay, fine. It's not cute.
Just be honest. You don't like it.
I didn't say that. I just like music you can dance to.
You can dance to this.
A-a-a-a.
Thor and Dr. Jones.
One plays with Lightning, the other plays with Bob.
I'm telling you dude, the song is no groove. You can't dance to it.
Who cares?
I thought the whole point of Footprints on the Moon was to write songs that make people think.
You can do both!
Like Michael Jackson's Billie Jean,
while you're dancing, you're thinking,
like, don't it, whose baby is it?
That's a funny spot collectibles.
I have many.
My most treasured is an autographed napkin,
given to me by my very thoughtful friend Penny.
That's her over there.
Hi.
Look at that.
A minute movie? My shirt's stayed on.
Can we see the napkin?
Of course. Excuse me.
This will just take a moment.
When did we get a wall safe?
When there was no more room in the floor safe.
When did we get a floor safe?
When we got the security camera.
There's a security camera?
Aw, man. Protecting your homes since 2012.
Oh, my God. We've done things on that couch.
Yeah, you don't have to tell me.
Have you thought about advertising directly to females?
Mm, okay.
Well, all right.
What if I put up a sign in the window that said,
women come in.
Don't be afraid.
Hey, have you read the online reviews for this place?
Mm, Internet's so negative I try to avoid it.
All right. Well, Heather H says,
the owner stared at me the whole time and didn't blink once.
Kelly M says,
the creepy guy who runs it asked me out
and called himself stupid before I could say no.
Just okay.
Says,
I told the weird owner that I liked his shirt.
He took it off and gave it to me.
See? Negative.
You actually think it's 2003?
No, just because I'm living my life like it was 12 years ago
doesn't mean I'm delusional.
And since it is 2003,
I don't know who you are.
So please exit the premises before I call the police
on my stylish new flip phone.
Hello, 2003.
Hey, we brought you to...
Where is everything?
In my present, it's in the future.
In your present, it's been crammed in the bedroom
by an enterprising young man I met in the Home Depot parking lot.
I know what you're doing.
You're trying to get attention so we'll feel bad for you,
but it's not happening.
No, what I'm dealing with is the same.
No, what I'm doing is trying to figure out how to live my life
now that everyone is leaving me.
Knock it off or across the hall.
As the kids are saying today, talk to the ham.
They're not saying that.
They are in 2003.
No, no, they're really not.
He started...
Hey.
Surrey, day startle you?
Yes, but at this point, pretty much any customer does.
What can I do for you?
I need a little help.
I accidentally destroyed one of Howard's comics boxes morning
and I was hoping I could replace it.
Wow, what happened?
Batman got his ass kicked by my curling iron.
Don't let the riddler know that.
It's a comic book joke.
Or maybe it's not.
Dad, this one?
Well, it's pretty rare.
Can you give me a few days to track it down?
I was kind of hoping to get it before how he comes home from work.
What's the hurry?
Well, he's always saying I should be more careful with my curling iron
and it seems like a dangerous precedent to let him think he can be right.
Well, do what I can, but I can't make any promises.
You know, I do work at a pharmaceutical company.
If you can make this happen today, I can hook you up with anxiety medication
and I depress you.
Really?
Do you have any of these?
I feel like everything is falling apart.
Come on, it's okay.
No, it's not okay. Look at me.
It took a temp job as a waitress forever ago.
I'm still doing it.
I can't quit because guess what?
I can't do anything else and I finally get my big break and it goes away.
Such a mess.
No, you're not.
Really?
Because this morning at Starbucks, a pair of old underwear fell out of my pant leg.
And it wasn't the only one in there.
Okay, listen to me.
This is just a minor setback.
No, it's not.
Okay, I've been out here for like 10 years.
I have nothing to show for it.
Well, you have me.
Right.
I do have you.
Let's get married.
What?
Let her have a setter.
Will you marry me?
Oh.
Did you seriously just say, oh.
You know, I love you.
But put your your drunken sad and feeling lost.
Okay, so do you you don't want to marry me?
That is not what I said.
No, forget it.
I take it back, offers off the table.
Who's in the mood to laugh?
I got an email from Professor Proton.
Goody, what's it say?
He's working on a paper about nano vacuum tubes and wants to know if I take a look at it.
A strange thing would come to you for that and not me.
Oh, I got two emails from him.
Do you have Leonard's email address?
And never mind I found it.
I can't believe he picked you over me.
I don't want to read a paper by some old husband who hasn't done any real science and decades.
Yeah, it's nothing to cry about.
Sheldon Cooper does not cry.
It's true.
You'd rust.
When Obi-Wan came to Luke on this very spot, he gave him all sorts of helpful advice.
So, um, what do you got for me?
Um, always.
Get, get a prenup.
That's it.
I thought there'd be more of a reason why you're here.
Oh.
Why do you think I'm here?
I suppose it has something to do with your recent passing.
It's just the first time you've lost, you know, someone close to you.
Oh, no.
No.
I've already had to say goodbye to 11 doctors.
Yeah, I've, I've lived a few of my doctors too.
Oh, hey, Sheldon.
Hello.
You okay?
I'm on vacation.
What do you think?
Why are you sitting in the stairwell?
Leonard told me to stay.
Oh, well, good boy.
Where are you going?
A ton of errands to run.
You need to make copies of my headshot, send them off to agents, and sign up for a new acting class.
Have fun.
Okay.
No.
You want to come with me?
Really?
Come on, boy, come on, let's go.
Get the gun.
Come on.
So, what did you think of your first funeral?
Oh, I don't want to be a jerk, but it was kind of a bummer.
Yeah, well, when I die, you can rent a bounce house.
Think about dying?
Well, I think more about, if I don't have any regrets.
What would you regret?
You know, home.
I didn't travel more.
Take more risks.
Learn another language.
You know, cling on.
That's true.
No, I meant that as a regret.
Just thought of one more.
What's up?
I regret not saying yes when you asked me to marry you.
Well, it just wasn't the right time.
Yeah.
And this is also not the right time.
Do not propose.
What?
I know that face, that's your proposed face.
I was not going to propose.
It's already two to one.
What's two to one?
I proposed twice, you proposed once, two to one.
Oh, my, it's not a contest.
Don't know what you're upset about.
I'm the one who's losing.
Fine, would you feel better if I proposed so you could turn me down again?
Yeah, I think I would.
Okay, Leonard, will you marry me?
Hmm.
No, don't you dare.
You reject me right now and tie things up.
It's just such a big decision.
I don't want to have any regrets.
And hold three, two, one.
Very good.
Now let's try warrior two.
And hold.
I've read that they're great yogis who have such mastery over their bodies.
They can draw water in through their genitals.
No, well, I don't think we're going to get to do that today.
Too bad.
Seems like a good way to drink a milkshake without getting brain freeze.
Oh, hey.
Now we go to reverse warrior.
How did she get you to do yoga?
Well, to be honest, I thought she said Yoda.
Wait, it's not all pants. There's one shirt.
Oh, hey, that's my shirt.
This one is too.
No, that's not mine. That's a big spot on it.
Oh, wait, so does this one?
Maybe the spot's the clue.
Sheldon spot. The poison is black.
Oh, that's clever.
Be there in a minute. I just had to preso, please.
Where the hell is the coin?
Wasn't the answer Sheldon spot?
Oh, yes, Leonard. Yes, it was.
The coin.
Yes, exactly. Where is the coin?
Why don't you look in your pockets?
I slipped them in there earlier today.
I don't get it.
Don't you see when we're all having fun together, we're already winners.
Oh, look, see? Even I'm a winner.
Are you kidding me?
This is stupidest thing I've ever heard.
You suck.
So hot.
Water would be great.
You're Lucy, right?
I'm a friend of Raj Kutherpolli's.
Actually, Amy recognized you.
Wow. How's he doing?
Oh, you know, he's good.
Great.
Yeah, this is none of my business, but why did you break up with him in an email?
Oh, I don't know.
I guess I thought it would be easier.
Yeah, I get that. I'll go get you your water.
When you say easier.
You mean easier for you, right?
Because I certainly didn't make it easier for him.
Any chance I can get a different waitress?
I'm sorry, this is rude of me. I will get you that water.
See, see, see, see.
Just now, you expressed your feelings to my face.
How come you could do that with me, but not with Raj?
I don't know your email.
You know what the worst part is?
You're sitting here perfectly happy, and he's at home a blubbering mess.
I thought you said he was okay.
Well, I also said I was getting your water.
Would look at me still standing here.
You know, I may be a bad waitress, but you are a bad person.
Now, you want to hear the specials?
Arthur passing away was harder on Sheldon than he's ready to admit.
Really hoping this will cheer him up.
Me too.
Although it might have been thoughtless of us to make a death star cake.
No, it combines two of Sheldon's favorite things.
Chocolate chips and the ability to destroy a planet at the push of a button.
Well, anyway, it'll be a nice surprise for the boys.
And how he doesn't think I take his interest seriously, so hopefully this will keep him full for a while.
Okay, let's get the fondant and start decorating.
This is pretty cool. You don't see too many spherical cakes.
I wonder why that is.
Hey, guys.
Happy Star Wars Day!
Wow!
A death star cake!
We were hoping it might cheer you up.
And even though it meant we had to miss the movies, we could still be part of the fun.
Oh, you didn't miss anything. We just started over.
Out of the bitch.
Hi.
Look who's here to put the Jew in Jewelry night.
Oh, sure, so it's fine when you say it.
Sorry, I'm late. I wanted to swing by the lab and pick up some even cooler tools for us to use.
I didn't know you were coming again.
Last week was a blast.
Plus I thought you might like having a guy here.
Who's not funny?
So what tools did you bring?
Everything we need to make Jewelry molds.
Here's some silver or crucible and an unsettling torch to melt it down.
Ooh, that looks like fun.
Maybe you should master glue before you move on to fire.
Okay, who's that first?
Rajesh, do you want to make a bracelet for your mom to go with the necklace?
No tanks.
I was going to make a necklace for my mom, but unfortunately she doesn't have a neck.
She's just chins and fat and feet.
Leonard, do you think I'm funny?
No.
You?
I think I'm hysterical.
I take it back. That was funny.
The philosopher Henri Bergsson says it's funny when a human being behaves like an object.
I bet that bit killed in the chuckle hut.
Oh, he didn't perform stand-up comedy. He was a philosopher.
I think we're zeroing in on your problem.
Perhaps I'll spend some time developing a unified theory of comedy,
which will allow me to elicit laughter from anyone at any time,
unless they're German, because that's a tough crowd.
Are you set on people laughing with you, because if you're cool with that, you...
You guys have a notice that Emily has a bit of a twisted side.
You mean because she has weird tattoos?
No, because she wants to have sex with me in a graveyard.
One more time?
She and I were supposed to watch the new Avengers movie tonight, but I was sold out.
So I said, what else do you want to do?
She said, let's go to a cemetery and do it on somebody's grave.
Like a random person or somebody she knew.
What difference does it make?
Well, if it's her father's grave and they didn't get along, then you know she holds a grudge.
The only issue is that everybody has their own thing.
As long as it's two consenting adults, I guess I don't see the harmony.
Well, if it's one consenting adult and one adult who pretends to consent,
because she's afraid of being alone.
That's a beautiful life.
Oh, yes.
You got the moon and the trees and Elizabeth McNulty, who apparently died when she was the same age I am.
Makes you feel alive, doesn't it?
So does enjoying a meal at a well-ed restaurant, but here we are.
You aren't scared, are you?
Of ghosts? No.
Of you, a little bit.
This is interesting.
Apparently, a key component in some forms of humor is the element of surprise.
Well, I make sense that prefrontal cortex is responsible for planning and anticipation
and patience with brain lesions.
Sheldon, you scared me, that wasn't funny.
Maybe you have a stick up your prefrontal cortex.
Okay.
The notion that you can read a few books and come up with a definitive theory of comedy is absurd.
I mean, humor is a complex neurological...
Oh, no, no.
I'm not going to be able to read it.
Okay, is her any good?
Any really quit the cheesecake factory?
Yeah. What are you doing today?
I don't know.
She already thinks I don't support this, so if I call it, it might look like I'm checking up on it.
Do you support this?
Of course I do.
She's a great atrism.
How'd she's taking this risk?
That's nice.
You bought that great.
Got a collar before I forget how I said it.
Hey!
Hi, what's up?
How's it going? You've taken Hollywood by storm?
Actually, I'm at the cheesecake factory.
You got your job back. That is great news.
I didn't want to say anything, but you are making the right choice.
But to plunge yourself into debt right now would be literally insane.
Yeah, I'm just returning my uniform.
And I support you.
You've come to me because you're my Obi-Wan.
I'm not familiar with that.
Is that an internet?
Wow.
You're dead, so I'm going to let that slide.
Obi-Wan Kenobi is a character from Star Wars.
After his physical demise, he comes to Luke Skywalker as his mentor in spirit form.
Well, that clears that up.
You must be here to give me advice.
This is weird.
Most of my robes open in the back.
Those are your Jedi robes.
Oh, wait. What is this?
Be careful with that.
Oh.
Oh, no.
I need help.
I'm going to need a bandage.