I forgot you.
As Thomas, I think a lot of youngers, they revere you,
so they look to you.
But the other thing you inspire is impressions,
people doing impressions.
Now, when people do impressions of you,
is it like nails on a chalkboard or do you kind of enjoy it?
No, I kind of enjoy it, especially if they do it well.
So, no, it's great.
I love it.
I only ask.
No, because any hiddleston is watching will know.
Tom Hiddleston does impressions.
You do rock pressure lots of people.
So, who is in your canon?
It's an expression of admiration to be clear.
So, I do impressions of people that I admire,
and I sort of listen to them.
I get the first time I did an impression that anyone was aware of.
I was just telling a story about Midnight in Paris,
the Woody Allen film I was in,
and how I never had the whole script,
and I thought it was set in the 20s.
And I turned up, and I bonded to Owen Wilson,
who didn't look like he was in the 20s at all.
And I said to him, I said,
so wait, how on who you playing?
Because I'm playing F-Scope Fitzgerald,
and I know Corey Stolves playing on his hemming way,
and we're all playing figures of history,
and he went, oh, no, no, no, no.
I'm from now.
I go back and play.
There's a time machine.
It's kind of cool, and it's kind of wooding,
and you're just kind of awesome.
Very good.
Yeah.
I've done, I've done, I mean,
I've done, I've been made to the impressors
of my fellow Avengers.
I think everyone does an impression
of Christopher Walken,
because he's such an easy kind of...
You know, I feel like what this show needs is more cowbell.
It depends on what you like me to say.
Basically, there's no punctuation
in the coming out of my mouth.
I like that.
I know whole pages of heat.
You surprised me.
So there's a scene in the middle of the film,
which you'll be familiar with.
You were there.
No.
The one person you don't need to explain to him.
So there's...
He remembers.
You're very good in this film.
Did you see him in the middle of the film,
which is...
Because Al Pacino and Robert De Niro.
Sorry about you.
They're separated, like, a great thriller.
They're separated from...
for the entire film, and they meet twice,
once at the end of once in the middle.
And it takes place at a restaurant, L.A.
It's a great scene.
It's one of the great pieces of screen acting.
You can hope to watch. There it is.
It's a picture of it.
It's like a...
It's a mutual recognition of each other.
Anyway, so there's a bit where they...
They sit and have coffee and have tea
and talk about stuff.
I'm going on, I apologize.
Anyway, so Al Pacino, at one point...
Al Pacino says this.
He goes...
So...
We're sitting here...
Like a couple of regular fellas.
I mean...
You do what you do.
I do what I got to do...
If I'm there...
And I got to put you away...
I won't like it.
But if it's between you...
and some poor bastard...
who's wife, you're going to turn into a widow...
Brother...
You are going down.
And then...
And then a cut...
And then Michael Man cuts back to the esteemed gentleman
at the end of the sofa.
What if you do got me backst in?
And I got to put you down.
I'm moving face to face.
Yeah.
But I will not hesitate.
Now for a second.
And that's my...
This is so...
This is so meta.
I feel like I've gone into a parallel universe where...
I...
You were playing Gullisport.
Yes, I played Gullisport.
No, that's great.
I do not get a press of Ken Brown.
That's my favorite scene.
Was he your favorite scene?
Yeah.
Still.
No, no, no.
No, no, but my favorite scene that was written before...
Not because of...
I'm doing it, but I just...
My favorite scene written in the film.
Yeah.
You know, that's a great, great scene.
Yeah, it feels like it plays into singles in a way.
Yeah.
And it's like the most beautiful game of tennis.
Did you do lots of takes?
I don't think we did more than...
Five to eight or nine.
Maybe a maybe less.
And you talk about dreams and you talk about your life.
No, no, no.
It's so great.
There's that bit in another bit where you go.
No, no, no.
You say...
You say, sir, he says...
Patino says...
So you never wanted a regular type of life.
And...
Bob, may I call you Bob?
Yeah.
Bob says...
What's that?
Bob accused of ball games?
Yeah.
If you have any ideas, I just...
We could be related.
Because...
Apparently...
Apparently, there's some Irish stock in your past.
No.
I really could be.
You never know.
No.
But you have an Irish name.
Do I?
It's a new shape.
A new shape.
It couldn't be more Irish.
There's no one told you that till now.
I've been told.
But, you know, I think my mother just liked the name.
Okay.
Is it your...
Christian?
It's my...
I think.
Let me educate you something.
Black people...
Black people are notorious for picking things that they saw one day and say that's my baby name.
That's how that was.
That's how it was.
There's no amazing story behind it.
You love the tattoo.
You have to actually came from Irish for a father that's not the case.
Mother was reading the paper and she was eating some cereal.
It's not even backstay.
Oh, shame!
She said that'd be a good name for the baby.
That's it.
That's how it happened.
Come on.
But not nearly.
You are here promoting your movie, but Kevin, you're working at the same time.
You're doing stand-up gigs.
Double dipping.
Yes.
Doing a ton of stand-up shows, my What Now tours here as well.
Major thank you to the UK fans.
The tour sold out in literally two days.
So you guys are amazing.
Baby Backwind.
Yes.
We do that.
And then after that, we came over here for promo.
What Cuba myself loved doing is really getting involved with the fans.
You know, we love putting our feet in the street and really being active and interacting.
So we've been doing a ton of pop-ups, just delivering the movie.
The best of our ability was just laughing in person.
And we split in all the tour minds.
That is not true.
You got to hear.
And then I'm here.
Yes, not true.
You know, you don't have a bunch of my stage dears.
Oh, did he?
He tackled me from the back.
Scared to live in mess out.
It was one of the most frightening moments of my life.
I think we might have another frightening moment for you.
This is you in Manchester.
Now, do you even know the name of that show?
Oh, no.
What do you want to do?
What's the only black guy today?
Forever.
That's Coronation Street.
Well done.
That's you in Beverly, kind of, with this picture.
This looks like you've been photoshopped in.
Yeah.
Are you really there?
No.
Roy's Rolls can't be that big.
First of all, it looks like I grew up there.
Obviously, your mother loves you because you heard daughter.
Yeah.
But she is actually a fan as well.
You know, we don't quite that.
It's, I know, she is, oh goodness, right.
So, one day my mum came to set on the Star Wars set.
And I was getting this thing called Cyber Scand,
which is where you stand in this kind of loads of cameras
and they kind of take your form and put you into a computer
and make a toy or a...
some sort of merchandise or your face on a cushion.
And so, I go off and do this and I come back and mum's
like, I've made a great friend.
I'm like, really? It's lovely. Excellent.
And she likes the merchandise, you know, director of all of Star Wars
or something.
And I'm like, well, I'll say, you're very impressive.
And then before I know it, what comes in the post
is loads of cushions.
My face on it.
So, my own mum, I guess, she gets to see it a fair amount, you know.
But it's not enough.
So, I was kind of blown away how much merchandise there is.
Yes, it's all...
And it's just the beginning. It was like the pre-murchin does.
Not even the real stuff is out yet and my mum has all of it.
And it doesn't have that the doll yet.
So, this is so...
Is this in your flat or her house?
Oh, God, yes.
Okay, so basically, she thought it'd be really funny if I came home
and it was everywhere in my...
Okay, so this is...
Is this her meleeous actual bedroom?
Well, the...
LAUGHTER
I'm not even going away.
I'm not even going to play the joke.
And then...
Oh, and then...
Oh, my goodness.
And we found the photo, but it's not like that now.
That's my dream.
There was another reason why I'm single.
You took a first date back to that.
Yeah.
Come on in.
LAUGHTER
I just think this little thing won't...
I don't have a CV, I just have a bedroom.
But this is cool, though.
So, your mother, a big fan, but...
Brad Pitt, also a big fan.
That was the best night of my life.
Yes.
I'm just...
Tell the story, big fan.
Oh!
I'm the story, big fan.
There are two billion people.
Yeah, there's a duvet.
We're only years.
Sippers.
No, yeah, there was this auction thing that happened,
and I...
They called me and said, do you want to...
Do you want to auction something off,
like maybe sort of an experience
watching the show with you or something?
And I was like, okay, it's lovely.
It's great for charity.
Yeah.
It'll be for some...
You know, something.
And it'll be fine.
Anyway, so I get there.
It's basic.
It'll be a good thing.
I get there, and it's basically like this...
It's basic...
It's the Oscars.
There's so many celebrities in this room,
and I suddenly remember that I said
that I would auction something off,
and so the fear grows.
So I was petrified, absolute petrified,
and then the person who's table I was on is a friend,
and he was being very kind and kind of put the paddle up,
and I was like, thanks very much.
That's very sweet.
That'll be that.
And then someone else's paddle up,
went up across the other side of the room,
and I didn't really know, and then suddenly it was sort of
becoming a bit of money, and I was kind of thinking,
oh, this is absolutely mental,
and someone went, it's Brad Pitt, and I was like, oh...
Oh, my God.
I like it, really.
Yeah, exactly.
And I look over to the room, and he's...
Goes pedal up.
Brad's paddle.
LAUGHTER
Oh, it needs him.
No, not quite.
Well, it didn't work out, because the person who's friend
who's my friend, I think it was probably all set up.
Person who's...
Who was my friend, ended up doing the highest bid.
Boom!
LAUGHTER
Friends.
But, yeah, I just kind of looked over with just the most insane,
emoji heart eyes being like this is just the greatest moment of my life.
Now, Olimore, you are going to be singing for us.
I am.
Oh, oh, oh!
Kiss Cam!
Oh, kiss cam!
LAUGHTER
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
Ohhh!
Ohh!
We got this for you!
Aww!
Thank you very much!
It's like a pulse relationship. It's like a douche break down.
You have a mind...
You have a Cole. Dry things.
You have a Cole! Back off lady.
Oh yeah, so we had to do the scene where she kisses,
Daisy kisses him and you know, you don't just kiss me
and I'll do the capriote.
We were sort of halfway through the scene
and I was sort of like here.
Yeah?
Oh, sorry.
Keep going, keep going.
I'll stay in the moment.
LAUGHTER
I was in a scene where I was in bed listening to the radio
because the voice of the man reading the shipping forecast
really turned me on.
LAUGHTER
This is the work I do.
So I was in bed and I had to be being turned on.
And I was getting slightly embarrassed and shy.
I was pregnant.
I was feeling mad as you are.
And Graham came over to me and he said,
OK, the noises that you're making,
could you make the noises that you might make getting
into a hot bath?
And that was it.
I was like,
oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
LAUGHTER
Very good.
APPLAUSE
So we're going to be so many suspicious husbands tonight.
Yeah.
I was just thinking.
Yeah, exactly.
That can I just say?
Sound familiar, guys.
You're getting into a hot bath, aren't you?
LAUGHTER
That was very lazy.
You're getting into a hot bath.
I've been married a long time, aren't I?
I prefer when they act like they're getting into a cold bath with me.
LAUGHTER
It's because you get life.
I did want to be as well as you all.
That was what I thought I was going to be my entire life.
I wanted to study the...
LAUGHTER
Like a teacher, so...
I've learned a lot from you already.
LAUGHTER
You never met?
No, did we on the film?
No, but I was honored to know
and I was working on the same project.
Thank you.
Oh, what's going on?
Hey, man, so she's kind of taken.
LAUGHTER
Well, are you...
Why do you have...
LAUGHTER
You've made the sex and arguments in the past with your wife.
I have, yes. The biggest one I've found is that...
If you have an argument about an issue, stick to the issue.
Don't start getting personal.
LAUGHTER
And I was spiteful, that's the one in it.
Yeah.
So we were arguing and I just sort of lost it.
And I said, oh, shut up, monkey feet.
Oh, no.
I didn't pick this out of the air.
My wife has got massive toes.
You think you can impress yourself as well, Brad, did it?
I don't know.
I'm not going to be a big fan of you.
LAUGHTER
You can impress yourself as well, Brad, did it?
Sometimes, if you want me to talk, I just...
Whenever comes into my head, I'll say,
I'm no no...
...when, or what it's going to be.
Is that your mum?
LAUGHTER
This is a walking battle.
No, we're not.
So it's a family guy.
It's a family guy.
The characters you do, you do...
Peter, Brian, Stewie, Quagmire and then a...
...smattering of others.
OK.
And are they all based on people?
Are you just...
They come from various places.
Peter, I knew a thousand Peter Griffins growing up
in New England, guys who would not think before they spoke.
Like...
No, no, self-mediting mechanism.
It's coming out here with no gateway.
LAUGHTER
And when you're doing...
...because, you know, those characters are in scenes together.
Yeah.
Do you do one line after the other?
Or do you all do one and then go back to the other one?
When I do a table read, yeah, I have to jump back and forth.
Hey, how what's going on?
Hello, Fat Man.
Oh, Stewie, how are you?
Back and forth.
It's good, right? That is good.
APPLAUSE
I was just telling a story about Midnight in Paris,
the Woody Allen film I was in.
And how I never had the whole script,
and I thought it was set in the 20s.
And I turned up and I bumped into Owen Wilson,
who didn't look like he was in the 20s at all.
And I said to him, I said,
so, wait, how on, who are you playing?
Because I'm playing F-Scope this Gerald,
and I know Corey Stolves playing on his hamming way,
and we're all playing figures of history,
and he went, oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm from now. I go back and play.
LAUGHTER
There's a time machine, you know?
It's kind of cool, and it's kind of wooding,
and you're just kind of awesome.
APPLAUSE
There was a director at Joe Schumacher,
who's a very funny man, very tall,
very sort of eccentric,
and he would direct with a speaker,
with a microphone and a speaker.
Usually directors will come up and say,
hey, I don't know, Johnny.
He'll be like, oh, car, and you'd hear this, you know,
trying to fool me in voice.
And I bolted into this suit.
I can't move.
And he would literally go,
and he would direct you, like,
as if you would have some emotional scene.
And he would go, okay, people, all right?
George, your parents are dead.
You haven't.
Nothing to live for.
LAUGHTER
Oh, my God.
You're not doing well.
And that man.
And time.
LAUGHTER
That happened a dream, Jimmy.
That's true.
You really were a blue coat, weren't you?
I wasn't blue coat. Yeah, at the place you showed.
Which was next door to He Shum Nuclear Power Station.
I think it is. I got a settler,
and I was, I worked a really good one in Yarmouth,
great Yarmouth, got sacked, which is another story.
And then sacked, and then, and was sent to,
we'll move on to that in a minute.
But, you sent to this,
sent to that one as a sort of punishment.
It was like, you're going to Morkham to do six months.
Because you have just...
You've just done something which...
What had you done?
Well, something that was considered cheeky in the 70s,
but now is illegal.
LAUGHTER
Oh, whoa.
No, that's actually...
It was actually an incident where it was my first attempt at stand-up comedy.
And what happened was, I...
I'd always wanted to do stand-up comedy.
I didn't have the guts to do it.
I got very drunk.
I had to go at doing it as a blue coat.
My mate said to me,
just copy all the other comedians at Pontons and steal the jokes,
and basically, talk to the front row.
So you're supposed to say, were you from?
They say Scotland, you say, who paid for your holiday?
Were you from Wales?
You make an oys like a sheep? Rubbish jokes, all right?
But I said, that's terrible.
He said, don't worry, you're just padding.
What you're doing is you're looking for comedy gold,
which is, were you from?
They say Kent, and you say, what did you call me?
Now at Pontons, this used to take the roof off, right?
LAUGHTER
So I tried it, but I was very drunk.
So I go on stage,
and I say, were you from...
I said, I said, Scotland,
I can't remember the joke.
LAUGHTER
I say, hello.
Then I said to, were you from?
The guy says, Wales, I'd black out, and I go, hi.
Hi, panic.
And then I say, anyone in from Kent?
LAUGHTER
And this bloke shouts out me.
And I said, well, you're a f***er.
LAUGHTER
So...
So I missed it.
LAUGHTER
So I said to walk him.
It's so unusual to have two such young Oscar winners.
This is normally something you have to do.
That's why we're friends.
Yeah.
You've got them in the neat club.
The other thing you share is quite short-lived careers in modeling.
Oh, I thought you just said short-lived careers.
Wow.
I was like, oh.
Happy New Year.
So...
So because you...
Now, what was your big break?
Was it Vogue a Squire?
Or all of the above?
Talk about modeling.
Talk about it.
Or was it, in fact, an actual...
I don't know.
I think it's about to talk about modeling.
Oh, my God.
It's a car.
No, yes, because he did...
Look at these.
Like, it's hard to make a jumper sexy.
True that.
But I think he's happy to see...
LAUGHTER
That's more...
That's more like Potter.
I mean, Cersei.
Your sweater has eyeballs.
LAUGHTER
That was a high point.
Oh, my God.
I think you can actually still buy that.
And the point of that is you can learn to knit it yourself.
So you...
Oh.
You guys can take one of those home and knit it yourself.
I can buy the sweater and then I have to do it myself.
Yeah.
Actually, there's a classic thing in here.
So, you know, when you want something of Christmas
and you say to your mommy, your granny,
I'd really like a really trendy sweat top.
I'd like a really nice trendy zippy-up set top.
And then they knit it for you.
LAUGHTER
Oh, no!
That's the Christmas nightmare.
Isn't it?
But you still do some modeling, don't you?
A sporadically and very unsuccessfully.
Oh, stop it. You do.
No, I'm not.
You do.
What I did do...
I did some...
I did a campaign for Burberry, which was very amazing.
And I did it a few years ago.
And Marieta Stino shot it.
Cool.
And I remember doing it.
It was when I was just starting out.
In this photograph, there was a sort of...
There was a model and me and actor, one-of-be-actor,
and a musician.
And Marieta Stino, who I'd never worked with,
who is one of the most extraordinary brilliant people,
but he's just almost in that moment.
He was almost like a sort of parody of himself.
So, we had to run and jump for the photograph.
And he goes...
He's literally got the camera there and he goes,
OK, so battling.
You're supermodel.
You rock star.
You're movie star.
I'm Marieta Stino.
I want to see golf!
I'm dancing to the air.
These two sort of pros.
I'm leaving with this shot.
He gets the photos because they're so natural,
ones of shock and minor despair.
And wonder, I think it was the same time.
Because you don't have my pictures.
No, I don't.
Because I'll tell you why.
Yes, tell us why.
Because it's really amazing, jump together.
I was an Abercrombie model.
Get in.
Abercrombie, a bitch like this, gentlemen.
Don't make your hoots.
They're doing it to the story.
We have to pitch.
So, my pictures never came out.
I did the whole campaign and the pictures never came out.
And I didn't know why.
And my agent wrote and asked why.
And they literally only responded with the photos.
Because they...
Their whole idea was like, we want real people.
So, they...
I don't know.
We were on a beach and then they threw us a football.
And they're like, play football.
And all the other models were playing football
in a pretty way.
And I'm like, and that me.
I was all of the photos.
I've got a red face covered in sweat.
My nostrils are flared.
I'm like, no!
I'm going to give a picture.
And like a one-pointed girl yelled,
just get her away from me.
That's all.
Yeah.
Well, you know, she's in the story.
When you...
Was you in college?
Yeah.
You did something quite extreme to meet ladies.
I wasn't...
I became a cheerleader.
Now, see, that's...
What?
Yeah.
Now, see, that seems quite an out there thing to do.
Well, it wasn't necessarily just to meet a woman.
It was so I could travel to all the places that the team went to meet women.
Oh, my God.
Yes, Mark.
I was going to all these other schools and...
But did you have pom-poms and stuff?
I had a megaphone.
You're a big dude.
Yeah, the girls had pom-poms, but...
I went to an all-male school across the street,
was an all-woman school spellman.
So we got our cheerleader, our female cheerleader, just from there.
So I was the only one who volunteered to be a cheerleader that year.
So I talked my roommate into doing it,
and he was like,
this is awesome.
We get to pick all the girls, so we pick them.
And we got to travel all these other schools to meet women.
What was totally dope?
Oh, my God.
Great plan.
I'm such a fan.
I'm like, this is huge.
But did you have to do cheerleading?
Did you have to do the chants?
We had some cheerers, but basically, we would go...
I mean, my roommate now would go,
hey gang!
Hey gang!
And then the girls would do the cheer.
They'd do some clips and we'd like...
We weren't picking them up.
We were picking them up, holding them up, or anything.
That's it.
You're just like a big gang.
Yeah, no, basically it.
You know?
And every now and then we do some cheerers
like, you know, Edward, Edward, he's our man.
If he can't do it, fuck it.
When you're single at the moment,
I am.
And Kylie, you're single at the moment.
Now, meeting people and dating is hard enough.
But Kamen DeHaz and Kylie...
I'm single.
Well, hello.
I wasn't sure.
I was going to include you, and it wasn't sure.
Well, lucky for you, Russell.
And you're married.
Lights out like a power router.
Oh!
I can feel the mist every time we kiss.
Just didn't know it down for like this.
There's a flash for the warning.
Will it wear your ring in the morning?
There'll be bottles in the bag.
You're amazing.
Right answer.
So are you.
Do you have a yoga move you could bust out for a quick take?
I have a few, yeah.
What's the most impressive thing you can do with that?
Well, I am one, but I might want someone to spot me.
Yes, I'll do...
I'm...
I mean, if we're with anyone, it's eye meat.
It's a good one for sure.
Really?
Oh, my God, you're so good.
Okay, wait.
Stand here.
I'm sure.
Just put your arm kind of like that.
Put my arm kind of like that.
Okay, wait.
And we're like, this is pretty exciting.
Yes, I love this.
I'm going to yoga both of you.
This is great.
It's herty baby.
I'm going to keep my legs up.
And then just, I'm going to hit your arm for once.
Do I need to catch you or don't need to just...
Just drop me from going over that way and then I can balance.
Okay, oh, this is fantastic.
This is fantastic.
Oh my God.
Wow.
Oh, wow.
Very nice.
Wow.
Thank you.
Do you believe me?
I'm so proud of you.
You do a Liam.
Oh.
I bet you do when he's not here.
Damn, I should have asked you before he showed up.
I'm doing him paisley.
Why are us at night?
You're doing cool and with, thank you.
What?
The cool one.
No.
I feel like, like, danceman.
I feel like I'm just going to make sick of barfings.
Do it.
You're making sick of that.
Fucking seal, aren't I?
Graham Dorphson.
You know, you're an Irishman.
You think these people accept you as one of their own, but they do.
They do accept you as whole.
Yes, Brian, we like some cool whip.
But why are you saying it like that?
Why do I have to say I'm saying cool whip?
You're saying cool whip.
Yes, I'm saying cool whip.
You're putting a lot of emphasis on the age.
Cool whip.
I'm saying cool whip.
It's so cool.
Cool.
I'm a man.
I'm a secretive level superman.
Okay, let's start.
Let's start.
Come on, do one line at a time.
What line shall I do?
I don't know.
I feel the need.
The need for speed.
You're good at it.
Do me.
No, no.
I'm not.
Who you at?
Who you at.
They do to...
Who, who?
Who?
Who you at?
I knew you used to be able to do Sean Connery.
Oh, yeah you could.
In fact, sometimes I would call up my agent and say,
Hello, I know it's a Sean Connery.
To, uh, Edelamator please.
And I immediately got through.
LAUGHTER
How about it, Ken, Mr. Leab?
That's a double deck.
You do, Donald Duck?
Yeah. Do you? Do it.
OK, now it's your turn.
LAUGHTER
Err...
APPLAUSE
A small dragon is back?
He is, yeah.
A crystal of finished business.
And I read that that as a voice, that there isn't...
I mean, obviously it's put through treatments and things,
but actually, it sounds very like what you did.
Oh, God. Do you always do that as well?
If you can.
Err...
So...
...around...
Oh, my God.
LAUGHTER
Is your heart beating faster?
Still not enough.
Oh, God.
Wow.
That's on the wrong side, so I'm not.
Yeah.
That's Clint Eastwood described as,
you hit a few marks, you say a few lines.
What's the problem?
LAUGHTER
Very good.
I don't know what this means, either.
I can't remember.
So, when you're in a Clint Eastwood movie,
you don't even know the camera's rolling,
and you just hear over your shoulder.
All right, go ahead.
LAUGHTER
So, you're doing something.
And...
You know...
You do it sometimes, you're doing some pretty hot stuff,
and you just keep doing it until you hear him say,
that's enough of that.
LAUGHTER
And then you move on, and you're on to the next set of,
it's intimidating as hell.
Please record your personal drink.
To end recording, key zero.
So, you press zero.
Don't record it.
Read that, then you press zero again.
Show me where zero is.
Zero is that one.
There's also your paper.
Endre...
I start?
Yeah.
I don't know who you are.
I don't have any money.
LAUGHTER
Oh my god, look at that!
It's so good.
But when I do have...
LAUGHTER
...our very specific set of skills.
Fills that make me a nightmare.
LAUGHTER
For somebody like you?
I don't know if my daughter will go now.
I will find you.
And I will kill you.
You said you were here with Harrison Ford before.
You did an incredible Chubaka,
but I'm told you also do a jaw jaw binks.
LAUGHTER
Oh, no, that's a big sumo.
This hand is your hand.
This hand is my hand.
No, wait, that's your hand.
Oh, no, that's my hand.
LAUGHTER
Oh, you explain this tweet that was sent to the show.
I hope you're not unhappy with yourselves.
But you're looking forward to this.
This is Thomas.
So, which of you knows Thomas?
You.
So, what's your name?
I'm Jessica.
Jessica.
And why is Thomas upset with us?
Thomas is upset because I've postponed a date for the second time,
so I could come and be here and meet him.
I'm getting a slime for everything.
Is he your boyfriend?
No, no.
We have not been on a date yet.
So, you put him off for the first time?
No, no.
Why did you put him off for the first time?
My sister, and this time Kylie.
OK, you know that will not bat into you.
Are you into him?
You don't know?
Well, really.
Really not bat into him.
She's four months twice.
Can I suggest you take him out tomorrow night when this is on?
LAUGHTER
Let's...
Let's make this means visit to the Red Chair just before we go.
Hello, who's there?
Hello, sir.
Hello, what's your name?
Thomas.
OK, and where are you from?
From Durham.
Durham.
All right, but you live here now?
Yes.
OK, very good.
I'll be going with this story, Thomas.
So, I asked a girl a couple of weeks ago, and she said yes,
which was great because she's quite hot and, like,
I really got a job going on.
I've got you a couple of weeks and once.
And I'm a rescheduled for tonight.
And she's held it on me again,
so she could come here and watch Kylie and Owen.
So, I have no plans tonight.
I thought I'd come down and see if she wanted to re-arrange for next week.
Well, can I say, Thomas, you're very keen,
because she has given you no indication that she is.
Oh, dear. Well, I guess you didn't look...
The good thing is you didn't make other plans.
That's good. Yeah.
OK, so this is your decision now.
This is you.
This is you sending a message to him.
So, Jessica, are we going to flip Thomas?
Or are we going to let Thomas walk?
This is... Oh, OK.
Please get Kylie to... Kylie, please, will you...
Leave her him off the red check.
Oh, no!
That's the worst ever!
It's a same name. It's a same name.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
I love it.
Wow, literally dumped.
I think everyone won't have the date when you got dumped.
Yes!
Oh!
He's going to be having nightmares.
The rest of his life would go to him.
Oh, he's really shocked.
Can you believe it?
Oh!
Oh, Jessica, what are you thinking?
That's a very loud voice.
Bush.
And a very sexy bit of PR, of course, that the mighty Farell,
he co-wrote...
Do you write all of this on?
I've reduced the whole album.
Yes, sir.
Wow.
Now, is it true that Farell, he was the one encouraging you
to be a bit more family-friendly, a bit more mainstream-wise?
Yeah, yeah, he made me change certain words.
I had a song called So Many Holes.
He made it So Many Proves.
Well, that certainly toned it down.
On prose, just prostitutes.
No.
They're professionals.
Oh, I see.
But silly me.
The ladies in the video still look quite like hoes.
They're professional.
They're in a video.
And then Farell, is it true that he...
I mean, I'm sure you enjoyed working with you,
but he did have some difficulties working with you as well.
Yeah, and when we were working on a particular song called
California Raw, Stevie Wonder,
he came up to the studio, and Farell had called a second-hand
contact from being in the studio with me,
and he kind of froze.
He didn't know how to produce it anymore.
He was stuck.
He was like...
Might have to explain what the...
Yes.
So Farell was in an environment created by Snoop.
Farell was no longer the same Farell.
It's not gonna stop.
Yes.
He was...
He was now someone else.
He was not...
He was not the greatest producer in the world.
He was the greatest producer in the world.
He's a guy in the room.
Excellent.
He's going to the next...
Oh, chill.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh.
Oh, my God.
Take that card, Elevine.
I'm actually talking about it.
I'm sorry.
They're not competitive.
You won't want to buy a thing about that one of yours.
Could you pick a winner?
The before winner?
I mean, I'm not saying anything but we are in a movie together.
I'm not going to just go for no one else.
She so wants to win.
Yeah.
Do you want to win?
Okay, yeah.
She's the best.
Yeah.
This is a weird thing.
Chris Pratt, this seems so unlikely that you have now learned how to do the voices from
Towing.
Yeah, sort of.
Yeah.
Well, I mean, we love that garbage TV back in the States.
My wife was crazy about it.
And when I was here filming Guardians, we shot Guardians of the Galaxy here in London.
And my wife, Anna, came out to visit and she fell in love with the show Towing.
The only way is Essex.
It's this show that's like basically their Jersey shorts.
The Jersey Shore from here.
Right.
It's like this town somewhere, Essex, I guess, and these folks are just like the worst.
And it was like, I'm a parrot a little bit.
And so when I hear it all the time, I just started picking it up and started like I could pick
up their accent and do their accent a little bit.
These are them and I'm like, yeah, I'm okay.
It's going to sound like this is a really embarrassing to do in front of a whole room full
of brits here, but I'll try it anyways.
So it's like, it's like, honestly, I like, I saw this guy.
Yeah, it's like, I was like, I just, they did like Michael Cheat on me when he was in a
beef heart.
Because he's telling me, he's like, you know, I miss you or whatever.
And I'm like, you miss me.
I want my mother.
I'm so proud of you.
I think it was a, some tips, I would say.
Some tips on boxing.
We've got a very, very, very high tech piece of equipment over here.
So if you'd like to come with me, it's over here.
The eye, the eye.
We've been playing with this all afternoon.
I lunged this thing.
Okay, so I'm turning on.
It's on.
Now, ooh, okay, there we go.
So I hit that.
Yeah.
Okay, so, ooh.
It didn't talk.
It didn't talk this afternoon.
What's happened to it?
Shut up.
Just hear it, just hear it.
Just hear it.
It's all about it.
That was really good.
Not only you serious.
He's ready to go.
Okay.
Now, do you have any tips?
Do you have any tips?
Because you're in high heels.
Should I take them off?
No, not you, I think.
Okay.
We're, we're taking this very seriously.
He's talking to me.
I mean, no run-ups.
If you want to take them off, whatever you feel,
I would never be thinking about run-ups.
So Rachel, go for it.
No, don't, don't take your shoes off.
I'll just hit like a girl in these.
Go on, Rachel.
Yeah, so, so competitive.
Wow.
She's down.
She's, she's slim.
She's slim.
Okay.
A flip.
What do you want?
You should do it.
Do you want to go straight?
Or do you want to go?
Oh, I don't mind.
I just feel like I could hit.
Oh, then you seem keen.
Go on, man.
Get any other advice?
Are you left or right-handed?
Right.
So you know, right, like back,
so you really get the whole right grip.
Right, like back.
Okay.
And the aim is just to hit it so it goes away.
You go, you do that.
You go boom, and it goes back up.
Okay.
You go, Graham.
I, honestly, mine was so bad.
So let's see what Rachel gets,
and then I'm the side of what I'm going to do it.
You got a score.
Yeah, you got a score.
So you're left leg forward.
Yeah, yeah.
Are you in range, though?
Are you in range?
Oh, I don't know.
Let's just let I find out.
Is that...
Come forward a bit, come forward a bit.
Yeah.
Because you want to remember your aim is to punch through the bag.
Through, so I want to go like that.
Yes, I like that.
What's the score?
I'm just hitting the middle.
Come on.
Turn around.
Oh!
Let me go, let me go, let me go.
One eighty-two.
Who's going to that?
Let me go next?
Okay, here we go.
Okay, what do I need to?
One eighty-two to beat.
One eighty-two.
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh.
That's a good one.
It's a good one.
Is it a table thing when you don't care, and then you do.
Come and just have a stand down with you.
And it's him last first, Lou.
What?
Okay.
Oh!
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
Wow!
That's a good one.
It's five nine four.
Oh no.
It's five nine four to beat.
Five nine four to beat.
Here we go, here we go.
Oh!
Wow!
Okay.
Anthony Joshua, I'll do it.
How you doing?
No, I'm so good.
I'm just okay, okay.
Okay.
No, no, no, no.
Oh no, I'm going to do this.
I'm going to do this.
Here we go, here we go.
Oh, look, I'm still going.
Okay, there you go.
Okay.
What was yours?
Eight.
I think it was three thousand.
No, it's six, seven two, was it?
Six.
What?
Six, seven two.
Six, three two.
So if you don't beat that,
you'll be able to beat me.
I'm going to look at this.
Okay, okay, here we go.
Here we go.
This is Technically Could Do.
The World Champion.
Oh!
Well done.
Valentine's Day.
Olivia Coleman, what will you be doing on Valentine's Day?
Oh!
Err...
Is this about...
Yes.
That would be watching a film.
Your film comes out on February 14th.
Oh my God, I'm pulling teeth.
Wait, because I thought you meant...
Because the perm years before that,
so I went actually watching on that day,
I thought you meant, what will I be doing?
I was thinking I'd have to do it.
I thought, don't need, yes, I don't want to do it.
It's a bit of whimsy, and too much.
I see, I see.
Well, I'll be sitting with millions of others in his cinema watching my new film, Human Fury.
So sorry, I see what you did now.
Yes.
Thank you.
No, this is a human fury.
A new British comedy, is yourself a Nick Frost and...
Yeah, I'm not on the poster.
A Chris Addao.
Oh, well, that isn't you.
But it could be you with a leg in the air.
Yeah.
Now, I could safely say, ladies and gentlemen,
without fear of contradiction,
it is the best British-based salsa rom-com
I have ever seen.
That can go in the poster, yeah, for sure.
No, it's a really funny sweet film.
It is a lovely film.
Now, Ed, who are you?
I can't actually remember the name of my character, but...
It was a while ago.
An awesome feature, which was promoting a film.
She didn't know who she was playing in the film.
It was finished. It was in the cinema.
It was a long time after we'd filmed it.
You might have checked before you came on a chat show.
I don't know if you know about her, but she is.
I have no idea.
I don't know.
I don't know why this...
Also, because contractually, no offense,
but it was sort of asked to come and...
No, I find that.
But I love you too.
No, no, no, no.
Wow.
She doesn't mean that.
I don't know. I don't know.
She doesn't want to be here, then.
Oh, no, no, no.
I love Greyham.
But I do wonder why they asked me to do it.
I don't help. Do I?
You do it.
I assume thinking she's never been one of my thoughts.
Oh, God.
She's good.
I like her.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I like you.
But you've made a carol, though.
Hiya.
What's your name?
My name is Eileen.
Eileen.
Yep.
I'm guessing you're from Ireland.
I am from Dairy.
We're from Dairy, up to the north of the country.
Okay. And you live there or here?
I started here. I live over there.
Oh, where? What are you doing?
I'm in a costume design.
A costume interpretation.
Okay. There will be subtitles on Friday.
I don't know. Right now, only I can understand the memory of it.
I can't do it.
Yeah, but I know. I can't.
No.
So far you're not missing anything.
I've never heard of costume interpretation before.
It's that costume design, isn't it?
It's a fancier.
It's a fancier, Frank.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
All the labour.
Okay. Off you go.
Right. So lead up to Christmas.
I was back home and had a bit more...
Exactly.
Right.
Did you get any of it?
Christmas. Something about Christmas.
Yeah, Christmas.
That's the only good detail so far.
This pick out words, you'll follow the story.
Blah blah blah. Christmas.
Blah blah blah home.
Born into the shop and I had to get milk and bread.
So I literally was really stressed.
So I was like,
I want to get the groceries.
Let's go.
Told my boyfriend to do a lap and just pick me up.
No need to park the car.
So as planned, I came out, you know, perfect timing.
I silver people, Carrier.
I just casually drifted by casual speed.
So without hesitation, I sprint across.
When we look, when we make groceries,
jump in the back of the car, screaming,
and thump in the back of the chair,
and I was like,
I'm going to show you this.
Go, go, go, go, go.
But taking a mind, it was Christmas,
and I had like a scarf up here,
and a hat.
I got, which was my boyfriend,
torn going to be this middle age, like, 60-year-old woman.
Screamin'.
Jesus!
I'm pushed or foot on the accelerator.
I'm just doing a little post.
Oh!
Good job.
Come on, come on, come on.
One of those.
Very good.