The pity gallery over here, dude.
Whoa, the Guru Kintal feels sad.
Oh, let's comfort.
I dropped the water, dayi, Rory.
Oh, no. I can't see the boss.
F***ing.
That's a good try.
You ready?
Yeah, I'm excited. I'm nervous.
There's always...
The two papers, this is rock.
It's because I've always said last time.
Papers, this is rock.
I don't know. Really?
It's his paper, right, though.
Whatever.
Okay.
You do the top here.
I'll do the...
I'll do the fisting.
LAUGHTER
Nice.
Okay.
No, no, no.
All right, scissors paper and rock.
Oh, yeee. All right, you can go for us.
All right, it's okay. Let's go.
Let's do this.
I always...
I always, always, I'm going to start off.
Something light.
Okay.
Which means...
No, no, we'll start.
Really?
Personally, I don't think you're going to understand
any of the jokes.
LAUGHTER
Rollin' Chinese.
We're going to an Indian.
What do you call Batman when he skips church?
I don't know.
Christian Bale.
LAUGHTER
You laugh because they laugh because...
Oh, did you actually get it?
I'm Christian Bale, like you bale on church,
because Christian Bale was in Batman.
And...
Oh!
She's really smart.
LAUGHTER
Wow.
Okay, I love those.
So that's...
Play.
I'm young and trendy.
No.
Sorry, I'm not old.
Fuck.
LAUGHTER
Cheers.
Oh, okay.
Oh.
Finally.
What do you call a moose with no name?
I don't know.
A non-a moose.
Hi.
That old moose got me to be honest.
All right.
What is a Jedi's favourite computer programme?
A...
Adobe Wan Kunobi.
LAUGHTER
Well, kept it in, kept it in.
That was really good.
Did you write that?
Have you seen Star Wars?
Just lie.
I've seen it.
I've seen the Mandalorian.
Oh, um...
Hey, shut up.
Shut up, sir.
I'm going to get you sword drunk right now.
All right, so are you saying everyone?
No, I'm going to get you sword drunk.
The even Pat's going to be like, finally.
LAUGHTER
Oh, my God.
Wait, it's not.
LAUGHTER
Oh, my God.
Excuse me.
Um...
Okay, I took a riddle in the other day.
Same.
Right.
And like, you know how that shit is like so effective?
It makes you just get through anything.
Well, I was watching, you know, the programme's 60 minutes.
I watched it in 30.
LAUGHTER
Oh, dear.
I got hit in the head with a cannonball today.
Don't even need to finish it.
LAUGHTER
I don't know why I love it.
You think that's what it's saying to the jokes?
I got hit in the head with a cannonball.
LAUGHTER
It's just funny.
You can't even stand the poop.
You're going to get a poop.
I can't even...
I can't even get a cannonball.
LAUGHTER
Generally one time I went to a supermarket
and I was like, can I get a...
I can cook.
And the lady goes, uh...
Okay, I'll try and find one.
If she brought me back, a wine cork.
LAUGHTER
Where on earth did you pull that from?
All right, I got...
You ready? Yeah, I'm ready.
Let's go.
I got hit in the head with a cannonball.
LAUGHTER
Ah!
Yeah, yeah.
Don't worry, I'm not hurt.
It was a soft drink.
LAUGHTER
Okay.
Yeah, it was so much funnier when you just said you got hit.
LAUGHTER
Mmm.
What is a DJ called his son?
I don't know what.
Derrick?
All right, I'm holding it together for this.
I'll tell you right now, I'm holding it together for this.
This funnier.
Uh...
What's blonde, cut in half, and curled up on my bathroom floor?
What?
My pubes. Thanks to Manscape.
Manscape is respected by over 10 million men.
That's 20 million testicles.
Introducing the Manscape Performance Package 5.0 Ultra.
The complete shaving set that will take your package
and make it look less like a joke
and more likely to get strooked.
It comes with a law more 5.0, which is dual blade.
That's true for the price of one.
It's a review with a smooth finish that's irresistibly sleek and utterly bare.
And as women, you know we prefer the bare.
It also comes with the weedwacker 2.0, Eer and North Trimmer.
Hey, Rory, do you both stink?
No, I've got Manscape's crop preserver, the baldie-ordering.
So now might, way in the rock little juntsons, smell like cupcakes.
And to top it off, Manscape is giving away two free gifts with every purchase.
You'll get the silk on marble smooth pocket for your jewels, box at 2.0
and a Traveler bag so you can take your bald trimmer's on the road.
Hey, over to Manscape.com to get the Performance Package 5.0 Ultra.
Use the cord, yeah, man, to get 20% off plus free shipping at 2.3 gifts.
Let's go shave.
I don't have balls.
I do.
All right, I'm going to turn it up a little bit.
Okay.
I had a wanker for my ex-girlfriend last night.
I know it's wrong, but I still have the keys and she's a heavy sleeper.
I do get it. Who said I don't get it?
Who did that?
That's good. Thank you.
Okay, we're going to play.
Okay.
No, no.
Who's there?
Rory.
Rory who?
Rory who sucks.
That's it.
My goodness.
Brother.
Who wants to get that?
No, I'm not.
I really wanted to say that last bit with such conviction.
Links, I've heard that.
I'm going to go on.
All right, cheers.
Cheers, cheers, cheers.
All right, I spent a lot of time preparing this next joke.
Okay.
Which will be ages, because I got here before, like the other day.
And I've worked on this.
Yeah.
I know I was hung up this morning, but I really worked on this joke.
Okay.
I actually put gullible on the ceiling.
Oh.
But you looked up.
Yeah, it's part of the self.
How was that?
I was like, I'm trying to sell my little look.
I think why she didn't look up is because she's like, what is gullible, man?
And what's a ceiling?
I was really hoping I would get you with that one.
No.
That's because she's like, I'm just going to be honest.
Yeah.
What's the difference between subway and my ex-boyfriend?
Tell me.
One gives me a foot long and the other gives me only six inches.
Hey.
Oh, only.
Oh.
Only.
Yeah.
That's like, I thought that was big.
I'm laughing and fucking packed with that.
That's cool.
Okay.
So the subway gives us six inches, right?
I do that for subway once.
You did that for subway once?
Yeah.
What rapper smells the nicest post-colon?
It was good.
I'm all right.
Um, why pig's bad drivers?
Why?
Because they hugged the road.
Why is Burruria bad driver?
Because I lost my license in 2017.
Because he's a pig.
That's just hit up, hit up, Rory.
With some jokes.
I'm on it.
Yeah.
Hello?
Hello, man.
Oh.
Since we're making it personal.
Okay, hang on a second.
Do you have a drink?
Since we're making it personal.
What do you call an anorexic blonde with a yeast infection?
So true.
A quarter pounder with cheese.
Oh.
Rory.
That's not real.
Even this pig wanted that.
That's disgusting.
That is disgusting.
Well, this is the half of the jar.
Did you hear about the terrorist musician?
No.
He's really blowing up on the music scene.
What's the leading cause of pedophilia?
Rory.
Sexy kids.
People are getting confused.
These goddamn sexy kids.
Oh, my God.
What do you call it when you pick a fruit off the vine before it's ready?
I don't know.
Statutory grape.
Who's going on?
I'm going to do that one.
Do you love eating sprays?
No, I'm scared.
Bro, I need to get myself a can in the amount of fireballs I'm going to be having.
Well, since you're not selling footpicks and stuff, what does a blonde word like...
Don't worry, we're going to edit this.
Since you're selling footpicks, what do blondes put behind their ears to make them more attractive?
They're ankles.
Mm-hmm.
Ruby.
Oh, yeah.
He's like, was that a lot?
No, you didn't laugh.
I didn't laugh.
You laughing now, but no.
Oh, my God.
All right, well, cheers to that little party trick I have.
I didn't know you knew about it.
Oh.
I'm listening.
Okay, you know, I'm not very good at spelling.
We know.
Well, I was going to say Hogwarts was an absolute nightmare.
In my head, I'm just like, what, you couldn't spell Hogwarts?
I thought it was a worse.
I thought that was a worse spell.
Wait, what's that?
To no one knows how to spell expel your armors.
It's not a real word.
It is.
Okay.
All right, I think you need a drink.
I think.
What's wrong?
Sorry.
Do I have black stuff in the mirrors?
It's called African American stuff.
Hey, it's the black mask.
All right, thank you.
I went to a 50 con.
A kick in it.
I went to a 50 cent concert last year.
I got to go backstage.
And he's a really cool guy.
He actually gave me a jumper that he made himself.
I was so impressed.
I was like, gee, unit.
I don't get it, but I'm laughing because they're laughing.
I have so many explain.
So gee, unit.
Oh, gee.
You guys have been busy with it, you know.
I've been to his signals.
I've been to his G unit.
G unit was like the group that 50 cent was a part of.
On a ride.
They came out about three years before you were born.
It's like 2006.
2006?
I was like, two.
No, those are the odd.
Sorry.
Okay, what did 50 cent do when he went to dinner?
Fiddy eight.
What do you call a Rackahose half black half white?
I don't know.
50 percent.
Oh.
Get him back with another video.
Oh, we got a video.
You got a video.
No, we got a video.
Everybody drinks.
Everybody drinking for Fiddy.
Fiddy say, I'm all Fiddy nor Ditty.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Pat's like, maybe.
Pat's in his...
Pee-ho-dee.
What are people saying when they see me with staff?
Oh my god, another interracial couple.
That's just no white.
Oh my god.
The couch is coppened, straced, is it?
That's very true.
And I'm like, are you okay?
A blonde is doing a jigsaw puzzle
when a boyfriend walks in and asks,
what are you doing?
She says, it's a jigsaw you idiot.
And he goes, what's it supposed to be?
And she pulls out the box and goes, it's a rooster.
And he says, oh babe, let's put the conflict back in the pack-in.
That's a bad joke.
Oh, okay, that was good.
I reckon that's the best blonde joke I've heard.
Like, this whole time.
That was clever. Did you write that?
Well, what kind of book?
Malfa Frusty's, man.
Oh my god.
I hope we get a throw up on camera, hey?
Oh, no, I got it. I did it.
Yeah, I did something.
I did something.
I know, it's joke.
Have you ever been so ham-ed you can't see?
Yeah, well wait until you meet my ex-boyfriend.
I didn't love it.
Sorry, man.
What was that mean?
It was like, oh, so ham-ed you can't see?
He's punching in the face.
It's between the blind and the blind.
It's good that none of the guys got that joke.
It's a blind joke.
Someone needs to go check on his Mrs. See if she's still breathing.
The blonde is standing on one side of the river
when she sees another blonde on the other side and she yells out,
how do you get over the other side of the river?
And the other blonde says,
don't be stupid, you're already there.
What?
It's okay, it's okay, babe.
Wait, she's like seeing a something in reflection.
No.
What?
What is that sauce?
Oh, okay.
I'll tell you what, these feet picks, Bennistad Sella.
You're doing amazing things.
How do you know what a blonde is used to your computer?
The joysticks wet.
For girls.
I have a new guy.
Okay, mine is her.
I feel like Bennistad is actually getting real angry, I mean.
I don't get a blend.
So what?
I don't get wet.
But you should use men's tape.
With their refreshing New Deodre and skincare routine.
Uh, um,
what do you call a dinosaur that crashes a bus?
What?
Tyranosaurus Rex.
Okay.
This is funny.
How did that happen?
That's it?
Where are you?
Why am I crying today?
Oh, okay guys, I got to...
The pity gallery over here, dude.
The Guru Kintal feels sad.
Oh, let's comfort.
And Patins are right as well.
The cheater, I don't know.
driver.
It's sad to have fun.
Okay, where are you?
Who?
Spice rule.
I'm thinking it.
I'll get out.
What about?
I'm sorry.