Age sucks if you got a face.
But is it because America is really so youth obsessed?
I mean, how?
And in the film, you show kind of that it is hard for a woman
of your age to get the job.
It's beyond difficult.
The only jobs really left now for women
unless they get friendly with people to do films.
But the only jobs that are really commercials,
I just thank God, I made my,
usually not this year, on a protocol girly,
which is for driver-jina.
And it's a...
It may yet?
Well, anyone knows the heartbreak of driver-jina.
LAUGHTER
I was...
I was perfect for it.
And Cavill's follow me home.
LAUGHTER
Three Jewish men are trying to rent my uterus
instead of going to Miami.
LAUGHTER
And there's...
Thank God for these commercials.
There's one called...
Zestra, is that coming in yet?
LAUGHTER
It's like women's...
Viagra has that happened yet?
It's women's Viagra.
And they have this big discussion with me.
Should they make it in pill form?
This is honest to God, true.
There was a lady's favorite.
Pill form or cream?
Because they didn't know which would do better.
And they find a side of these idiots will do it in cream
because if it's in pill form, in a bar,
a man can drop it in a woman's drink.
And she won't know it.
But if you're in a bar and a guy goes,
so where you from?
LAUGHTER
Oh!
Another thing.
I know I'm going to get this alarm a lot.
Charlize Ferrer.
No, I was just...
I was back there freaking out.
You're like the first person who said it perfectly.
Really?
Yes. I'll stop now.
I won't say it again.
It's amazing.
15 years.
And then you came along.
Oh, she's just here.
Do you guys know each other outside of being back there
on a sofa?
I know, John.
And I don't know Steve.
LAUGHTER
John, can I see him on the telly?
You know that's not real.
I know.
Now, it is Jubilee weekend.
Do you have plans?
Anybody got plans?
I didn't realise it was Jubilee weekend.
But when I got here, I got in town a couple days ago
and was invited, I guess, to sit next to the queen
on the boat, going down the...
Oh, you're joking, that's amazing.
Oh, you're joking.
I'm not going to do it.
LAUGHTER
I don't know her.
Four hours.
It's a long thing.
What are we going to talk about?
I don't own crowns or...
Or tiaras or...
No, I don't know if you're joking or not.
Are you joking?
Oh, no, I'm completely joking.
Oh, no.
Nothing...
He has been invited on the boat.
I'm really confused now.
Are you being invited on the boat?
No.
Well...
Did you like him as well?
Nice of me as well.
That's fun.
It's a big story.
I didn't even know there was going to be a boat.
And...
And these two were thinking...
No!
Do they know we have an Oscar?
Do they not know?
It's just another thing you don't have in common with the Queen.
Now, Charlie's there.
Now we're delighted you're here for all sorts of reasons.
I'm so happy to be here. I'm a huge fan.
Thank you.
That's the end of episode one.
The Doctor's thing.
Yeah.
Did that really happen?
My mum will kill me for telling this because it was my...
Our family doctors.
And I...
He'd been...
Our family...
My doctor since I was a child.
And I went to...
As an adult.
Because...
I was...
There was something wrong with my...
Bum.
When you said,
Bum, you looked at me directly in the eyes.
I'm sorry.
I mean, Emma Rouse,
Dunn, Unnerved and E.com.
I think.
There was something...
Do you count?
But there was something wrong with my...
Bum.
LAUGHTER
I was really imagining.
Yeah.
And I was...
I said,
There's this thing wrong with my Bum and he went,
OK.
And I went,
So...
What did he say?
He goes,
Well,
It'll probably be all right.
And I said,
Well, I...
I was really lucky.
I'd like you to just...
If you could make me feel better about...
If I feel better,
then it will be all right.
And he went,
It'll probably clear itself up.
And I said,
Yeah, but...
It's your only way I could be sure...
And he went,
Oh...
You want me to put my finger up there, don't you?
LAUGHTER
No.
Not if it's not magically necessary.
LAUGHTER
And the other...
I think...
Maybe there's a reason,
But what is the reason that you film it
in the school you used to teach?
I think it's therapy, probably.
I mean, natural classroom where I taught,
Because I was just to keep the theme going,
A real teacher for a long time.
Yeah, I taught for...
Yeah, but six years in the school that we film it,
In the classroom that I'm going mad in, and...
But that's really...
Well, that was my classroom, yeah.
But you did it for such a long time, did you ever enjoy it?
Was there ever a moment when you thought,
I like this?
No.
OK.
Well, I met some very nice people there.
And you were like,
You were nominated for Teacher of the Year, weren't you?
Yes, I was great.
I was.
Yeah.
Yeah, you know, yes.
I've told this story many times.
But Teacher of the Year is a very prestigious award,
It's taken very seriously, rightly,
By the hard-working teaching community.
And my head teacher called me in,
And he was wetting himself laughing.
If I couldn't stop laughing for the first ten minutes,
And he went,
I went, what...
Why have you called me here?
He goes,
You've been...
You've been nominated.
And I went, oh, OK.
And it was by a very sweet girl called Gemma,
I've humiliated many times.
And it's a six-page document that people have to fill in
For the reasons why you should be nominated for Teacher of the Year.
It was blank,
Aside from one sentence that she'd written on it,
Which was of the reasons why she'd written on it.
She was like,
I'm telling you,
I'm not going to write it down.
It's a book that I've written.
It's a book that I've written on.
I'm not going to write it down.
She'd written on it,
Which was of the reasons why you think he should be teacher of the year.
And she'd written,
He's a well-good laugh,
And he don't make us do no work.
LAUGHTER
Why have you seen more of you two together?
It's a pairing.
It really is.
It's a match made in heaven.
Oh, my God.
Now, Jack and Chan.
Yes.
Jack and Chan.
Yeah.
Right.
I haven't done that once.
I'm very stupid.
I haven't seen it in my hands.
I'm going,
Jackie Chan.
I'm not doing it.
Because is it true that everyone just goes,
Jackie Chan?
Yeah.
I really hate that.
I'm trying to do it.
Whenever I go in the Euro in America,
Especially the father-of-the-chews,
Look, Jackie Chan!
Why nobody see Robert De Niro?
Why?
That's a Robert De Niro.
Wow.
Dax King Hoffman, Jackie Chan.
One day, one day, I hope people...
Wow, that's the Jackie Chan.
Yes.
That's Jackie Chan.
I'm trying.
I'm trying to Australian myself.
You just come from the Can film festival?
Yeah.
Can film festival.
Do you enjoy things like that?
Are they fun?
Or is it just business?
The whole thing about those big events,
the particularly in candles, red carpet things.
Do you enjoy them?
No, I can't do any of that.
I really can't.
I've seen you.
Have you on a red carpet?
I don't think so.
No.
Have you?
Have you show up at things?
Not much, to be honest.
But you've done posh things.
You've met the Queen, haven't you?
I haven't met the Queen.
Yes, I haven't met the Queen.
I think it was one of those receptions for people in the arts.
You should have been there, Graham.
I was.
You were overlooked.
Yes, I was.
Yes, you were the dirty potty man.
Yeah, I was.
You know what I was amazed at with the Queen?
She's very tiny, which is something for me to say,
because I'm quite short.
And she moves as if on roller blades.
She just slides up like that.
Is there no actual walking sky?
I don't know what's going on under there.
She might be on castors for all the men.
But she comes to where you are, the group where you are.
For a start, you have to, you have to tussle with that whole idea of will you curse?
You went, will you curse?
And I decided before, no, look, curtsy.
It's no.
I'm not going to bow down before Royal.
I'm not going to.
And then immediately you do.
Immediately you curse.
You're barging much, too low.
No.
That's really revolting.
And then I mean, of me, I mean.
And then, the Queen says a small, there was a group of about four of us around her.
And she says a very small thing, you know.
So are you enjoying the evening?
And everybody goes like this.
She's like,
I'm not.
So the Queen, I think people are just nervous.
Are they eager to please?
Don't want to be beheaded or something.
I'm in the Queen.
So the Queen, I'm sure, must think that she's a great comedian or something.
That's what she says is people forning and loving and everything.
She says, I was doing it.
Why was I doing it?
I did it.
You met the Queen.
Yes, I do.
You met Jack Jarrett.
I was in Hong Kong.
I remember, and long, long time ago, my English is so bad in that time.
I remember when Queen was here, you used her hand.
Otherwise you were standing here.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Royal, what?
You're Royal Highness?
Yes, Royal Highness, yes.
I then have the remember.
You're Royal Highness.
Then it's when we're playing around.
Queen's coming, Queen's coming.
Then, what should I say?
Then I see the Queen, the Queen, stop, stop, stop, so quick.
No, no, no, no, no.
I said, oh, OK.
Then when she comes, you're already ruined.
I just admit it like you.
I admit it like that.
She stands still standing there.
The people are into the Jackie Chan and her.
Oh!
She keep talking to me.
My head is empty.
I don't know what she's talking about.
You know, honestly, go away.
Go away.
Leave me alone.
I'm telling you.
Of course, I'm so happy just standing here,
more than like a three-minute, five-minute,
but I just don't go away, please.
Don't talk to me anymore.
I don't know how to answer back.
I'm going to America.
That's right.
If they're at New Zealand, that's right.
And they got whisked off.
They got whisked off on a little...
Oh, that's good.
That's a hell of a service.
Oh, my God, the glasses, champagne.
Can we say whisked on BBC One?
I think.
She can't say whisked off.
Oh, that...
You can say piss stuff, though, can you?
Yes.
Oh, it's all good now.
Yes, yes.
Minutes in. Good night.
Now, did you drive yourself here tonight?
No.
No, I've got my driving license.
No, I'm still on driving me.
Would you get in the car with them?
If so...
Come on, be rough, honey.
You're coming to black moron.
No, it depends.
But now my husband is officially allowed to drive.
Yes, I would get in the car with him.
Good.
I know, yeah.
That was right.
It's only two sixty-one years.
But I mean, the children are teaching you.
No, well, before I was too pissed to drive you.
Okay, fair enough.
I went out for my test and I'd go,
let's see him in, I'd go,
no, Mr. Osborne, come back in on the day.
I'm not even getting in the car with you.
Walking on the test,
I'd be in the bottle of oak,
and my pocket didn't go any good.
Did you learn in a manual or an automatic?
I can drive anything, one of those, a few trees.
That's all I've got.
There are anything you can use yet.
No.
I've got a job.
I think that's the only solution.
Is that anything that can go on BBC One?
Not yet.
You've just had a promotion.
It's all DVD extras.
I know.
But it's a proper western.
I mean, we see Tom Hanks gun-token,
which we already see.
Well, I don't have, I don't wear one.
I am given one later on,
so it's not like, you know, I'm not doing the root and toot and kind of,
you know, but I ride a horse,
and I drive a wagon,
and I've discovered, so I'm not a rider per se,
but I did learn.
I had a fabulous,
got to know a fabulous whop name,
Wimpy, who was my horse.
Wimpy was my horse.
And I don't know if anybody here has written a lot,
or made a western Emily has a couple of westerns under her belt,
as I recall.
Emily, my darling, how are you?
How are you?
Wonderful to see you.
It's good to see you.
Emily Glunt.
Do you know what I'm about to do a western?
Like, next year, I'm doing a six-part western,
and we were just discussing how allergic I am to horses,
and I do every scene with a horse, you know.
I'm going to be anti-histamine, up to my eyeball.
Do you have to kiss the horse?
I do.
Yes, and that isn't what happens in westerns,
you make out with your horse.
You develop an affection for those beasts.
You're a champion.
You're kind of wick.
Every morning, you throw your arms around Wimpy,
and you say, how are you, my darling, little chestnut?
I'm so convinced about you.
Which you sort of have to do, because I have a feeling that horses, honestly,
they would much rather live in a world without human beings climbing on top, though.
And they know the moment you climb on their back, that you're terrible at riding.
Like, I mean, I've been learning right now,
I'm in London now, rehearsing for it,
and I go riding three times a week,
and every time they give me a different horse to see, you know, how you fare,
with one that's more sprainy, or one that's less of a Ferrari.
And I got on one of the other day called Rusty.
My god, I almost took off with me, it was terrifying.
I couldn't walk the next day, Rusty did me in.
No, no, no.
Rusty did her in.
Rusty did me in.
Oh, wow.
Is that the name of the film?
That's what he is.
Oh, my god.
I'm a gin now, Sir Patrick Stewart, and you don't really use the Sir much, do you?
Um...
What should I...
Sorry, should I have been calling you...
No, I shouldn't. Am I supposed to?
No.
Okay.
But do you...
No, do you...
I take my lead from Sir Ian,
whom we've both shared some time with.
Yes.
And he is...
He is so...
Flegmatic about all of that, and I just...
You know, it's a great honour, but it's not something that I need to press.
When you bump into another Sir when you're out and about.
Do you then...
Do you...
Do you pull the other Sir?
Well, you must roll in Sir circles.
Okay.
Circles.
Sir, sir.
I just...
I just opened it.
Yeah.
It's minute.
That was alright, man.
Sir, I heard it.
Can I read the ignorant American in the ass?
So, how do you become a Sir?
Um...
Well, Patrick, how?
I don't know.
Well, you know, it's a case of...
Oh, no, no, no.
I got mine on the Queen's Birthday Honours.
But you have reminded me that I did have a Sir encounter,
only a few weeks ago in Los Angeles.
A rather fancy...
In fact, extremely fancy restaurant.
Tell them what it is, they'll know.
Um, it was the... the... the Tower Bar.
Uh, something to tell you?
No.
No, yeah.
Guys, that's cool.
No, no, no, no.
Sit, sit, sit.
Look up the tower.
The Tower Bar.
Oh, man, it's on you.
What?
It's on you.
Oh, man.
Oh, go on.
Keep going.
You keep going.
Okay.
Well, not a Tower Bar, it is a spot.
I got a feeling this isn't going to work out.
It's a spot.
It's quite far away.
Um, so we had four of us were seated at a table,
about 15 minutes later,
into the restaurant, walks Sir Paul McCartney.
Wow.
Good.
Now, Paul and I have a very slender relationship,
but it's lasted decades.
Okay.
I first encountered him in 1964.
No.
When his girlfriend, Jane Asher,
then, had told him that I loved Aston Martin's.
I was driving a battered old Ford,
but Aston Martin's were my dream car.
She told him this.
And one night, we knew he was seeing the show.
There was a knock on my door.
And I said, yeah, come in.
I'm there in my underwear.
As usual.
Well, I always...
As you break people, I have a round.
I have a round back just in the hope.
I'm in, I'm in my pants.
Yes.
I'm ready for you.
Come in.
And the door opened, standing there was Paul McCartney,
who I had never met before.
And this was 1964.
And he said, Jane says that you like Aston Martin's here.
Drive this.
Wow.
And he tossed a bunch of keys off the window.
And it was an ass.
It was easy.
Anyway, you want to hear the rest of the...
Keep going.
We're in the fanciest restaurant in LA.
We're now in the Tower Bar.
Tower?
Oh!
What?
Oh, my God!
Oh!
It's a legend.
I am feeling less, less good now.
Keep going.
You're in there.
The Paul McCartney's coming.
I'm ready for you.
You know him in the 60s.
And he sees me and comes over and I stand up and say,
Hi, and we have a big hug in the restaurant.
And I'm very much aware that there's all the tables
are full on this kind of thing.
And we talk for five or six minutes,
and he goes and sits down.
Five minutes go by, and into the restaurant walks a ringo star.
I swear to you.
I'm not making this happen.
What were they together?
They were...
Oh, they were at the same table.
Well, they were at the same table.
Well, we were at the Tower of Bartholomew.
I am expecting so many free meals.
And we finish early, and I get up to go,
and Paul stands up to say goodbye, and we have a hug.
And this we have a hug.
He says into my ear,
Do you know a ringo?
I said, yeah, of course.
I've never met him, but I'm...
Oh, ringo, come on, come over here.
Hang on a minute, he said,
Sir Ringo, Sir Patrick, Sir Paul.
Hey, we've got the Knights of the Round Table.
Oh, you're doing well.
You got that.
You're doing well.