I think you're gonna use mouth and get a pump and down on this.
You're gonna actually fix it.
You gotta erase that.
You mean?
You're gonna erase that.
Oh!
Hey buddy.
How are you?
It's been a while.
I'm good.
Yeah?
Is that how usual way of saying hello, isn't it?
Hello.
It's good to see you, man.
Likewise.
What's been going on?
Um, I don't know.
Not much.
I'm running.
Sumo.
How's that going?
It's going well.
That's going fine.
Yeah.
I'm wearing polar shirts now.
It looks great.
It looks exciting.
Thank you.
Digging the vibe.
Digging the look.
Digging.
What are you up to?
Just bring it back.
Anyway, let's get on to the segment.
Yeah, good chat.
Move on to the segment.
Um, would you like to start?
I would love to begin.
I'd love to begin.
Please tell me a joke.
How are you?
I'm not tall enough.
You're a bit too weak.
That's my...
Oh, change...
Yeah, okay.
Tristan, my public is...
I changed.
Whoa!
You changed.
You've got famous?
Yeah.
What, um, life's about change.
Life's about change, pal.
Mmm.
Life's about change.
What do my ex-girlfriend
and a public toilet
have in common?
What?
Um, they're both usually busy
and full of shit.
All right.
What's Michael Jackson's favorite painting?
I could probably guess this one if I tried.
Van Gogh.
It's a monochleeta.
Oh, no.
How many of these do you have?
Hundreds.
Pages.
How did the TikTokers pay for their rent?
Now, by explaining this video is sponsored by Surfsharp.
It keeps your personal data protected
from online criminals and big companies.
A VPN makes sure that your city, country, and download history
aren't attached to your identity.
And that's important in this day and age.
Surfsharp's CleanWeb feature blocks ads, stops malware,
and keeps track of fishing attempts against you,
which means it's looking out for your best interest.
But Alan, what if I'm on holiday?
Shut up.
Doesn't matter about that.
You can change your geographical location back to your home country
so you can keep up with the movies and TV shows that you enjoy.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
Surfsharp offers a 30-day cashback guarantee,
which means there's no risk in trying.
You could do so much in 30 days.
You could watch every episode of Love Island.
And I, that's what I do every day.
Surfsharp offers a 30-day cashback guarantee,
which means you can try it and test it.
And if you don't like it, you can get your money back off the 30 days.
Use promo code, you're mad for three months for free.
What's more than three for three months?
You're getting me? What the heck?
Hit that link down below.
They say 9 out of 10 people suffer from diarrhea.
I guess that makes me number 10 because I love it.
What do you call it when two transgender b****s have sex?
Uh...
What?
Micro-transact.
I don't even get any more understand of that one.
Oh, all right.
I thought that was quite good.
Pull you off the booze.
Well, I mean...
I'm an artist.
I went for a walk with a girl the other day.
Hey, man.
Sorry.
Well, he's right.
It's tighter as a walk until she saw me in the bushes.
Then it became around, run.
And it became around.
It became around.
If you tell him what?
Around.
All right.
Have you got what?
Why is China bad at football?
Why?
Because every time they get a corner, they open a restaurant.
You know, like...
Chinese restaurants.
Do the accent.
Reach a corner.
No, you're...
You're the only one.
You did the team.
No.
No, the one.
Not the one.
I hope you guys know that you're creating a culture of racial division.
Yes.
I was at the dentist the other day.
And the dentist said, oh, this is going to sting.
And I said, okay, go ahead.
And he says, you're a fat loser.
Is that...
Have you just modified one of your bits?
No.
Oh, I just kind of like that bit.
That's how the bit I had.
Have you said that movie where Johnny Depp gets molested?
No.
It's called Who's Eating Gilbert's Date?
He wrote that.
I thought it was a part of the Caribbean.
Like the Caribbean...
Oh, that's a big sense.
No, that doesn't make sense.
I thought it was called the fear and molesting.
He molested you.
I wanted to just do an hour of that.
I think I'm a cop.
I thought it was called...
Amber heard something.
But what's the difference between a hormone and a vitamin?
Oh, what?
You can't hear a vitamin.
Oh, I got that fear.
Yeah, that hurts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel it.
That's good.
Yeah, because you can hear a hormone.
Yeah, well, we're going to work on our chemistry.
What do you call a Chinese guy with a camera?
I'm not a Ching Chong, right?
What?
What are you calling?
Filming!
Oh!
It's not a snapper.
It's not a Godzilla.
Dude, that's racist.
They can't say L.
Filming.
When...
Continue.
Fuck it.
Um...
Hey.
Homo...
Oh, hey.
Give me a joke.
The dude should do ASMR.
Did you know...
Homo was so... was in... was...
The other day, I saw a stop sign, a road sign.
Let me do that again.
One time, I saw a sign that said, watch for children.
And I thought to myself,
Huh, that's a good deal.
So I traded in my Rolex,
and now I get free iPhones and Jordans at home.
Because the children make them...
to... to joke about the child labor state.
Say the child labor of the man.
That's the real thing, yeah.
Oh.
You're a pedagogy.
This one will never make the...
I'm disappointed.
My girlfriend told me to stop singing,
I'm a believer, or she dumped me.
I thought she was joking.
Yeah.
But then I saw her face.
And I'm a believer.
I'm not good at finding the clitoris.
I'm just joking.
Probably because I don't belong in the hood.
That was bad.
It didn't belly button.
And what?
Ellen, would you believe the doctor told me I had to stop masturbating?
I said, why doctor?
And he said, because I'm trying to examine you.
Oh.
It's just like the first joke that pops up when you Google down jokes.
It's just a joke.
Zero or all?
When Hammer was in prison,
he used to put butt, used to pour butter on all the bars of soap.
So people would drop them more when in the shower.
There's a dirty little freak.
Isn't soap already separate?
Yeah, but you met at Atrice Lippurit.
You said it would constantly drop.
Oh, okay.
That's what you do.
You're a slippery guy.
You're a manipulative fucking.
You're a shit.
I'm ungrateful little freak.
Oh!
I'm agent.
Now I feel like I'm a...
I'm a doctor's masturbating.
I like...
Shut the fuck up, Ellen.
Why are chickens so funny?
Why?
Um...
Oh, I know that one.
It's the...
I think I was gonna do that.
Oh, because they make good jokes.
No, can you not trample on my fucking punch lines?
Oh, fucking dickhead.
Is why I didn't want to work with him today?
Fucking hell.
All right, I tell you, stupid fucking robot.
I'm trying to have fun.
You're not...
It's kind of your fault that it's not going well.
Fuck off.
Oh, fuck.
What?
I wanted to say something.
I wanted to stop looking at something.
You did it.
You did some good jokes or what?
Fuck me.
I was talking to fucking software.
Fuck you.
Stop.
I was just joking.
It was a fun hit.
Yeah, it was a fun hit.
It's not.
Yeah, I still work non-stop.
Why are chickens so funny?
Why?
Because!
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Nice.
I'm so confused.
It's too...
What?
It's dead, I'm just moving back together.
I still don't know if I'm attracted to the hammer world.
What the hell?
You're like, I'm a man.
Love you, Syracuse.
What?
Are you a pothole?
That was great, I think.
I was like, fuck you.
I'm a bit scared.
I was mad at you.
I was like, fuck you.
Let's go!
I think it's your turn.
That's funny, Steve.
I just wanted to know, I wasn't going to talk to him once I started doing this.
Just make sure that.
The cat says otherwise, I mean.
Hammer's new special, it should be called Oranges the New Hack.
That's a good idea.
That was better than any of your roast jokes to get the killer.
You lost his wall pal.
Yeah, the user that says otherwise.
I guess it should be kissing makeup.
Yes.
Are you tracking down?
Oh.
Yeah.
What's that, Rayby?
What's that?
It's called Taking Charge.
What about this?
This is what disillite in the mood.
I suggested to my wife that she looks sexy with her hair back.
Oh.
Apparently, that's incisited to say to someone during chemo.
Oh, fuck.
She doesn't whip that hair back and forth.
Cancer does.
It's the same joke that he told.
To reminisce about prison,
Hammer sometimes does an escape room,
while being angly penetrated by the security guard.
Just to reminisce.
Did you find these on the internet or did you write these on the road?
Yeah, I could tell.
Because they're good.
How can you tell if your wife is dead?
I don't know how.
The sex is the same, but the dishes start to pile up.
Oh, God.
You know, learning the dishwasher or whatever.
That's pretty nice.
That's good gear.
I don't use dishes. I just get taken out.
Hammer is so fat, not even door ought to explore him.
That's a child, cousin.
When you were a regular heavy 32,
these are those jokes.
This is not good.
Me as well.
Here we go.
Self-chop.
That's so much.
And the shot is actually more intense.
Just a fella.
That's how it goes.
You're up.
Alex.
Come back to us.
He's drooling.
Would you like a tissue?
Yeah.
Good thing it's good and free.
How about you?
Where's the bottom?
You put your finger in his mouth and get him on this.
You got to raise it up.
Oh my God.
Holy shit.
Wow, Nikki eats a lot of pineapple.
Oh my God.
That's so much.
That's so good.
Guys, can we just get back to the jugs?
This is it.
Fuck, get that.
It's a lot of pineapple.
It's supposed to be about the jugs.
Another one.
I'm gonna get it.
You didn't even finish your last shot.
I know.
Don't hold them though.
Oh my God.
Is it my joke?
How many feminists does it take to change a light bulb?
I don't know.
Don't be stupid.
Feminists can't change anything.
Am I right?
We should ask our local feminists.
What do you think about that?
What's the difference between a rock star and a gynecologist?
A rock star fucks his singers while a gynecologist sucks his fingers.
I give you love, I love it.
I give you love that one.
We need to get away from all the skills jokes.
As before I saw these jokes.
These are amazing football jokes.
Did you know that black holes are billions of years old?
Amazingly, some of the black holes Stephen Hawking studied were only 14 years old.
Oh my Lord Jesus.
This is a pedophile.
I'm not a pedophile.
We just got an additional camera.
Glad joke was done.
Why did the seamen cross the road?
Because I put on the wrong socks this morning.
You can look at me when you tell the joke.
No, it's just too embarrassing.
Who's there?
Quiet horse.
Quiet horse who?
That's great.
Did you write that one?
I'm not saying I'm not saying good.
I'm not saying good.
In betray day, neck or pedophile.
We like to just do a little actual dad joke.
Just to give him a guess.
I've actually had a pretty good day so far.
I got working up with a blowjob this morning.
Crashly.
Thank you.
It's probably actually the last time I slept on the park again.
Wow, if I didn't fuck up the wording.
Yeah, it was the wording.
The wording got you.
Park was my cousin's name.
Actually, that was Lee Sun Park.
Oh, yeah.
You might know this guy's about what do you call a Chinese guy with one leg?
Limping.
Taiwan shoe.
Free Taiwan baby.
Wow, political.
I'm a political guy now.
I once asked my dad, how do I spell penis?
He said, oh, Sun, you should've asked me last night.
I had one to tip my tongue.
Tell me you something else.
You have the jokes about your dad touching you, don't you?
I'm not freaking him.
Oh, bad out.
Bad out.
Oh, what?
For anyone who missed that, I'll just broke the chair by being fat.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
You've got an sour.
You've got weird hours has arrived.
Yeah.
Your name is Wobbles, you better run.
Oh, my God.
Oh.
What is he?
Can we call that from the tape, please?
I'm so sorry.
Is it my time?
This is why the easy mutation dad joke channels can't date us because of the weirdness.
You think it's just about telling jokes, no.
It's about fun and soft.
It's about me and we.
All right, what about this?
You know the people in Dubai don't like the floodstones?
Yeah, why is that?
But the people in Abbey, Dabbey, do.
Tell you what, that joke was rock bottom.
What's the hardest part about eating a vegetable?
What?
The taste and then putting it back in the wheelchair.
Maybe I'll regret saying that tomorrow.
Do you know that my siblings had,
is that all the Chinese 100 people's siblings?
No, that's racist, dude.
What are you talking about?
You know my sibling had gender affirming surgery and now reads the news on today FM broadcast.
Talk about transistor radio.
Wow, you really have a knack of playing with words amazing.
I really enjoyed being read it, put word by word just to make sure you got the language correctly.
Today is forever.
What's...
You mean?
FM sounds like the choice they're given on the form.
What's the difference?
It's me!
It's a Spanish spine.
Did you actually fall?
What?
He did fall, it smells like prison officers penis.
I'm clutty, what's the difference between three dicks and a joke?
Tell me.
Andrew's mother can't take a joke.
She can take three dicks.
She's a fucking ski-sie little whore.
Are you serious?
She's a dirty bird, your mother.
That's like one of the most viral clips I've ever had.
Oh, is it?
Am I in it?
You were in the video.
Diffin' Abby. Are you serious?
That's what my family's for.
Oh, that's the different Abby joke.
I don't know, I don't watch the videos.
I don't watch the videos.
I don't watch the sound of this at all in fact.
I just skip to my jokes and then I skip the rest.
I should do another one though.
Yeah, do another one because that one was dog shit.
They're all dog shit.
Okay, how about this one?
Did you know that Jack the Ripper, after being caught for his crimes, escaped and moved to Melbourne, Australia?
Did you guys know that?
I didn't know that, tell me more.
Well, at first I was surprised until I realized it's in his name.
He's Jack the Ripper.
What?
You trust a lot.
Someone should rip me apart.
Like the...
Did you even get that joke?
A Ripper is like what you call a Australian colloquialism.
Yeah, but why not?
He's a Ripper.
We smell them, he's like the most like...
He's like, let's do it.
This happened in the 1800s when they went their culture.
We call it like kind of this kind of strippers, guy the ribbers?
I don't know.
I have to do what I have to do.
I have to do a telejoy.
Alright.
Alright, yeah, yeah.
He's where I write myself.
Yeah!
Andrew!
Alright.
What?
Alright, here's the original.
Ready?
What did the Terminator say at the grocery store
when someone asked for help finding the milk?
What?
I'll be back.
Oh!
That's a pretty lunch.
Tell me, girl, baby.
Oh, well, well, well, what does the whorny frog say?
Rob it.
Boo!
That's about your dad's side to get deep in.
Oh my god.
We discovered that everyone's better with that one though.
What do you get when you mix up...
...brown chicken and a brown cow.
What?
Brown chicken, brown cow.
That's pretty good.
That's not the answer.
Sorry, sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
We're laughing at your double allegations, pal.
Oh my god.
What's the difference between Wuhan and Vegas?
What happens in Vegas stays in Vegas.
Good for you.
That's a rude one.
Oh, when he sweated it off again, you get it.
What has two legs and bleeds?
What?
Half a dog.
Jesus.
No, what?
He's so...
He's so funny.
Uh, Jada.
Sleepy Joe, sleepy Joe.
Why is a threesome...
Why is a threesome with two Thai girls...
...like Wendy Mulanari?
Why?
Because he's smashing balls.
I want you to drink that and I want you to think about what you've done today.
That's it, right?
Better ending.
What do you think is gonna be a better ending?
It's great ending.
Turn me off.
Oh.
Oh my god.