This one's from everyone's favorite Alan Fang.
I don't know him.
Why do ginses smell so bad?
Why?
Yeah, look at your bow.
I bow.
How are you?
I am good.
You're good? I'm great.
Good.
We have to invest each other.
You're the last girl of the group.
The final boss.
That doesn't count, does it?
Bowser.
We haven't started yet.
Is it the green one?
No, it's fine.
Okay.
All right.
Um, oh, okay.
Wait, do you do one, two, three, or scissors paper rock?
Should we do rock purposes?
No, scissors paper rock.
Should we do it for him?
Yeah, three rock.
Rock paper scissors.
Boom!
Sounds so weird.
I don't like it.
Yeah.
Okay.
I like to tell dad jokes.
No shit.
I do, I like to tell dad jokes.
Um, he laughs at everything I say.
Did I?
When?
Did I laugh?
Oh.
Yeah, yeah.
Hello.
Already spilling it.
Thank you.
Oh, you're a jossess for staff.
Nah, foxes.
Oh, all right.
I got a long jug for you.
I'm sorry.
I got a long jug for you, because you seem to like those.
I do.
Uh, three guys are at a ski lodge.
Uh, uh, and they didn't have enough room at the hotel.
So they all had to share a bed.
Uh, and uh, in the morning, uh, the guy who was sleeping on the left side says,
I had the- I had the craziest dream.
Uh, I got a- I got a hand job from a guy.
And then the guy on the right side of the bed said,
That's crazy.
I had the same dream.
And then the guy in the middle said,
That's weird.
I had a dream.
I was skiing.
I see it was jacking him.
Yeah, sick.
Ooh.
That's good.
I like it.
Yeah, that's good.
That's pretty funny.
Do you have to call them my dad is dead jerks?
Oh, he's dead boy.
He's dead.
No more, though.
Just checking.
What, what, what?
What?
Would you have to call them what?
My dad is dead jerks instead of dad jerks.
Deceased dad jerks.
Yeah, thanks for the punch out.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Is that the joke?
That was the joke.
That was the mean.
I can do another one.
It was mean.
I want to do any mean ones.
I had another mean one.
This dad died in the sea.
Do you want to do the other mean ones?
No, no, no.
Keep it, keep it for the next one, right?
OK.
Why did the mafia cross the road?
Why?
Forget about it.
Oh, it's so racist.
Spaghetti.
I'm trying to get it.
No.
I'm going to get it.
Fuck.
Oh.
All right.
OK.
I want to win this.
I really want to win.
You're doing badly then.
I know, I know.
You should make me laugh.
OK.
How do you tell the difference between a pure bread cat
and an in bread cat?
One cat has two slices of bread on the inside of it.
That's the criteria.
It's a real bread.
Why does Dr. Pepper come in a bottle?
Why?
Because his wife died.
Do you come in a bottle too?
No, I use socks.
I've got one for you then.
Did you hear about the erectile dysfunction?
Sorry.
Seminole?
No.
It was a flop.
No one came.
I was there.
You see only one.
All right.
Why did the pirate get cancelled?
Why?
Because he used the hot R.
Nice.
Yeah.
What's the love?
No.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, I'm dead inside.
This is going to be real.
Yeah.
All right.
I told you.
Oh.
It's just like an awkward tick.
All right.
I put it on the top.
A awkward tick.
All right, go on.
What's the difference between you and a calendar?
What?
A calendar has dates.
The gloves are off.
I promised there's no more men once.
Don't cry.
What, what do you call an Asian dwarf?
Just a small person.
Tiny.
I don't know if I fully get that.
What's the word meant to...
TIE.
Tiny
Dwarf eyes not Asian eyes dwarf eyes are like
A
Good
Is it my turn? No, it's my turn. Okay, this will be shit
Some of a laugh
What just snakes call it when they do 69 what 11?
That's pretty good. That's pretty good
I think it's pretty good. That's pretty good. Thank you
Why don't they teach drivers ed and sex education on the same day in the Middle East?
Why? Because it wears out the camel
Because of the hums
Grinding how do I make you laugh? What do you like?
Can I know funny jokes?
Fair enough
I got on a real tear for 69 jokes, so I like this naquel. That was it's good right? What does 69 plus 69 equal?
Stinna for four but you laughed like I'm so bad at maths. I was actually trying to do that
It's a hundred and 38. All right. It was a joke ever you didn't have to actually do the calculation
He was struggling. I was trying to help
I can do basic math
I'll have you know I can act to double digit numbers at the care of it
How do New Zealanders find sheep in tall grass?
How irresistible
That's actually exactly what I like all right good stuff. Oh sheep fucking jokes. That's that's how you get us
What do you call a bug that lets you fuck its wife a
Cockaroch
That's good that's good
Hey bug can I fuck your wife?
What do you call a party with a hundred dwarves? What a little get together
I like it. I heard about a tattoo place that was giving out free tattoos to women who would flash their boobs. Is that why you have all your tattoos? Yeah, it was that tattoo for tattoo special
That's that's good. Thanks. So how many free tattoos did you get?
202018 it's 20 different
I'd love to have extra nipples
Quit gìing, you're ready
That's an old joke, eh?
No, we'll see you then.
That's gonna be like a whole hour on that being a pro, but...
Like a prison name.
Jokes about being a pro.
Anyway.
What's the difference between white owls and black owls?
White owls go,
whoo-toot! And black owls go,
what up dog?
That can be a man really, that's good.
Do you know why I like jokes about cats?
Why?
Because I love kitten around.
That's for you.
Okay, this is, I like this one.
How do you stop a dog from hump in your leg?
Piss on your own leg.
No.
You pick it up and suck its c-
Hey, nice.
I'm a dog of a god that's gonna come in handy.
Oh yeah.
Oh, you've already got a pod, okay?
I thought that one was good.
I clearly.
Okay, so I'm going to the couch for jokes.
I haven't seen any of these, but the gang sent me some jokes.
All right.
I'm gonna read them one at a time.
Okay.
This one's from everyone's favorite Alan Fang.
I don't know him.
Why do genders smell so bad?
Why?
So blind people know who to avoid as well.
Still not a ginger.
Look pretty ginger to me.
All right, what about this one?
Why do they call genders in China?
Hey, what about my turn?
Nush.
Drink.
What do they call genders in China?
What?
Gross f-
That's really funny.
Yeah.
Should I do this?
Yeah, do the accent.
No, I'm not doing the accent.
I'm just choosing not to do the accent.
That was great.
We can cut some of those shitty ones out anyway.
Don't order clothes.
Don't touch it, bro.
Oh my god.
Who's reaching for something else as well?
No, it wasn't.
I was reaching for something else.
This one's from a killer.
I'm a f-cking loser.
No, it's not as well.
This is a killer.
Knock, knock.
Boo.
You don't have to cry.
It's only a joke.
You have really nice eyes.
You're gonna get out of here.
Yeah, let's go.
That was so shit.
Um.
I've got one for you.
Do you know what makes cats great bosses?
What?
They have excellent leadership.
You ask for dad jokes and then I say dad jokes.
And you just...
This is yeah, man.
We want racism, homophobia, and sexism.
That's how I'd be like it.
I just...
What's the difference between menstrual blood and sawdust?
Oh, one's like...
...find getting your mouth.
You can't gargle sawdust.
Yeah.
I see where these are going.
Oh.
Do you like moon cups?
Andrew?
Catches it all in there.
That's fucked.
Alright, this is from Abby.
Hi.
Do you hear that Viagra is a treatment for some then?
No.
It doesn't cure it, but it does keep the sheet out of your legs.
What's your legs?
I don't know.
You don't get that.
Sorry.
You said out of your legs.
I'm just a timing pass.
I'm sorry.
I'm trying to include everyone.
I got one more to end it.
It's still going to get two million views.
Not for the comedy.
When is an elf not an elf?
When.
When he's sucking on your c***, then he's a goblin.
We're talking about a goblin.
What's your name?
I'm Andy.
Hello.
Welcome to my screen call.
Fantastic.
That's fantastic.
That's great.