Good, can I just say I heard all of those.
We know.
I feel red, right?
Sup, Rory?
Dark people.
We are in America.
You're cool.
We've got something very special for you.
We have got a dad joke since all about America.
And we are doing two teams.
Whole crew Pat has picked his team.
Team Pat.
I have picked my team.
And these are the rules.
Regular dad joke rules apply.
If you laugh, you have to take a shot.
But not only that, you also have to tag team out with one of your team members on the couch.
Team with the most points at the end wins.
Let's go!
We are doing this for America.
And I'm doing this for England.
We are doing this for England.
This is my rock.
Who are the hardest working Americans who are they?
Mexicans.
Okay.
Aye aye aye.
Not laughing at this one.
I'm not going to tag down.
What's the worst band in America?
What?
I don't know if you've heard of them.
They have a song that goes boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Is it a tally band?
There's a quiver.
Is it my Spotify rap?
What are you the second time?
Oh god.
You know one day I would love to visit the Grand Canyon.
Side note, Peyton hates it when I call it the John of the Grand Canyon.
She's so good team.
Oh my god.
You're going to go team and get out.
Dead for me.
What the fuck out of you, Pat?
Jesus.
You're a new-roa vendory.
You're a real poly.
It's got to be my team.
I'll let you go first.
Thank you.
Well since Pat was talking about the Grand Canyon,
I've actually booked a helicopter ride through the Grand Canyon.
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
I thought that was a big doubt.
I thought he was about to go through Peyton's vagina.
And on your left, there's Peyton's vagina.
I do, guys.
It's very tight.
Hi.
On this team we have Tyler John.
Here we go.
Some people think that the biggest handprints in Hollywood
are up the Chinese team.
But they're actually on Justin Bieber's house and it's P Diddy's hand.
Baby, baby, baby, baby.
No!
Oh, when I was 13.
I was 13.
I had my first love.
I told him these ones in there.
I want a couple more before I get out of the car.
I'm going to get a little bit of a ride.
I want a couple more before I get out of this bitch.
Sorry, team.
That's all right.
You got a pain.
Peyton's been talking about how she's brought all these jokes today.
So I'm very excited to hear these.
I'm so smart.
Okay, let's go.
Seriously, all right.
So I got my friend some baby all the other day and I went,
shit, did it?
That's pretty good.
That's crazy stuff.
That's really good.
Simone Biles is the only black woman in America when they say,
put your hands up.
She goes,
I can't.
The mind games are unreal.
What do you pull an ti American guy in debt?
Trump.
I mean like ew, I would never call him.
That's our girl.
That was a little giggle shortly before.
That was a giggle for you.
You're a good girl.
Yeah.
Okay, so you're also a hilarious lady.
Slay, slay, slay, slay.
How you feeling?
Good.
Do you want to go first when we do another one?
No, I'll go.
Challenge, challenge, challenge, challenge, challenge, challenge.
Okay.
Okay, so the new quiet place movie came out.
But it's not a horror film.
It's the ditty tapes.
Ditty is getting roasted.
And he deserves it.
Fuck, ditty.
Those self-driving cars in LA,
they actually remind me of Matt's brain on the mind out.
Because you know like the lights are off but nobody's home.
She's on the routine.
I love you Matt.
It's true.
You seem as only raw jokes about themselves.
We're out the other night.
I saw these two homeless transvestites arguing on the street.
I bet you had the better outfit.
So I went over to them and said,
Timmy and Matt, you're both so beautiful.
I'm so messed up.
I'm so much.
What's the difference between American dad jokes
and Australian dad jokes?
I mean one country baller pull a gun at you if they get offended.
You.
That's a lot.
That's so bad.
That was so bad.
We did it together.
Can we come in with this ball?
These guys have been cane for these balls.
Yeah.
Apparently they're really going.
So they're going to make it snappy, huh?
I bet can I just say I heard all of those.
We know.
I'm going to wear this.
Cheers, guys.
Cheers.
Nice on girls.
Timmy got Matt debut.
Wow.
You're all fair now.
Good to see you.
There we go.
This is the table, dude.
What do you think?
It's quite nice.
First time in.
It's like a knee toe.
The couch is all the way over there.
That's where I belong.
Alright, let's send you back.
Did you guys?
You're boxing.
You're holding on.
You're just going to pull the decide.
Until I can't say America.
Yeah, you've been riding them.
To be a lot.
He's a fuck out of him, right?
Get on the wheel.
Bill, he's good.
That's the shortest debut on the table.
Hi.
It was good while it lasted.
It was great.
You're going to give it up here.
It was awesome.
I think that's what I'm saying.
Oh, the final last one.
What do you call the area between a California women's boobs?
What?
Silicon Valley.
I did that.
That's a great thing.
We did a card battle out without saying anything.
Give it to get.
Let's rock it fuel.
Straight out rock it fuel.
We should go to cheese for both of you.
Jesus Christ.
Let's rock it fuel.
Where are you going?
Slip in slides.
Hell.
Let's do that again.
Slip in slides.
Fun for everyone.
Except Justin Bieber.
He gets PTSDD.
Oh.
What?
No cap.
You don't know what daddy eats.
The Mayvatch time?
No.
Matt laughed.
Oh, that's a big one.
Hang on, sorry. Can I just, uh, how does it feel?
What? Me interrupting you.
That's the joke of the day.
Did he use laugh?
I smiled.
It's smiling, smiling.
I think he did.
I swear to God, I smiled.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
You can interrupt all you want.
What's the similarity between Ian and every product in America?
They're all from China.
Made in China.
Okay.
Sun of it.
Try a random joke that's not easy to fucking figure out.
Horrible.
Restaurant.
In America is five guys.
Which is also how he lost his virginity.
Do you see that dribbles run out of it?
You're pretty pretty pretty.
You're saying five guys.
Oh, man.
That was good, but you fuck off.
There you go.
How?
I've been seeing these robot delivery food things in America.
Yeah.
In Australia, we just call them Indians.
What's going on?
Oh, damn it.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah.
Just stare him down.
Oh, he got me staring down.
That was a great joke.
It was either that or caught sass.
Which one do you want to eat those?
That little bottle.
Do you have any of this?
Yeah, I have any.
Oh, Jesus.
Have some.
I'll have some.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's nice.
Good one, Ian.
I like that one.
Nice one, Ian.
All right, that one.
Yeah.
That's my guy.
No pain now.
No pain.
Fuck him up.
Go, go, go.
Go, go.
Go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go.
I didn't know we were in a timeless whiff concept.
Stare it down.
Ah, I like it.
I love Americans.
Good one.
That's the joke.
Oh, right.
Stop riding your joke, man.
I like it.
Come on, Ian.
And steal him like the rest of us.
No, don't be telling jokes.
I like it.
No, no, no.
Tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me, tell me.
That was the joke.
You know what I was saying?
You say?
Let me go out here.
I got pulled up by customs at the airport.
Uh-huh.
Surprise, surprise.
Always.
I looked like I have drugs on me.
And the guy was like, I need to see your papers.
I need to see your passport.
I have some questions.
And I was like, I have some questions.
Aren't you Mexican?
Shouldn't you just be like, underly, underly, underly,
get in here, brother.
I've had a Mexican work on the American borders.
I was like, having a Jew work at Auschwitz.
Oh, big.
She's surprised me.
I mean, that joke was longer than our fight.
Oh, my God.
That's my team member.
That was a great, great.
I'm so good.
Hello, my man.
Very full-ean.
So, Jor, Jor, next, tell me which other country you love.
OK, what do you call an atomic bomb in Hawaii?
What?
An ukulele.
That's so good.
They're all dead.
A ukulele.
I've ever seen a lacrosse.
Like, lacrosse.
What's up?
Like, the American spot across.
It's a lot of muscle that gets wasted.
I haven't seen that much wasted muscle since I looked at Michael J. Fox.
Oh!
You're gonna be crying.
I love foxes.
They're so cute.
OK, OK, OK.
Why was the American wolf less than a wolf?
Why was the American wolf way down upset?
Because he only got 50% of the chip.
Hey, you know what I love?
But I wrote that, so...
Hey!
We're in this car!
That's a cracker.
I like it.
I'll try one with you.
Yeah, let's have a buzz ball.
You have a rag on there.
I'm gonna try it.
Oh!
No!
You want to try it?
I don't believe this dude.
Let me try it.
Yeah, I mean, it honestly looks like a night out with Pat.
That's not very nice.
Like a night out with Pat.
OK, OK, OK.
OK.
The...
It's correct, then, I guess.
Oh, OK.
OK, that was it.
Let's get to the moving underlay.
Oh, mate.
Oh, mate, go on, buddy.
Oh, boys, I'm back.
I'm gonna have a pre-shot joke.
To pre-shot joke? Yeah, sure.
Oh, yeah, go for it.
Oh, yeah, no.
I'll have that.
Timmy, Timmy, joke off of that one.
I won't warn you.
I'm gonna ask you.
Who's the worst in America right now?
Marie.
Oh, shit.
It's actually Peyton Faru and in that joke.
Oh, no!
I'm sorry!
I'm not giving a different thought.
Don't laugh.
Keep it together.
Hello.
I've got one for you.
Funny thing is, I wrote a few of Matt's jokes today,
so I'm gonna tell him one of the ones that I gave him.
I went down on a UFC girl the other day.
Good job.
Yeah.
I've put in not me out.
Ultimate fishy shit.
Oh, my God.
Hey, Rory.
I went down on a UFC fight in the other day.
They're pussy knocked me out.
Ultimate fishy shit.
Get it!
Hey, I only do one Matt.
You told that delivery.
That's a man you wrote that does suit.
Yeah, I just write that one.
You're the hot fan.
I'm hot!
You're hot!
I'm hot.
Hello.
Pleasure.
Why are Americans good at Rubik's jokes?
Why?
Because they have a history of separating colors.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you're hot.
I'm gonna do it.
Oh, my God.
I tried so hard not to laugh at that.
That was insane.
I can hear you.
Cheers.
Learn how to say it.
Timmy.
Timmy, you can win this.
It's your debut.
Two fat chicks were next to me in a local convenience store.
One dropped a bag of jolly rogers.
Ranchers.
I've never watched a funny game of hungry hippos.
Oh, my God.
That's hilarious.
Don't laugh, Timmy.
Don't laugh.
He doesn't get it.
He got this.
That was funny, Timmy.
Timmy, that was...
That was good.
We can tell you don't know what a jolly rancher is.
No, I don't.
That's not what I'm saying.
So there's a prostitute problem in LA.
Yeah, the problem.
The problem is, they say no to me.
The smell is roast.
Yeah, Timmy.
Hold me together, then.
Let him out.
He's a good, new, racist, shameless, finish up.
What are we doing, short, listen?
Me and Casey.
When you go to say this thing,
you need such a good joke to me.
This is so hard.
You laugh to let it out.
Yeah, well, like, get him out.
Get him out.
It's just Timmy with tits.
You see this then?
And cut 20.
Bring it on.
Bring it on, Sass.
Bring it on, dude.
You got it.
Oh, no, you got it.
You're the newbie today.
Uh, George Washington, that probably had wooden teeth,
which made it really hard when he ate the beaver.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, man.
Dude, that was fine.
Get over here.
You got it.
Thank you.
You utilized it.
You were easy.
Oh, you said it.
I said it.
Sorry, man.
Dude, that was fine.